<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Matress dumped halfway down Chartham grove, 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546871</link>
<description>This is becoming a popular spot for flytiping. Maybe it needs cctv cameras.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8546871.0.jpeg?12a3b882&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Chartham Grove, West Norwood, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546871&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546871</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 21:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.433426 -0.109115</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Streetlight not working, 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546870</link>
<description>Streetlight hasn&amp;#39;t been working for months (the one nearest the green BT cabinets)&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Stapleton Road, Upper Belvedere, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546870&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Lamp post</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546870</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 21:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.476281 0.14005</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Shelter by 208, Croydon Rd, Beckenham - a red pen cross has been daubed on one of the two, side by side, perspex advertisement panels., 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546863</link>
<description>Shelter by 208, Croydon Rd, Beckenham - a red pen cross has been daubed on one of the two, side by side, perspex advertisement panels.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Croydon Road, Elmers End, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546863&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti / Flyposting on stop or shelter (non-offensive)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546863</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 21:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.399618 -0.040623</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flytip &amp; Litter, 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546830</link>
<description>Small flytip of wood pieces and various litter around this entrance/exit.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 84, High Street, Beckenham, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546830&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytip</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546830</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 20:59:14 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.4082 -0.025116</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flytip, 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546807</link>
<description>Piece of furniture left around this location.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 2-4, Fairfield Road, Beckenham, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546807&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytip</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546807</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 20:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.407371 -0.026976</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lancaster Avenue SE27 grit bin, 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546801</link>
<description>Lancaster Avenue SE27 at the side of 463 Norwood Road SE27 9DJ facing Lancaster Avenue – between Norwood Road and Dalton Street junction is a yellow plastic Lambeth grit bin graffiti tagged. Please forward fixmystreet.com link to your contractor for report map pin &amp;amp; picture.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8546801.0.jpeg?8b24fff4&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 463, Norwood Road, West Norwood, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546801&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546801</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 20:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.436444 -0.104455</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Electrical Cabinet, 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546800</link>
<description>The grey electrical cabinet at this location is wide open, unlocked, as of Sunday morning (14/12/25).&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): High Street, Beckenham, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546800&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Public Right of Way footpath</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546800</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 20:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.407791 -0.025338</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lancaster Avenue SE27 on the side wall of 463 Norwood, 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546791</link>
<description>Lancaster Avenue SE27 on the side wall of 463 Norwood Road SE27 9DJ facing Lancaster Avenue – between Norwood Road and Dalton Street junctions. Graffiti towards Dalton Street junction end on plain low down concrete render and plain red brickwork wall. Please forward fixmystreet.com link to your contractor for picture.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8546791.0.jpeg?ea8c2d90&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Lancaster Avenue, West Norwood, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546791&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546791</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 20:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.43649 -0.104352</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Another fly tip - same van as last week, 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546787</link>
<description>Another fly tip tonight - same van as the fly tip left last week. Seems to be a weekly recurrence!&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8546787.0.jpeg?1f361dc3&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Bliss Crescent, Lewisham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546787&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546787</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 20:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.470445 -0.019201</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abandoned waste bin, 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546770</link>
<description>This brown bin has been left abandoned for several weeks now. It has been left on the pavement outside the back gate of our house and is causing a nuisance. Please can you retrieve the bin, remove the contents and relocate the bin elsewhere. Thanks.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8546770.0.jpeg?1ff5b8fa&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Olney Road, Walworth, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546770&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping - Green Waste (Estates)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546770</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 20:37:52 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.484465 -0.098316</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abandoned trolley, Rollins str, 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546744</link>
<description>Trash bags and an abandonded trolley. Please remove.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8546744.0.jpeg?6d5e8d90&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Rollins Street, Peckham, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546744&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping - General (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546744</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 20:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.483521 -0.053406</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Corner of Albany St and Nash St NW1, 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546739</link>
<description>The street light is at the start of Nash St NW1 but with junction of Albany St next to block of flats called Rothay. This street light is not working.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 7-8, Albany Street, Fitzrovia, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546739&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street Lights</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546739</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 20:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.529103 -0.144242</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>At and around the bus stop (not sure if arrow is in right place), 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546733</link>
<description>A lot of litter at the bus stop here and around Thank you&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Willesden Lane, Kilburn, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546733&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street cleaning - Street needs sweeping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546733</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 20:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.544352 -0.211729</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Cars speeding at 35 - 40 mph on Sandford &amp; Ethronvi Rd, 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546722</link>
<description>I am resident living on Ethronvi Rd for the past 10 years and my house is close to the intersect between Sandford Road &amp;amp; Ethronvi Road. In both directions cars are constantly speeding hitting speeds of 35 - 40+ mph. I have witnessed over 15 car accidents in my time living here. But my biggest concern is the fact there is a nursery at the end of Sandford Road and a soft play at the end of Ethronvi Road/ near Queen street. Vulnerable people live here and there are lots of families and elderly people in this community. I don&amp;#39;t want there to be a major death or fatality before changes come about to ensure that these issues do not happen again. There needs to be speed bumps along both roads &amp;amp; or lots of speed cameras to change the delinquent behaviour of cars speeding. Deadly driving is a liability to our community and society at large and with speed cameras on these two roads along with speed bumps it can provide Bexley council with additional revenue streams and also drive down the rate of antisocial behaviour as well as fatalities.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Harcourt Road, Blendon, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546722&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other street defect</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546722</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 20:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.459443 0.134635</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Urgent Road Safety Measures Required at Sandford Road &amp; Ethronvi Road, 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546708</link>
<description>I am a local resident and have lived in this area for over three years. My home is located close to the junction of Sandford Road and Ethronvi Road, and I am writing as a concerned parent and member of the community to formally raise serious and ongoing road safety concerns.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Excessive speeding on both Sandford Road and Ethronvi Road is constant and highly visible. Vehicles regularly travel at speeds far above what is safe for a residential area, often reaching an estimated 35 to over 40 miles per hour. During my time living here, I have personally witnessed more than seven road traffic collisions at or near this junction. These incidents are not isolated and reflect a persistent pattern of dangerous driving behaviour.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This location presents a particularly high risk due to the presence of vulnerable road users. A nursery is located at the end of Sandford Road, and a children’s soft play centre operates near the end of Ethronvi Road close to Queen Street. The surrounding streets are home to many young families, elderly residents and pedestrians who rely on these roads daily.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Local and borough level data reinforces these concerns. Publicly available Transport for London and Metropolitan Police collision data shows that Bexley records hundreds of reported road traffic collisions each year, with a significant proportion occurring on residential roads. Speed is consistently cited as one of the most common contributing factors in serious and fatal collisions across the borough. Nationally, government data shows that pedestrians struck at 40 miles per hour are around five times more likely to be killed than those struck at 30 miles per hour. These risks are well understood and widely documented.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Traffic calming measures are proven to work. Department for Transport evidence shows that speed humps and raised tables can reduce average vehicle speeds by up to 25 percent and reduce injury collisions by more than half on residential roads. Speed enforcement cameras have also been shown to significantly reduce repeat speeding offences and serious collisions in high risk locations.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I am extremely concerned that without intervention it will only be a matter of time before a serious injury or fatality occurs, potentially involving a child. It should not require a tragic incident to prompt preventative action when the danger is already evident and ongoing.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I strongly urge Bexley Council to take immediate action by implementing the following measures:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Installation of speed humps or raised traffic calming features along both Sandford Road and Ethronvi Road Installation of permanent speed enforcement cameras to deter persistent speeding A formal road safety assessment and speed monitoring review of this junction and surrounding streets&amp;#10;&amp;#10;In addition to improving safety, these measures would reduce antisocial driving behaviour, lower the long term burden on emergency services and the NHS, and provide enforcement revenue that can be reinvested into local transport and safety initiatives.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This is not simply a traffic management issue. It is a public safety matter affecting children, families and older residents who should be able to move around their community without fear. I respectfully ask the Council to treat this issue with urgency and to confirm what actions will be taken and within what timeframe.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Thank you for your consideration. I look forward to your response and to seeing meaningful steps taken to protect this community.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Yours sincerely,&amp;#10;&amp;#10;A concerned resident and parent&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Ethronvi Road, Blendon, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546708&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other street defect</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546708</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 20:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.459866 0.133539</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Speed hump with chunks missing, 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546696</link>
<description>Could cause a puncture as chunks of tarmac missing with sharp edges.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Crofton Lane, Crofton, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546696&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Road Defect</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546696</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 20:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.382048 0.087645</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Foot path bridge lights not working, 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546694</link>
<description>The bridge footpath lights have not been working for weeks it’s real dark and feels unsafe as it’s so dark at night. The bridge from Churchill Road to Burghley Road. Can these be repaired asap please&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8546694.0.jpeg?4c54ffe6&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Churchill Road Footbridge, Tufnell Park, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546694&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street Lights</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546694</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 20:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.557212 -0.141627</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dead Fox, 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546642</link>
<description>Called to report a dead fox in private property and followed instructions to collect the fox in a bin bag and leave it in a public space to be collected by the council.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;It is double bagged in a black bin liner.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Located on the curve of the pinpointed location.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Peartree Way, Greenwich&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546642&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Dead animals</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546642</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 19:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.494298 0.018864</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>White Van abandoned in Alden House, 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546594</link>
<description>There is a white van with flashing lights abandoned within Alden Hose Estate. The van has been there for a few hours with the lights flashing. No one has been seen near the van since it appeared.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Duncan Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546594&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned Vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546594</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 19:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.536942 -0.060593</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Builders rubbish bag and items dumped in stairwell, 14th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546565</link>
<description>Please remove&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8546565.0.jpeg?b10599ab&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Lettsom Street, Camberwell, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546565&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping - General (Estates)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8546565</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 19:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.470351 -0.085834</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>