<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Home appliance and bags dumped on Irving Street, 26th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071994</link>
<description>Home appliance and bag dumped on Irving Street&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8071994.0.jpeg?ad07c75a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 17 - 18, Irving Street, Bloomsbury, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071994&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071994</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:36:16 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.509981 -0.129048</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Child car seat dumped in grass verge, 26th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071986</link>
<description>It positioned near the lamp postnon edge of verge, it may be hidden by parked cars.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8071986.0.jpeg?0a0b0bf4&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Alsike Road, West Heath, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071986&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Grass Verges</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071986</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 01:49:33 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.491374 0.125347</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Blue barrel and nitrous oxide cannisters, 26th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071985</link>
<description>They have been there a few weeks. Barrel contains left over food. Noodles or something. Barrel is heavy. Opposite this, there&amp;#39;s nitrous oxide cannisters which are possibly hazardous&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8071985.0.jpeg?f9f5beb1&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Alsike Road, West Heath, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071985&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071985</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 01:45:54 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.491416 0.124905</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Outside 23 Rochester Terrace, 26th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071982</link>
<description>Overgrown hedge is blocking the footpath.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8071982.0.jpeg?5bf4e0fe&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 21, Rochester Terrace, Kentish Town, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071982&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavement Defect</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071982</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 01:33:24 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.545247 -0.140106</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>A correction of address regarding garden complaints., 26th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071971</link>
<description>I would like to make a correction regarding recent complaints made about the state of the garden in Manor Way. The address stated in the reports is incorrect and is that of an upstairs maisonette above number 36 as you can see in the map attached. The garden that the complaints are being made about belongs to 108 Magpie Hall Lane. Thank you&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8071971.0.jpeg?1209eb33&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Magpie Hall Lane, Bromley Common, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071971&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Litter and Detritus</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071971</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 01:11:16 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.384723 0.045992</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street light out making it very dark., 26th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071964</link>
<description>Street light is out . My daughter works late and is afraid to walk past this part on her own. This is the second time I’ve reported this issue , first time being 3 months ago ! It has the number 36 on the side of that helps with locating it . Thanks&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Piccadilly, Mayfair, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071964&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street lights</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071964</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:52:40 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.505373 -0.145345</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>1-14 Thetford House - Lift H&amp;S issue - needs urgent cleaning, 26th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071962</link>
<description>There has been dog or human waste left in the lift for at least three days, which poses a serious health and safety issue that requires urgent attention. This situation is particularly concerning for residents with disabilities who are trapped and unable to use the lift.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The council and the police only monitor the building during office hours, when these incidents are less likely to occur. There is no nighttime patrol or CCTV monitoring to address the ongoing issues!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;We are constantly facing problems with drug users frequenting our estate, using the communal areas as a restroom, a bar, or a place to sleep, which has made all residents and tenants fearful to come and go from their properties.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;When will we finally be equipped with the long-awaited safety entrance intercom system and/or CCTV?&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Moreover, the communal lift landings have not been cleaned in almost a year, which makes me question why I am paying service charges. I will be filing an official complaint with the tribunal, as this situation has persisted for far too long without any action taken, despite multiple reports.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Abbey Street, Old Kent Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071962&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Lift Cleaning Service</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071962</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:42:28 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.498222 -0.077215</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The glass is smashed, 26th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071961</link>
<description>Smashed glass&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Bell Green, Perry Vale, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071961&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Damage - smashed glass or panels / jagged metal edges on shelter</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071961</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:38:51 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.429494 -0.037504</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Wood broke on bridge, near orange and grey flats, 26th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071953</link>
<description>Woods broke on bridge, the last one coming from ferry on to Woolwich dockyard, my son nearly fall down it , been broken months&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8071953.0.jpeg?8172e21a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Spindle Close, Charlton Riverside, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071953&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/Footpaths Repairs</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071953</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:18:20 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.493702 0.050503</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Wooden Post, 26th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071949</link>
<description>Scadbury Park Nature Reserve, St Paul’s Cray/Chislehurst: A wooden post which has signs on it advising the public of no cycling or horse riding has come out of the ground as per the attached picture. The post is located as you pass the Moated Manor and you head in the direction towards the field where the horses are.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8071949.0.jpeg?640b4632&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): The Drive, St Paul&#39;s Cray, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071949&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Park Repairs</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071949</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:10:34 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.416212 0.093984</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Litter Bins Full, 26th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071941</link>
<description>Inside Scadbury Park Nature Reserve, Chislehurst: Please could you empty several full litter bins within the “Picnic Area” of the woods.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): The Drive, St Paul&#39;s Cray, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071941&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Overflowing litter/dog bin</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071941</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:05:14 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.415186 0.090897</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dumped Items, 26th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071938</link>
<description>Inside Scadbury Park Nature Reserve, Chislehurst via Perry Street public car park heading towards St Paul’s Green in St Paul’s Cray: There are white sheets which have been dumped - please see the attached picture. You recently closed my previous report on here stating that you couldn’t locate them however they are very much still there and are easy to spot. Please could you remove them.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8071938.0.jpeg?06196d07&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): The Drive, St Paul&#39;s Cray, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071938&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytip in Park</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071938</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:02:45 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.410186 0.089481</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Metropolitan police commissioners camera displacing antisocial behavior to other areas of the neighborhood well done., 25th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071934</link>
<description>Metropolitan police commissioners camera displacing antisocial behavior to other areas of the neighborhood well done.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8071934.0.jpeg?fb2ba460&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Merriam Avenue, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071934&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071934</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 23:59:52 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.545318 -0.028787</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ongoing fly tipping, 25th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071915</link>
<description>Continuous fly tipping every single week. This has been previously witnessed to be residents above row of shops. Why is this being allowed to continue. Bio hazard - food rotting smells, flies everywhere.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8071915.0.jpeg?75cc6aeb&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Ellenborough Road, North Cray, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071915&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Grass Verges</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071915</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 23:40:10 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.420151 0.131827</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lack of maintenance at this location dead large palm trees dead bushes posing a hazard to disabled and pedestrians. Trees and bushes need cutting down before they cause injury., 25th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071896</link>
<description>Maintenance required public common land overgrown bushes dead trees. Posing obstruction for disabled people and residents. This space is meant for community and residents which we cannot use due to lack of maintenance.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8071896.0.jpeg?32185eb5&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Daintry Way, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071896&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071896</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 23:28:48 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.546003 -0.028771</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Homeless and drug issue in Goulton Road, 25th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071894</link>
<description>Residents have reported feeling unsafe, particularly during evening hours, as the presence of drug activity often attracts antisocial behaviour. The issue also poses health and hygiene risks, with discarded drug paraphernalia sometimes left in public areas&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Goulton Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071894&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071894</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 23:28:07 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.552669 -0.053719</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dear local Trowbridge Residence and leaseholders please be advised and beware of organised gang criminal group that are stealing motor vehicles on a daily basis at this location and operating from Beanacre Cl, London E9 5JY,Merriam Ave, London E9 5LS has been reported to the local Hackney council anti-social behavior department and the metropolitan police service which seem to be lazy to act or do anything about this anti-social behavior and criminal activity. Criminal gang have recently stolen a white Toyota from Brentwood, also stole a gray Audi from Richmond Kew gardens, they have nicked cars from Ilford and Romford, stealing car Kent, they are stealing all different types of cars but they seem to have a thing for Toyota&#39;s Criminals are stealing motor vehicles and robbery on a daily basis in all different boroughs. once they have stolen the vehicle. they then drive the stolen car back to the location at Beanacre Cl, London E9 5JY,Merriam Ave, London E9 5LS to strip the vehicle down and change the identity of the stolen car i.e clone plates switch to avoid police capture an ampr cameras, throwing number plates down Hackney council manhole cover drainage system,removing GPS trackers, previous owners property and possessions are then discarded in and around public footpath on the floor,on roofs,in gardens, down drain covers, criminal gang discard anything that can link them to the robbery or crime by discarding evidence. Criminal activity takes place all hours,early hours daytime,morning.Organise gang also using mopeds to do the robberies and cars. The gang are wearing dark clothing tracksuits with face masks and gloves. The gang possibly are Irish travellers. By the sounds of it the local council do not care about stolen vehicles and anti-social behavior also the metropolitan police show an incompetence attitude towards the reports that are being made in regards to stolen vehicles and robbery allowing this to happen. Residence and leaseholders have to remember at the end of the day Hackney council and the police get a wage and they go home they don&#39;t care. Safer neighbourhood police have allowed this to go on for many years.SNT Not using their initiative and being lazy to investigate. Hackney council and the metropolitan police safe and neighborhood team need to work alongside with Hackney council to come up with a strategic plan to tackle these issues. Assigning a DS officer to investigate.who has experienced in organised crime not like snt and surveillance operations., 25th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071884</link>
<description>Dear local Trowbridge Residence and leaseholders please be advised and beware of organised gang criminal group that are stealing motor vehicles on a daily basis at this location and operating from Beanacre Cl, London E9 5JY,Merriam Ave, London E9 5LS has b&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8071884.0.jpeg?fb2ba460&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Mare Street, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071884&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071884</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 23:21:35 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.544881 -0.056788</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rubbish dumped, 25th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071875</link>
<description>Number 36 dumped rubbish into alley at 3AM&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8071875.0.jpeg?7bbc8903&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Russell Close, Barnehurst, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071875&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Alleyway</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071875</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 23:18:24 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.457765 0.14574</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>There was a group of counsellors, Cllr Jessica Webb, volunteer Ellie,Cllr Christopher Kennedy, was seen on 03/08/25 at 14:37pm in Merriam Ave, garages E9 5NE observing looking at a member of public,residence private paperwork, property items laying on the floor discarded from a vehicle theft or robbery which has been discarded inbetween the garages out of sight of the metropolitan police commissioners camera. The councillors did not take any action or report this. Councillors turn a blind eye but they were not to know it was connected with a robbery. Councillors just looked at it like someone&#39;s dumped their rubbish which is not the case. This is a victim of crimes property. This behaviour has been witnessed time and time and again authority and safer neighbourhood police do nothing. This has been repeatedly going on for a number of years criminal activity what is the councillors doing about this you have seen with your own eyes now what action are you taking. You want people to vote for you but you do not serve the community in this anti-social behaviour and criminal activity which you have witnessed and seen the evidence. This is not the first time there is multiple victims over the last couple of years property being discarded out of stolen vehicles. Where is a large group of residents involved in criminal activity who live on the Trowbridge estates. I do not have much hope in the councillors or authority because they do nothing.They are lazy and competent people and do not deserve to serve the community. leave residents,tenants to suffer this anti-social behavior.The evidence and facts are laying in front of you. Do your jobs and your duties you signed up for and serve your community., 25th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071871</link>
<description>There was a group of counsellors, Cllr Jessica Webb, volunteer Ellie,Cllr Christopher Kennedy, was seen on 03/08/25 at 14:37pm in Merriam Ave, garages E9 5NE observing looking at a member of public,residence private paperwork, property items laying on the&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8071871.0.jpeg?7f4ac124&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Hillman Street, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071871&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071871</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 23:15:43 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.545176 -0.057494</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dear Simon Priscilla and Denise Corbin housing managers of Hackney wick could you please address this issue.Osborne road antisocial behaviour lime bike.You have decided or have struct a deal with the Lime bike company allocating 3 car parking spaces in Osborne road which is an absolute nightmare for the residents. How can you justify this decision taking up car space for Lime bikes that pay no insurance, no road tax, and not paying for car parking permit like I am, why are privileged. This is also causing ASB especially at the weekend. Why have Hackney council given Lime preferential treatment I am sick of moving these bikes out of my way because of the outrages decision you&#39;ve made. I have been a resident in Osborne road for 25 years and never experience such disruption. I have always owned a car and I have always paid from 2012 for a parking permit yet the nuisance bike get everything for free. I have asked in the pass to have a designated parking space with a very valid reason and guess what you refused but, now you give LIME BIKES FREE Parking which is causing a nuisance. Whoever, thought this was a good idea perhaps you should have this going on outside your own home and see how you like it. Lastly they are also leaving bikes near peoples cars I came out one day to find a bike learning on peoples cars. I THINK YOU SHOULD REMOVE THIS IDEA IMMEDIATELY. Other boroughs are scrapping them completed because of the nuisance these bikes are causing is seen on TV las week. Good morning Britain. I will be showing pictures of these bikes on Good Morning Britian and explaing to them what an issue it is causing in this cul-da-sac . The users leave the bikes anywhere they feel like it, I have had to personally move bikes in order to get passed when driving my car and when walking out of my front door. Friday and Saturday nights are worse than a week day. Is there a deal thats been made with the company to allow this prefe., 25th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071868</link>
<description>Dear Simon Priscilla and Denise Corbin housing managers of Hackney wick could you please address this issue.Osborne road antisocial behaviour lime bike.You have decided or have struct a deal with the Lime bike company allocating 3 car parking spaces in Osb&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8071868.0.jpeg?e86aafb9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Reading Lane, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071868&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8071868</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 23:11:42 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.54505 -0.057755</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>