<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Couple of chairs and rubbish fly tipped, 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032986</link>
<description>There is a build up of junk in the bike stores&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8032986.0.jpeg?278c4d18&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Balls Pond Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032986&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032986</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 11:13:59 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.545994 -0.077153</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Kerb needs sweeping, litter and leaves, 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032983</link>
<description>Never gets done .during street cleansing&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Cowper Road, Widmore, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032983&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Leafing</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032983</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 11:13:23 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.39458 0.035581</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Destroyed wooden cabinet, 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032982</link>
<description>Wooden cabinet flytipped and has since been run over and thrown against the tree&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8032982.0.jpeg?0a9bd902&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Brett Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032982&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032982</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 11:13:32 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.548733 -0.055984</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Both sides of road in kerb, street cleansing not done, 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032976</link>
<description>Loads of litter along the kerb on both sides of road, needs proper clearing and sweeping&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Havelock Road, Widmore, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032976&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Litter and Detritus</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032976</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 11:12:46 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.397041 0.029635</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bin overflowing and rubbish on footpath, 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032973</link>
<description>Please empty and clear&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 48, Homesdale Road, Widmore, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032973&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Public Litter Bin</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032973</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 11:12:10 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.396984 0.029375</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bin overflowing abd rubbish dumped around it, 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032967</link>
<description>Please empty and clear&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 8, Homesdale Road, Widmore, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032967&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Public Litter Bin</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032967</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 11:11:34 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.396302 0.028031</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Vehicle has hit bollard overnight causing it to bend and the pavement break. Obstruction., 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032956</link>
<description>This has happened overnight. I left my flat to go out and saw that the bollard was at an angle. It’s clearly been hit by a vehicle and this has caused it to buckle the pavement. It’s an obstruction and eye sore.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8032956.0.jpeg?0e1c14bb&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Westcombe Hill, East Greenwich, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032956&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/Footpaths Repairs</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032956</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 11:09:24 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.47791 0.01926</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Littering and street remains u swept, 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032948</link>
<description>Continued build up of litter which encourages dumping due to lack of bin. Please help. Stepping out into this day in day out is depressing&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8032948.0.jpeg?3e5ed333&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Queens Drive, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032948&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Littering</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032948</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 11:11:07 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.560807 -0.092078</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dead rats, 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032941</link>
<description>We have found two dead rats in the bin area, located in front of Flat A. The smell is very strong and unpleasant, and there are children living in the property. We kindly request urgent cleaning and pest control support for the bin area. Anjith Somarajan&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Albert Road, Poverest, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032941&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Dead Animal</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032941</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 11:06:14 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.383999 0.10936</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>BBC NEWS Hackney scraps &#39;flawed&#39; disabled parking system a close-up of a parking bay with a disability logo painted on the tarmac, of a representation of a person in a wheelchair Image caption, 149 individuals were refused a permit since January 2024 Josef Steen Local Democracy Reporting Service Published 25 May 2025 Hackney Council has scrapped a &quot;flawed&quot; scoring system it used for disabled parking assessments which denied residents of blue badges. The additional guidelines in this system were found to have caused &quot;injustice&quot;. Councillor Christopher Kennedy, the borough&#39;s health and social care chief, confirmed the council would write to all 149 individuals refused a permit since January 2024. The verdict came after resident Mrs D appealed to the regulator after the council refused to renew her blue badge, according to the Local Democracy Reporting Service., external &#39;Partially accepted&#39; In April, the Local Government and Social Care Ombudsman, Amerdeep Somal, decided that Hackney&#39;s &quot;flawed policy&quot; went against government guidance. She added that it had made it &quot;very difficult for people with disabilities to qualify for a permit&quot; and that it was &quot;likely more people were also denied a permit when they would have qualified, had Hackney&#39;s guidance followed that of the government&quot;. During a cabinet meeting at the Town Hall, Mr Kennedy said Hackney Council honoured the regulator&#39;s ruling by apologising to Mrs D, paying her £500 and offering her another in-person appraisal. He added that the watchdog &quot;did not tell us that Mrs D should be given a blue badge&quot;, but rather that she was entitled to another assessment without the flawed scoring system. The Greens&#39; co-leader, Zoë Garbett, asked the health and social care chief if the local authority had identified any lessons it had learned from the process to avoid a repeat of the situation. But Mr Kennedy said this was &quot;very difficult&quot; because of the circumstances under which she was given a blue badge in the first places. &quot;Mrs D was offered a permit without a physical in-person assessment during the pandemic,&quot; he said. &quot;Her subsequent desire to really investigate how we did our assessments was driven by the fact that the subsequent decisions from an in-person assessment did not match with what happened when there were no in-person assessments.&quot; However, he acknowledged the council had not &quot;handled it very well as an organisation&quot; and had communicated poorly with the resident, including getting her date of birth wrong. In April, the watchdog said the council had only &quot;partially&quot; accepted its findings, and disputed the conclusion that it had caused injustice. A Town Hall spokesperson subsequently told the Local Democracy Reporting Service (LDRS) it accepted the findings but was &quot;confident&quot; the majority of blue badge applications were assessed correctly and would undertake a review to ensure processes were &quot;fair and robust&quot;.Hackney Wick ward,Trowbridge estate councillors &amp; Hackney council authority discriminating local residents who are vulnerable disabled people.Disgraceful &amp; sickening behaviour you expect more from your local authority. Council picking on vulnerable people, 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032905</link>
<description>Hackney Wick ward,Trowbridge estate councillors &amp;amp; Hackney council authority discriminating local residents who are vulnerable disabled people.Disgraceful &amp;amp; sickening behaviour you expect more from your local authority. Council picking on vulnerable people&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8032905.0.jpeg?d19dc150&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Reading Lane, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032905&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032905</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 10:59:21 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.544836 -0.057198</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Gipsy Road SE27 9QY outside property 197 (, 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032902</link>
<description>Gipsy Road SE27 9QY outside property 197 (ie between Salter’s Hill and Rommany Rd junctions) is a traffic island – Keep Left board graffiti tagged on said island – currently on rear face which is black plastic. Please forward fixmystreet.com link to your contractor for picture and Google Streetview link: https://www.google.com/maps/@51.4269337,-0.0891255,3a,61.4y,290.73h,79.54t/data=!3m7!1e1!3m5!1sTqogmk8XrrcUFqX8QoXvZw!2e0!6shttps:%2F%2Fstreetviewpixels-pa.googleapis.com%2Fv1%2Fthumbnail%3Fcb_client%3Dmaps_sv.tactile%26w%3D900%26h%3D600%26pitch%3D10.462980400901259%26panoid%3DTqogmk8XrrcUFqX8QoXvZw%26yaw%3D290.7295668531371!7i16384!8i8192?authuser=0&amp;amp;entry=ttu&amp;amp;g_ep=EgoyMDI1MDgxMy4wIKXMDSoASAFQAw%3D%3D&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8032902.0.jpeg?5f67f952&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 188, Gipsy Road, West Norwood, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032902&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032902</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 10:59:10 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.426925 -0.08943</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abandoned rubbish by cycle storage, 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032898</link>
<description>This rubbish has been here for 4-6 weeks&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8032898.0.jpeg?eb3f5ea3&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Norcott Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032898&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032898</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 10:58:57 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.561362 -0.065571</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Also reported under Parks, But this is a Tree Issue(s) within a Bromley Park, 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032877</link>
<description>In Church House Gardens the trees are generally not being look after. Beautiful acer tree are being swamped by samplings, ivy, and brambles. There is thisone tree that looks to be very distressed. Possibly case of developed Ash-Die-Back. There is the potential to collapse onto the recently sold Churchill Theatre (now owne by Galliard proterties) with potential insurance claim. Please could this investigated by the Bromley TREE team (and any required action taken) along with ALL the tree within the park. A report made available so that a managment stratagey can be developed along with the Friends group to bring these gardens back from the brink.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8032877.0.jpeg?1a97326c&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Tetty Way, Plaistow, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032877&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree Requires Pruning</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032877</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 10:53:02 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.403672 0.013989</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dangerous shattered glass pane, 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032851</link>
<description>Glass panes have been dumped by the bus stop bin. The reason I choose hazardous is because the glass has shattered all over the pavement and the road - right where the buses stop so a danger to bus passengers and buses&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8032851.0.jpeg?45209ef8&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 410, Wickham Lane, Plumstead, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032851&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032851</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 10:46:16 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.476034 0.108172</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dangerous shattered glass pane, 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032850</link>
<description>Glass panes have been dumped by the bus stop bin. The reason I choose hazardous is because the glass has shattered all over the pavement and the road - right where the buses stop so a danger to bus passengers and buses&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8032850.0.jpeg?45209ef8&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 410, Wickham Lane, Plumstead, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032850&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032850</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 10:46:25 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.476034 0.108172</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>What is the mayor of Hackney doing about all these road closures due to works the mayor of Hackney needs to open alternative roads the ease the traffic flow. What is the mayor of Hackney doing about Chatsworth Rd, London new road ltn closure causing chaos on surrounding streets and even for the local homerton hospital ambulances struggling to get emergency patients to the hospital due to the mayor&#39;s ultra low street sign being enforced today hac01, 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032846</link>
<description>What is the mayor of Hackney doing about all these road closures due to works the mayor of Hackney needs to open alternative roads the ease the traffic flow. What is the mayor of Hackney doing about Chatsworth Rd, London new road ltn closure causing chaos&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8032846.0.jpeg?a13c0fb8&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Chatsworth Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032846&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032846</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 10:44:54 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.552012 -0.044078</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dumped bins, 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032843</link>
<description>Causing an obstruction and creating additional rubbish to be dumped&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8032843.0.jpeg?acb25231&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Rangefield Road, Sundridge, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032843&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytip</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032843</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 10:44:44 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.421184 0.018001</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Yet another mattress, 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032841</link>
<description>Fly tipped&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8032841.0.jpeg?997a45e0&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Downham Woodland Walk, Downham, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032841&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly-Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032841</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 10:43:50 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.428636 -0.001659</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rommary Road SE27 next to the junction with Gipsy, 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032839</link>
<description>Rommary Road SE27 next to the junction with Gipsy Road is a green Lambeth plastic road sweeper’s bag bin – tagged. Please forward fixmystreet.com link to your contractor for picture and Google Streetview weblink: https://www.google.com/maps/@51.42701,-0.0895279,3a,50.7y,331.64h,83.12t/data=!3m7!1e1!3m5!1sfkNd5UJ5Qi44wY8A0ylkPg!2e0!6shttps:%2F%2Fstreetviewpixels-pa.googleapis.com%2Fv1%2Fthumbnail%3Fcb_client%3Dmaps_sv.tactile%26w%3D900%26h%3D600%26pitch%3D6.883260704147261%26panoid%3DfkNd5UJ5Qi44wY8A0ylkPg%26yaw%3D331.63547719405955!7i16384!8i8192?authuser=0&amp;amp;entry=ttu&amp;amp;g_ep=EgoyMDI1MDgxMy4wIKXMDSoASAFQAw%3D%3D&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8032839.0.jpeg?303d12fa&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 188, Gipsy Road, West Norwood, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032839&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032839</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 10:43:21 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.42705 -0.089613</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>What is the mayor of Hackney doing about all these road closures due to works the mayor of Hackney needs to open alternative roads the ease the traffic flow. What is the mayor of Hackney doing about Chatsworth Rd, London new road ltn closure causing chaos on surrounding streets and even for the local homerton hospital ambulances struggling to get emergency patients to the hospital due to the mayor&#39;s ultra low street sign being enforced today hac01, 16th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032830</link>
<description>What is the mayor of Hackney doing about all these road closures due to works the mayor of Hackney needs to open alternative roads the ease the traffic flow. What is the mayor of Hackney doing about Chatsworth Rd, London new road ltn closure causing chaos&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8032830.0.jpeg?a13c0fb8&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Mare Street, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032830&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8032830</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 10:41:37 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.545145 -0.056207</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>