<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Defect in middle of the south end of Hatherley Road, 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041441</link>
<description>This &amp;quot;repaired&amp;quot; defect on central area of the fancy road surface is now a defect in its own right.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hatherley Road, Longlands, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041441&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Damaged road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041441</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:16:46 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.426379 0.102788</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rubbish dumped in woods Poverest Park, 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041404</link>
<description>Several bags of household rubbish dumped in woods next to vehicle barrier at end of access road off Footbury Hill Rd. Bags have split.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8041404.0.jpeg?dbaa3de9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Perry Hall Road, Poverest, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041404&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytip in Park</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041404</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:14:46 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.384325 0.097622</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ongoing Fly-Tipping at Entrance to Bostall Manorway Estate, 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041387</link>
<description>Subject: Ongoing Fly-Tipping at Entrance to Bostall Manorway Estate&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Dear Royal Borough of Greenwich,&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I’m writing to report another case of fly-tipping near my home at 1 Bostall Manorway, Abbey Wood, London SE2 9EE—the first house at the entrance to the estate.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This time, someone dumped a large garden swing chair right next to my property. Unfortunately, this is not a one-off incident. Every two to three days, I find new rubbish dumped near the entrance—items like fridges, wardrobes, loft junk, and even broken glass, which is especially dangerous for my children and other families living nearby.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Despite reporting this issue many times, some items—like two small fridges—have still not been removed. One has now been moved to the opposite side of the street, directly across from my house.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Several times, I’ve asked the council to install a sign stating “No Dumping of Rubbish” at the entrance, but nothing has been done. The situation is becoming very frustrating and unsafe.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Please can you take urgent action to:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;• Remove the dumped items&amp;#10;&amp;#10;• Consider placing a clear sign to discourage future fly-tipping&amp;#10;&amp;#10;• Increase monitoring or enforcement in this area&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Thank you for your attention and support.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8041387.0.jpeg?61383a3a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Bostall Manorway, Abbey Wood, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041387&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041387</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:10:08 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.489855 0.11361</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Graffiti on Prince Consort Road close to Holly Trinity Church, 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041367</link>
<description>As above.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8041367.0.jpeg?77a6b6a3&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Prince Consort Road, Knightsbridge, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041367&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti and flyposting</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041367</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:07:11 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.499845 -0.178166</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Litter left on the street, 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041365</link>
<description>Litter on the street&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8041365.0.jpeg?ae27519a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Alfearn Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041365&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Littering</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041365</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:07:11 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.555341 -0.0529</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Overgrown shrubbery blocking footpath and parking spaces., 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041359</link>
<description>The shrub has completely overgrown the footpath, making it unusable for pedestrians, and is now encroaching into the road. This is restricting adjacent parking spaces, preventing cars from fitting properly and blocking doors from opening on the shrub side.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8041359.0.jpeg?7fdab6f9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Badsworth Road, Camberwell, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041359&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree Issues on the Highway</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041359</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:06:42 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.476529 -0.096289</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Nettles &amp; Brambles risk encroaching and closing pathway, 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041358</link>
<description>There are an increasing number of brambles, nettles and other vegetation growing on the footpath between Kemnal Road and Green Lane. The pathway as a consequence is becoming narrower and will soon be closed over and prohibit its use by the public. Nettles are at waist height and present a danger to children. The brambles exist at various heights and could hurt children and adults alike. At one time it was possible for two adults to walk along side by side but no longer. This current issue ha# persisted since springtime and reoccurs from year to year.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8041358.0.jpeg?1e3cba0f&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Acorn Close, Chislehurst, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041358&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Public Right of Way footpath</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041358</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:07:04 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.420695 0.076238</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Shit in Nappies, 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041291</link>
<description>Dirty soiled nappies and maybe sanitary towels at corner 25 Buckler Gardens SE9 and outside on pavement. Put up cameras and catch these dirty animals that dump rubbish, black bags and what not on our estate. You move shit in you get shit on estate!&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8041291.0.jpeg?9a15e1f4&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Longcroft, Coldharbour, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041291&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041291</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:02:04 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.429895 0.055522</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>A Fly Tipping problem has been found, 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041290</link>
<description>Commercial waste being piled up in front of 15 bradbury street&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Bradbury Street, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041290&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041290</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:01:21 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.548588 -0.076095</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Wheelie Bins Dumped, 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041283</link>
<description>There are two wheelie bins dumped at this location on the footway (NOT PRIVATE LAND) which do not seem to belong to any of the houses in this area. Please could they be removed as they are attracting more rubbish. This is opposite 56 Roslin Way at the entrance to the service road at the rear of 35 Roslin Way.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8041283.0.jpeg?c848203a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Roslin Way, Sundridge, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041283&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytip</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041283</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:00:04 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.42068 0.018184</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ironing board dumped FFS, 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041278</link>
<description>Another fly-tipped household item left on Pellerin Rd ffs&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Pellerin Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041278&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041278</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 14:58:44 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.551529 -0.078306</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The whole street is a mess and need a good sweep up please., 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041276</link>
<description>I could upload 40 pictures with varies items dumped along side Eglinton Road.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Please send a crew to clean up the road. It feels and looks awful.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Thank you.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8041276.0.jpeg?194d32eb&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 169, Eglinton Road, Shooters Hill, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041276&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street Spillage</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041276</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 14:58:26 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.480268 0.06622</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Draincover side of the road, 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041257</link>
<description>Siddcup bypass a20 street lamps are all numbered stree lamp nearest to it SBP273-275 Southbound sides&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 50, Tyron Way, Longlands, Sidcup, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041257&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Manhole covers</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041257</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 14:57:04 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.423564 0.092145</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hundreds of RATS living under recycling bins and in surrounding undergrowth, 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041228</link>
<description>Hundreds of RATS are living under the recycling bins and in surrounding undergrowth. They terrify the thousands of local residents and tourist who walk along the canal towpath. This extends from the food waste bin all along the towpath under the walk bridge.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8041228.0.jpeg?6dbc526e&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Delamere Terrace, Maida Vale, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041228&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Animal Nuisance</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041228</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 14:52:29 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.52222 -0.187705</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dead fox outside bin store, 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041206</link>
<description>A dead fox was reported by a resident at Thyme Close&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8041206.0.jpeg?18393ea6&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Thyme Close, Kidbrooke, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041206&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Dead animals</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041206</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 14:50:10 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.463326 0.030955</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dumped double bed and mattress, 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041168</link>
<description>Fly tipping&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Brightside Road, Hither Green, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041168&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly-Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041168</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 14:44:34 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.450162 -0.003706</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Owner failing to pick up dog poop, 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041167</link>
<description>A bald man in his mid 50’s attends the park nearly every morning around 11.30am with his brown and white spaniel. His dog is aggressive towards other dogs in the park, but the man refuses to put his spaniel called Jimmy on the lead or to muzzle him. The dog wanders the park pooing as and when he wants and the owner does not pick up after him. The dog regularly goes into the pond (which according to all the signs in the park, is a designated water body, so it’s illegal to do so) and steals the birds eggs. Again, the owner refuses to put the dog on a lead. The man often returns to the park in the early evenings around 5.30-6pm with a four pack of Fosters lager, drinks alcohol in the park, letting his dog poop in the park, not picking up after it and letting it be aggressive towards other dogs. Last week a man had to tell the owner not urinate up against the green hoarding in the park as it’s disgusting, there were women and children in the park. Please can the park wardens try and deal with this man’s behaviour and ensure the dog is under control and the owner picks up the dog poop.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Rochester Avenue, Widmore, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041167&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Dog Related Incident</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041167</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 14:44:28 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.402958 0.021543</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree outside no.33, 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041164</link>
<description>A new tree was planted earlier this year, but the water bag that was fitted when the tree was planted has always had a large rip in it. The tree hasn&amp;#39;t been watered at all (other than by local residents when possible), even when the company comes and waters the rest of the new trees on the street. I have seen them in the past come, look at the broken water bag and then drive off. The tree is not doing well, and looks as if it is dying. The rest of the street trees are thriving. I have contacted Street Tree directly as they were the ones that planted it, however they claim it isn&amp;#39;t their tree, even though they planted the rest of the street&amp;#39;s trees, and this tree outside 33 has the same label, tree type, water bag brand etc. as the rest of the trees down the road. It is confusing as Camden&amp;#39;s street tree map identifies all of the trees on the road, with all their new information, but this tree&amp;#39;s information still provides the old, very mature tree that was cut down early this year, so the new young tree that has been planted in its place isn&amp;#39;t on the interactive map. The tree needs a new water bag and a lot of watering!&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): St Albans Road, Dartmouth Park, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041164&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Watering - Watering bag damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041164</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 14:47:00 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.561759 -0.147076</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>RE16YOG-black Volkswagen Caddy, 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041135</link>
<description>RE16YOG-black Volkswagen Caddy&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This vehicle has been dumped outside 36 Boundary Road for two months. Vehicle has been broken into. Reported several times by neighbours over the last two month, but nothing has been done. It is the Councils responsibility to deal with abandoned vehicles. Please remove.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 28, Boundary Road, Falconwood, Sidcup, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041135&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned and untaxed vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041135</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 14:39:54 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.452579 0.087397</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Mice infestation, 18th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041111</link>
<description>Children’s park within Lancaster estate bushes that have been unkept are running a live with mice !!! Bins in children park are not emptied, safety flooring around swings has lifted and is a serious trip hazard, and dog owners are using it and not cleaning up at her there dogs , health and safety concerns has this park been forgotten about are our children not important&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Lancaster Street, Elephant and Castle, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041111&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Parks/landscapes</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8041111</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 14:35:14 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.499723 -0.102307</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>