<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Loose setts at top of Hatherley Road, 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154474</link>
<description>The granite setts forming the road surface at the top of Hatherley Road (Sidcup High St end) are loose and not fixed securely - they make an unacceptable amount of noise when you drive over them and loose setts are a hazardous surface for cars and pedestrians that obviously needs to be replaced. These issues are far more important than the look of the setts - in fact the loose setts makes Sidcup look like a badly maintained area - PLEASE can you just replace them with normal road surface asap. Also it is dangerous for children and the partially sighted - there is no clear separation between the road and the pavement. This problem has been there for over a year (far too long).&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hatherley Road, Longlands, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154474&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Damaged road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154474</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:12:13 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.426587 0.10288</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Loose setts at to of Hadlow Road, 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154467</link>
<description>The granite setts forming the road surface at the top of Hadlow Road (Sidcup High St end) are loose and not fixed securely - they make an unacceptable amount of noise when you drive over them and loose setts are a hazardous surface for cars and pedestrians that obviously needs to be replaced. These issues are far more important than the look of the setts - in fact the loose setts makes Sidcup look like a badly maintained area - PLEASE can you just replace them with normal road surface asap. Also it is dangerous for children and the partially sighted - there is no clear separation between the road and the pavement. This problem has been there for over a year (far too long).&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hadlow Road, Longlands, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154467&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Damaged road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154467</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:07:51 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.425831 0.104683</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large wooden board dumped on pavement, 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154462</link>
<description>Large wooden board dumped on pavement, blocking pedestrian access&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Waverley Crescent, Plumstead, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154462&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154462</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:06:10 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.483888 0.08259</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dead animal on pavement, Limewood Road near to Hurst Rd corner, 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154450</link>
<description>Dead animal seen today (11th Sept) in the morning in the above location&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 26, Limewood Road, Northumberland Heath, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154450&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Dead animal</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154450</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:00:10 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.474293 0.163679</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Stuff dumped in road, 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154448</link>
<description>As above&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8154448.0.jpeg?89119955&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Brooke Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154448&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154448</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:57:10 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.560328 -0.069583</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Car not insured, 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154418</link>
<description>There is a blue citroen ax parked on meaford way which is not insured and is causing a hazard. it is parked about 2 ft away from kerb and makes the road very narrow to pass especially with the dumped red vw polo and abandoned black trailer in same area. it is impossible to access the units for deliveries in large lorries.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Meaford Way, Anerley, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154418&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicle</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154418</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:44:56 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.416877 -0.060347</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bollard defaced, 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154409</link>
<description>This bollard was defaced by a utility firm YEARS ago. The tape has been there ever since. All over Westminster utility companies are defacing street furniture in this way and it is never cleaned up. I recently returned from a drive all round France Spain and Portugal - I saw nothing like this anywhere! Can our council please show some civic pride and clean this stuff up? And can the utility companies defacing our environment please be called to account?&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8154409.0.jpeg?64dc1416&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 20, Great Peter Street, Millbank, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154409&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Signs and bollards</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154409</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:42:41 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.496961 -0.130654</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Overgrown shrubs blocking public payment for the school run., 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154408</link>
<description>Residents are not trimming shrubs. Overgrown shrubs block pavement where children walk to school. Half of the public pavement is blocked. Soon we won’t be able to pass through at all.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8154408.0.jpeg?b0d152db&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Malling Way, Hayes, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154408&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Overhanging Vegetation from private land</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154408</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:43:00 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.384796 0.008577</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dumped black trailer, 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154401</link>
<description>There is a dumped black trailer on meaford way anerley it is causing a problem for vehicles delivering to units and also makes road very narrow it is opposite reported red vw polo&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Meaford Way, Anerley, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154401&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicle</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154401</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:39:42 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.416877 -0.060347</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ugly tape on bollards, 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154392</link>
<description>All over Westminster and especially Horseferry Rd, utility companies have left hideous plastic tape on elegant street furniture like bollards. In many cases they have been there for years. I have contacted the environmental team and been ignored. It is utterly defacing and degrading the environment. How can we get ALL this stuff removed?&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8154392.0.jpeg?0a453250&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Horseferry Road, Millbank, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154392&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Signs and bollards</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154392</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:37:25 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.494933 -0.129324</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dumped vw polo, 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154390</link>
<description>La06lkf dumped untaxed no mot and no insurance volkswagen polo red. it is parked away from kerb making road very narrow. it is being damaged by vehicles trying to squeeze through i have been told it has been there for about 6 weeks.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Meaford Way, Anerley, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154390&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicle</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154390</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:36:27 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.416877 -0.060347</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abandoned black mini, 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154388</link>
<description>This car has been abandoned parked outside somebody’s garage for 6 months, we now have four cars that seem to be using it as free parking when everyone else had to buy a parking permit in a no parking area.and cars coming and going at all hours. The garages are on Simms Road Townsend House&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Strathnairn Street, Bermondsey, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154388&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154388</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:35:20 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.490909 -0.064787</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Furniture left outside property on Bellot Street, 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154374</link>
<description>Bits of furniture have been sitting outside this property on Bellot Street for a few days.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8154374.0.jpeg?3f50b958&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Bellot Street, East Greenwich, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154374&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154374</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:31:25 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.488537 0.005178</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Plywood on Bellot Street, 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154372</link>
<description>This piece of plywood have been left on Bellot Street for weeks. I assumed a collection had been arranged for pickup by the council but this does not seem to be the case.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8154372.0.jpeg?a5dad402&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Bellot Street, East Greenwich, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154372&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154372</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:29:31 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.487886 0.00515</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Household goods being dumped, 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154354</link>
<description>This is a constant problem with people pulling up and dumping their rubbish, and the local housing office don’t care.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8154354.0.jpeg?7286b4c7&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Strathnairn Street, Bermondsey, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154354&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Posting - General (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154354</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:20:55 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.490909 -0.064787</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Complete Painting of Double Line in front of CHM, 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154347</link>
<description>In early 2020 I reported a severe risk to Health &amp;amp; Safety for the residents and owners who live down the drive of Coachhouse Mews. It was captured by yourselves under #2168614 and you responded on 23/06/202 10:46 saying that the issue was being passed to traffic management team. The risk that I raised is that 50 Anerley Park which contains 8-9 flats and 1-3 Coachhouse Mews also are down this drive. When I raised the initial complaint action was taken and double lines were painted to stop people parking in front of the entryway to assist emergency services if they needed to reach us in an emergency that has been the case on multiple ocassitions since we moved here in 2008, however there was a vehicle parked where the traffic management team wanted to paint the line so as you can see in the photograph the double yellow line was not extended fully and people often don&amp;#39;t consider it as a double line as it is broken away from the main double line. As there is presently roadworks happening and no cars are permitted on the section of road I&amp;#39;m speaking of can a proper a full double yellow line be painted. I hope that makes sense and is clear. We have had to get fire trucks and ambulances down the small drive and it is often very difficult for them to make the turn in order to get down the drive if cars are parked on the double line.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8154347.0.jpeg?2badfcf8&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Anerley Park, Crystal Palace, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154347&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Road Marking</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154347</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:19:05 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.415487 -0.066696</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lampost has been hit by vehicle and the lamp has been knocked off. Lamppost is leaning over and the road is completely dark., 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154336</link>
<description>About three weeks ago the Lamppost was hit by a vehicle and is now leaning over. The lamp itself was knocked off and sat on the ground for a week, but has now disappeared.The lamppost is unsafe and the road is completely dark at night and is putting residents at risk.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 10, Chartwell Way, Anerley, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154336&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Lamp Column Damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154336</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:16:25 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.411355 -0.063678</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree branches are hanging too low, 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154312</link>
<description>All the other trees on the street have been cut back except this one. Branches have fallen off in the wind.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8154312.0.jpeg?cf7cbd65&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Villiers Road, Penge, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154312&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree Requires Pruning</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154312</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:07:38 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.405561 -0.049172</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Would it be possible for Wardens to patrol Fernhead Road and Shirland Road?, 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154303</link>
<description>Would it be possible for Wardens to patrol Fernhead Road and Shirland Road? Because these roads are rife with dog fouling. Despite you putting up signs encouraging dog owners to clean up after their dogs, many of these signs have been pulled down to pavement level! And they are ignored. Other streets that have these signs, they have not been pulled down! The culprits must live in one of these streets! I have actually had dog fouling thrown at the wall where I live and have had dog fouling put inside my dustbins! Thank you in anticipation.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 97, Fernhead Road, Kensal Town, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154303&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Dog fouling</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154303</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:02:13 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.529332 -0.201485</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Would it be possible for Wardens to patrol Fernhead Road and Shirland Road?, 11th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154302</link>
<description>Would it be possible for Wardens to patrol Fernhead Road and Shirland Road? Because these roads are rife with dog fouling. Despite you putting up signs encouraging dog owners to clean up after their dogs, many of these signs have been pulled down to pavement level! And they are ignored. Other streets that have these signs, they have not been pulled down! The culprits must live in one of these streets! I have actually had dog fouling thrown at the wall where I live and have had dog fouling put inside my dustbins! Thank you in anticipation.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 97, Fernhead Road, Kensal Town, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154302&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Dog fouling</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8154302</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:02:13 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.529332 -0.201485</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>