<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Rubbish dumped behind black unit outside 101, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283978</link>
<description>Up to 3 bags left by Road, foxes have ripped open and nappies and food waste left over floor&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8283978.0.jpeg?f3d8f795&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Honiton Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283978&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly-tip Small - Less than one bag</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283978</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 08:07:27 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.535682 -0.202639</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Outside 1 by tree, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283974</link>
<description>Wooden shelf unit, and pop-up tent left by tree&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8283974.0.jpeg?b9730790&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Honiton Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283974&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly-tip Small - Less than one bag</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283974</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 08:05:10 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.535682 -0.202639</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abandoned vehicle. Been sprayed and number plates remoced, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283966</link>
<description>This vehicle has been resprayed and had the number plates removed front and rear. It has no MOT and is an eyesore on our street. It leaks oil and is neglected and in ruin. Please have it removed&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8283966.0.jpeg?616eaad7&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Kenilworth Road, Poverest, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283966&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicle</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283966</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 07:59:06 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.385343 0.075288</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ash dieback, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283957</link>
<description>Tree is dying and likely to fall if not cut back/down as with previous trees causing damage and possible harm to wildlife and humans&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8283957.0.jpeg?63472a37&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): FP127, Coldblow, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283957&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>TPO enquiry</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283957</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 07:52:26 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.440107 0.160831</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Unacceptable Lake view, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283953</link>
<description>I have lived on Gadwall way for over 7 years where residence and children enjoy the view of the lake, people sit on the bench right in front of lake and see docks, birds and fish swim in front of the beautiful conservatory.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;A while ago the residence were lied to that beautiful flowers will be planted in the water front to make the water cleaner, and that in the summer time it would beautify the view of the lake and also provide the best environment.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Ever since the lake was restructured all we see in front of our house as residence is grown wheats and smell of a canal with dead fish in the lake which was contrary to what we were told when the front of the lake on Gadwall way was going to be reconstructed.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;It appears the purpose of changing the look of the view of the lake from what it used to be must have been because the council or those responsible for the idea must have done so for the benefit of people coming from far for fishing games at the other side of the lake adjacent to the Gallions park, and it appears there was no consideration given to the health, safety and the environment of us living in front of the lake from the other side of Gadwall way (SE28 0DB).&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Since the lake side was reconstructed, the residence of Gadwall way hardly go outside of the house to play or sit idown by the conservatory front of the lake as people usually do with their family and kids before, and the lake smells so badly with the sights of dead fish which made it horrible and parent can no longer take the kids to play in front of the house anymore.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Whoever came up with this idea had cut off all the residence of Gadwall way from enjoying the beautiful view of the lake and the environment and they had intentionally built a canal right infront of the residence. I believe they must have done this without given any consideration to the health and wellbeing.of those of us living right in front of the lake.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I think something urgently needs to be done about it because it makes some of us living in the neighbourhood very sick anytime we walk close to the lake and see dead fish in the lake.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;It is an horrible view especially for children walking pass the front of the lake to school. It is very wrong and unfair for the local authority to allow this to happen as we were sent a letter telling us the refurbishment is to make the environment beautiful and safe.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Even in the nights now the residence in Gadwall way cannot go close or sit in front of the lake because of fear for their own life. People we see coming to sit in front of the lake in the night are group of men from outside the area and some of them covering their faces at night and you can hardly see them from inside the house because the wheat had grown so much and had completely covered the view of the lake.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I fear one day something very tragic will happen if nothing is done to prevent it now.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8283953.0.jpeg?a7af005a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Fishermans Walk, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283953&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Parks/landscapes</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283953</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 07:48:33 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.497309 0.085882</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lots of shopping trolleys and household waste dumped on tge grass in the corner and opposite, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283944</link>
<description>This has been here for months and the collection is getting bigger, something needs to be done, cctv maybe? It is usually cleared and within a couple of months it slowly starts building up again. These people are lazy and have no pride in the area they live in.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8283944.0.jpeg?db8d0fd2&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Newmarsh Road, Thamesmead, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283944&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283944</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 07:36:21 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.502861 0.098317</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>3 Lime bikes left on electric vehicles charging space, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283938</link>
<description>Three Lime bikes have been left on the space reserved for electric vehicles by the charging point outside 83 Leander Road SW2.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Electric vehicles are unable to park and charge their batteries as a result.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8283938.0.jpeg?fd7bc41f&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Leander Road, Brixton, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283938&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned Lime bike or scooter</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283938</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 07:31:17 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.452259 -0.115478</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abandoned vehicle, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283928</link>
<description>Car left on road for 4 weeks. abandoned on road&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8283928.0.jpeg?a5d3aa49&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Congleton Grove, Plumstead, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283928&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283928</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 07:17:33 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.484802 0.074908</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Small-appliances recycling bank full or broken, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283906</link>
<description>Small-appliances recycling bank near Morrisons does not open.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Jenner Close, Longlands, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283906&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street cleaning and litter</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283906</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 06:27:43 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.424917 0.101673</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street cleaning, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283885</link>
<description>Ceres Road again is absolutely filthy. The road has not been cleaned thoroughly for weeks now. A joining Kashgar Road is also the same. Fallen leaves clog up the kerbside, previous grey leaf collection bags still on roadside uncollected on Ceres Road&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Fly tipping mess scattered bottom Ceres Road adjoining Kashgar road.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8283885.0.jpeg?eecbce71&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Ceres Road, Plumstead, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283885&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283885</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 03:17:37 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.487431 0.095456</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large grafitti tag on galvanised steel shutters of the Dry Cleaner&#39;s at 226, Venner Rd, Penge on the corner with Newlands Park., 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283868</link>
<description>Large grafitti tag on galvanised steel shutters of the Dry Cleaner&amp;#39;s at 226, Venner Rd, Penge on the corner with Newlands Park.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8283868.0.jpeg?b736e7ab&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Newlands Park, Penge, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283868&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283868</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 01:35:09 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.419464 -0.053601</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fridge, wardrobe, pallets, garbage bags, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283866</link>
<description>This fly tipping has been here for 5 months. I reported 2 months ago and nothing ha been made, the problem just increase (wooden pallets and garbage bags are there noe). I saw foxes there in the evening, it&amp;#39;s becoming their home soon. I&amp;#39;m desperate, struggling to understand who to report to solve it. My next step will be to take it to the local newspaper, it s already become public health issue.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Quebec Way, Rotherhithe, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283866&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping - General (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283866</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 01:30:43 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.49843 -0.041631</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Gazebo frame dumped, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283865</link>
<description>14 Paston Close had a gazebo up. Now their gazebo is gone + the frame of a gazebo has been dumped on the green next to their house.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This was dumped at some point on Saturday 11 October, as it was not there on Saturday morning&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Paston Close, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283865&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283865</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 01:29:05 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.558411 -0.043331</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>11/10/25 - Near 10 Shortlands Rd, Shortlands, the Width Limit rectangular blue warning sign is rotated about 80 degrees away from approaching traffic., 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283864</link>
<description>11/10/25 - Near 10 Shortlands Rd, Shortlands, the Width Limit rectangular blue warning sign is rotated about 80 degrees away from approaching traffic.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Please find a permanent solution as this has been reported about 5 times in 3 years eg put a pair of bolts through the pole and sign.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;My apologies for mixing up this width limit sign with the Low Bridge sign nearby. The Low Bridge sign has been straightened up. The Width Limit sign repair still needs doing.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8283864.0.jpeg?4b936e25&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Shortlands Road, Shortlands, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283864&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Sign Missing/Damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283864</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 01:27:10 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.404584 0.00055</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Outside 116 Fortune Green Rd - Badly damaged EV street charging point, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283863</link>
<description>Following a RTC, the vehicle has badly damaged a EV street charging point. Met. Police have isolated power switch to EV charging. LFB have placed a safety cordon tape around the hazard area. Duty of care left with Met. Police. Recorded by LFB.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Fortune Green Road, West Hampstead, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283863&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Utility Boxes and Cabinets</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283863</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 01:29:42 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.555487 -0.19651</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>In Newlands Park, Penge, approaching the junction with Lennard Rd, on the red triangular &#39;left hand bend advance warning&#39; sign, the sign light is out., 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283860</link>
<description>In Newlands Park, Penge, approaching the junction with Lennard Rd, on the red triangular &amp;#39;left hand bend advance warning&amp;#39; sign, the sign light is out. Seen after dusk on 11/10/25.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Newlands Park, Penge, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283860&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Sign Light Not Working</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283860</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 01:15:37 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.420075 -0.053007</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Kenilworth Road, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283852</link>
<description>It’s getting worse and worse and worse - it’s appalling&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8283852.0.jpeg?116a71a7&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Willesden Lane, Kilburn, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283852&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly-tip Large - More than a van load (Estates)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283852</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 00:35:36 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.540865 -0.200762</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Parking sign damaged, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283849</link>
<description>Outside 177 wardour st&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8283849.0.jpeg?81aefbec&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 177, Wardour Street, Camden Town, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283849&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Signs and bollards</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283849</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 00:18:22 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.515005 -0.135388</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flytips / domestic waste for collection, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283845</link>
<description>Please collect fly-tips / domestic waste from Charles Grinling Walk&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8283845.0.jpeg?c5f5049f&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Charles Grinling Walk, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283845&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283845</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 00:09:41 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.490137 0.061654</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Road surface, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283843</link>
<description>Park mead road is dangerously uneven and is cracking. Seems as though road is subsiding in parts and some parts are dangerously uneven and dips dangerous when driving. Not sure if this is causing damage to peoples homes on the street.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Park Mead, Blendon, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283843&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Damaged road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8283843</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 00:02:14 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.450801 0.110185</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>