<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Inappropriate images on the display in the windows on the gallery, 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999710</link>
<description>Miłość gallery Is currently has highly provocative art exhibition and its exposed to anyone passing by. Not against the art but male genitalia that is two meters in size should be closed from passers by that include minors. Primary school is opposite&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7999710.0.jpeg?77b0e088&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Downham Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999710&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999710</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:08:40 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.538937 -0.07802</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Overgrown bushes, 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999681</link>
<description>Bushes are all over grown on to the walking paths on both sides. They need to be trimmed back.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 42, Crescent Road, Plumstead, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999681&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Parks/landscapes</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999681</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:00:34 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.487777 0.068732</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dog Fouling, 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999668</link>
<description>There is a huge volume of dog fouling in Bromley around Haywwod Road. On almost every street I walk on around this area (Jaffray road, Southland Road, Homesdale Road, Havelock Road) I will come across dog faeces. What can be done to enforce responsible dog ownership?! It is really disgusting!&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Haywood Road, Widmore, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999668&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Dog Fouling</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999668</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:56:30 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.396542 0.035976</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Car has not moved for 4 weeks, 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999652</link>
<description>Car has a flat tyre and looks abandoned as it has not moved for sometime. Its taking up parking spaces that homeowners cannot use in Greenway&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7999652.0.jpeg?0345e53b&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 13, Greenway, Elmstead, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999652&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicle</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999652</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:52:08 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.4232 0.061858</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree falling fruit and leaves hazardous., 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999644</link>
<description>2 cherry trees outside no 41 and 45 Haywood Road. Both trees require pruning (despite the 1 outside 41 being pruned a fee weeks ago after logging request as too close to property). The fruit falling from leaves are dangerous: It makes the footpath slippy and I cannot enter my house without fallen cherry fruit being brought inside on shoes. It attracts huge volume wasps and flies which makes entering and exiting my property very hazardous. I have 2 small children and a new baby - the wasps are dangerous to have right outside our house. Residents are avoiding parking under the trees as the cars are destroyed with cherry fruit and bird faeces. This is hazardous again as the car attracts wasps(v difficult getting children in and out of car) and is harmful to the cars requiring more cost in more frequent car washing required. It is a health and safety issue with my children and not being able to enter or exit the house with the excessive mess on the path and the wasps and flies it attracts. It means I cannot park outside of my house either. These trees have never been maintained properly by the council, perhaps path cleaning happens once per year but given that cherry trees shed their blossom then fruit then leaves , this is not near enough. I would like to request that the trees are removed. It is an extremely poor choice of tree for a residential street. There is a high risk of harm to my children (or anyone but particularly children) due to the slippy footpath and the constant amount of wasps and flies. The limited street parking is even more restricted now. It is a yearly issue and this year it is particularly bad with the trees not being pruned properly and the amount of wasps. I would like the trees removed.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7999644.0.jpeg?268051fd&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Haywood Road, Widmore, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999644&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree Requires Pruning</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999644</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:51:07 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.396359 0.036103</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dumped bed posts, 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999640</link>
<description>Dumped bed posts and slates from 45 Rancliffe Gardens, been dumped in walk way from Rancliffe to kingsholm. Remaining posts still in the front garden of 45 Rancliffe gardens, will soon be dumped too&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7999640.0.jpeg?fe0544d3&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Rancliffe Gardens, Well Hall, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999640&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999640</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:52:01 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.459402 0.044565</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pieces of Glass Ignored by Street Cleaner for DAYS, 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999637</link>
<description>A bottle or something made of glass smashed and left shards of glass around the chicane. It&amp;#39;s been there all week. Dog walkers, kids, walking through a pile of glass that over time has just spread through footfall.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7999637.0.jpeg?2d2f69cb&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Sanford Walk, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999637&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999637</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:55:51 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.562486 -0.071524</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>I was walking home and a dog jumped to bite me, 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999630</link>
<description>I was walking on the street from the shop and a dog, he seemed to be a wolf type, jumped at me and bite me I struggled around 1 minute or so to pull my t shirt of he&amp;#39;s mouth and after I was able to do it he was still trying to jump at me and bite me&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7999630.0.jpeg?cf6171c0&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Picardy Street, Lower Belvedere, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999630&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Footway / carriageway</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999630</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:48:39 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.49144 0.148815</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street and pavement cleaning, 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999619</link>
<description>W used to have regular pavement and street cleaning along Orchard Road and lower sundridge Park road, it isn&amp;#39;t happening. Mini cabs park up in Sundridge park avenue close to Copley dene and just throw wrappers and dosguarded food out of cats, there are broken bottles and disguarded gas cannisters as well as lots of twigs, leaves and vegitation. t almost like the middle of autum rather than summer, it smells, please clean it up&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Sundridge Avenue, Widmore, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999619&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Litter and Detritus</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999619</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:45:35 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.407537 0.034576</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>No… sofa is still there., 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999615</link>
<description>Already reported this but got a response back saying it was no longer there, I believe you guys got the wrong location because it is still there.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7999615.0.jpeg?395ff717&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 87, Foots Cray Lane, Albany Park, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999615&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999615</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:44:10 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.435745 0.119802</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Weeds on pavement and in kerb need ckearing as the street looks uncared for, 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999604</link>
<description>These weeds are now getting out of hand can something be done please&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Avondale Road, Finchley, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999604&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999604</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:40:09 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.599863 -0.179195</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Trees that are hanging too low and causing obstructions, 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999603</link>
<description>There are several trees on the lower part of Sundridge Park avenue that are hanging low ( below head height) they need to be cut back these are public trees. Anyone with any kind of visual disability would walk into them. Please can they be dealy with&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Sundridge Avenue, Widmore, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999603&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree Requires Pruning</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999603</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:39:39 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.407537 0.034576</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bikes locked to the lanpost for year&#39;s, 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999601</link>
<description>Hi, we have reported this time and time again. Hackney council even put a note when it will be removed in 2023 but it&amp;#39;s still there. Please help&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7999601.0.jpeg?4a5d5f7e&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Shrubland Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999601&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned private cycle</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999601</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:40:00 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.538799 -0.067421</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Turn right filter light is not working, 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999587</link>
<description>The filter light is not working so only one car can get through turning right&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Village Way, Eden Park, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999587&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>General Fault</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999587</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:38:41 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.396669 -0.028757</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The tree overfrowth is still blocking the vision of the crossing, 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999583</link>
<description>This issue is not resolevd it has been reported 3 times and closed down twice. This happens everyyear the tree surgeons who came out last year said it should be dealt with every 3 months during the growth season, this year we have tried to get you out and reported it as H&amp;amp;S which is obvious, but nothing happens. can you get it dealy with please&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Orchard Road, Widmore, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999583&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree Requires Pruning</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999583</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:35:59 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.409778 0.034063</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Three or four lime bikes thrown into the pocket park alongside Lower Sydenham station., 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999575</link>
<description>Three or four lime bikes have been thrown into the pocket alongside Lower Sydenham station. Please can they be removed from the bushes?&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Kangley Bridge Road, Perry Vale, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999575&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned Lime bike or scooter</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999575</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:34:49 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.425709 -0.033433</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Missed rubbish collection at the The Vicarage, Brackley Road BR3 1RB, 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999572</link>
<description>Missed non recyclable rubbish collection.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 20, Brackley Road, New Beckenham, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999572&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Litter and Detritus</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999572</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:34:26 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.416491 -0.031775</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lighting on footbridge and to/ from, 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999571</link>
<description>Is anything going to be done to improve lighting on and near the public footbridge whilst Network Rail replace the footbridge at the station?&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Most of this work will take place during winter and commuters will be forced to use this route to and from the station&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Queensway, Petts Wood, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999571&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Light Not Working</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999571</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:33:54 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.389929 0.072714</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Overhanging tree foilage at junction of Elm Way/Poplar Grove, 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999563</link>
<description>An overgrown tree at junction of Elm Way (house no 1) and poplar grove is a danger and hazard for pedestrians. Branches and foliage are very overgrown and hangs low, hitting heads, and the fruit is dropping to then ground and causing slips, trips and falls to disabled pedestrians. Also obstructs the road name sign.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 73, Poplar Grove, Colney Hatch, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999563&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Overhanging Foliage</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999563</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:34:08 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.608514 -0.149365</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flytipping in pathway to open space, 8th August</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999561</link>
<description>Large items, including a mattress, dumped in overgrown pathway, adjacent to 56 Magpie Hall Lane, leading to open space&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Green Way, Southborough, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999561&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytip in Park</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7999561</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:31:23 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.386526 0.04723</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>