<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Strong winds breaking dead and living branches off tree, 13th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286700</link>
<description>Have seen trees being pruned around the borough but have never seen any attention given to the very mature oak trees at the bottom of Mead Way. When there are strong winds there are always dead branches broken off and landing on grass and pavement and during storm Amy it was living branches. Concerned about adults and children getting hit by these branches as they fall. Particularly concerned about the oaks on the even side.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8286700.0.jpeg?12df5d8d&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 4, Mead Way, Hayes, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286700&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree Requires Pruning</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286700</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 00:02:53 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.388277 0.0169</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abandoned dumped vehicle van blocking garden maintenance gates., 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286694</link>
<description>Abandon dump vehicle van for over a year.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8286694.0.jpeg?27c3e04b&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Daintry Way, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286694&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286694</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:45:16 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.546075 -0.029369</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abandoned scaffolding on building next to “fuckoffee” cafe on Bermondsey street, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286692</link>
<description>Abandoned scaffolding seems to have been in place for years with no work being carried out. This has resulted in litter, weeds and debris being dumped within it and causing a mess. Please tell building management to remove the scaffolding and tidy up the area.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8286692.0.jpeg?52b4ed1b&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 153, Tower Bridge Road, Old Kent Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286692&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/footpaths</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286692</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:39:38 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.498775 -0.079036</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Antisocial behaviour being caused by line bikes. Weekends are the worst over 28 line bikes dumped all over the place even leaning on residents, visitors vehicles causing damaged to their cars because bikes of being left in dangerous, inconsiderate way. What is the mayor of Hackney doing about this nuisance and anti-social behavior with these line bikes everywhere. I live in the area and I have motability issues, disabled and often have to try move lime bikes off my car or out the way. Lime bikes laying in public roads causing a hazard to other road users., 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286691</link>
<description>Antisocial behaviour line bikes. Why is the mayor and authority not addressing these issues is it because mayor and authority are getting a big chunk of money from the investment company line bike and leasing bays two company.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8286691.0.jpeg?b21a5830&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Semley Gate, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286691&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286691</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:38:48 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.546844 -0.028622</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Kingsley Rd - junction with Priory Pk Rd, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286688</link>
<description>Dumped cabinet, rugs and general rubbish. Has been here for several days now&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8286688.0.jpeg?a844ac77&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Priory Park Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286688&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly-tip Medium - Up to medium size van load</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286688</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:35:01 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.539605 -0.201155</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hazelmere Rd - pedestrianised area between Glengall Rd and Priory Park Rd, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286687</link>
<description>Dumped TV, cushions, clothes and general junk. Was strewn across this area this morning and then tidied into a heap by the street-sweeper. Much of this waste appears linked to the vagrancy issue that has arisen at this site in recent weeks&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8286687.0.jpeg?724cfaa9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Priory Park Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286687&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly-tip Medium - Up to medium size van load</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286687</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:32:38 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.539567 -0.20026</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Kenilworth Rd - outside Coronation Court (near junction with Willesden Lane), 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286680</link>
<description>Enormous flytip. Fridge, cabinets, clothes, DIY waste and general rubbish. Pavement completely obstructed. Reported multiple times over the last week by myself and others. All equally appalled that Brent Council have not cleared this sooner, which has encouraged further dumping at this side. Shame on those who have done this and shame on Brent Council for not having dealt with this sooner&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8286680.0.jpeg?b52b0bb5&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Kenilworth Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286680&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly-tip Large - More than a van load</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286680</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:29:17 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.540755 -0.200793</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rubbish dumped, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286678</link>
<description>This is a repeated dumping site&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8286678.0.jpeg?2d1fe636&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Dunsmure Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286678&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286678</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:26:55 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.570406 -0.07431</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Road sign hidden on trees by the fence of the Bull Pub, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286668</link>
<description>The road sign to state that Sandy Lane has a width&amp;#39;s restriction is hidden in the bushes / tree on the side fence of the Bull Pub and needs replacing to the entrance of Sandy Lane because unless your in the pub gardens you can’t see it.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8286668.0.jpeg?e4835ded&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Main Road, St Paul&#39;s Cray, Orpington, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286668&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Sign Missing/Damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286668</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:17:36 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.403324 0.118663</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Unconfined active construction site with open trenches and construction materials scattered., 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286666</link>
<description>The whole length of Beak St was not properly fenced, protected or signed. Pedestrians clambering over open trenches. Construction materials scattered. Accident waiting to happen. Called the Compass Infrastructure emergency phone and got the auto operator with options. Pressed 5 to report an emergency. Engaged. All afternoon. Tried all the other options. All continuously engaged. Given the proximity to one of the UK&amp;#39;s premium tourist assets it was a disgraceful display of poor construction and a health and safety hazard. I am in construction and I have never seen such a bad live site in the UK. UKPN and Compass need to be called out about this urgently.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8286666.0.jpeg?05c7d7de&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 35, Beak Street, City of Westminster&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286666&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Safety fences and barriers</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286666</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:16:07 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.512283 -0.137825</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Continuous Parking Issue!, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286656</link>
<description>There is a continuous and problematic parking issue on Bourneside Gardens and a safety concern on Primrose Close. There are not enough parking spaces for residents on Bourneside Gardens. Residents and visitors are struggling to park, and vehicles are now parking on grass verges and tight spaces between houses, especially at turning points. This blocks access for others trying to enter or leave their homes and prevents people from turning around. A large silver van is parked long-term and rarely moves. Another work van belonging to a resident at 10 Bourneside Gardens (We believe the tenant is subletting) is parked daily and purposely takes up two spaces adding to the issue. These vehicles are taking up much-needed space. Parking permits were previously considered but shelved – I strongly request that permits are reconsidered to prioritise residents.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;On Primrose Close, there is a white Ford Transit Van (Reg: RO65 CDZ) that has been parked for around six months. A man is living in it. The van has no MOT or tax and he is using gas canisters inside, creating a serious safety risk. It is also impacting the appearance of the area. Please investigate and take appropriate action on both matters. Thank you.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8286656.0.jpeg?074c7425&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Bourneside Gardens, Southend, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286656&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Car Parking</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286656</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:08:34 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.424455 -0.011148</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Weeds : Brambles by river ornamental gardens need cutting back, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286655</link>
<description>The weeds and brambles by the beech trees and all around the river / ornimental gardens area needs cutting back they are taking over the lovely plants wrapping around the plants and trees . Friends of Brooks Way maintain these gardens every weekend in a small area but it’s to much for them to do it all it needs council gardeners to cut these back now&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8286655.0.jpeg?49058451&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Brook Way, St Paul&#39;s Cray, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286655&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Shrub Beds</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286655</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:08:48 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.402054 0.116629</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sofa and rubbish in the bushes, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286648</link>
<description>There is a sofa and rubbish in the bushes.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8286648.0.jpeg?3a27ca57&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Tormount Road, Plumstead, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286648&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286648</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:01:17 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.481541 0.088963</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Two large mattresses on the sidewalk, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286639</link>
<description>Two large mattresses are sitting on the sidewalk, that people are having to walk around.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8286639.0.jpeg?126e9afa&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Pendrell Street, Plumstead, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286639&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286639</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:58:54 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.478305 0.085704</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bushes / weeds to high by Garage Door Company, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286636</link>
<description>There’s bushes and weeds covering the black metal bollards facing the garage door company which need cutting down please they are far to high&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8286636.0.jpeg?1db72e74&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Brook Way, St Paul&#39;s Cray, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286636&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Shrub Beds</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286636</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:58:40 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.402144 0.114708</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Trees and bushes hanging over the railing by railway bridge, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286630</link>
<description>There are loads of bushes and trees hanging over the railing by the railway archeson Cray Avenue which need cutting back please&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8286630.0.jpeg?edc5ccb8&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Sevenoaks Way, Poverest, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286630&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree Requires Pruning</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286630</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:50:00 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.39497 0.11195</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Near International Journal of Excellence in Research, Bloomsbury Way, London WC1A 2SE, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286628</link>
<description>I am writing to make you aware and request urgent Repair of a seriously defective manhole cover located at the junction of Bloomsbury Way and Bury Place, WC1A, near our home.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Over recent weeks, the manhole cover has become loose. Each time a vehicle passes over it, it emits a loud clattering sound - so forceful that our house vibrates. The noise is especially bad in the evenings and overnight, when buses frequently pass (often every 5 minutes). It genuinely feels like a train rolling by. The disturbance is severe: it wakes us and our 15-year-old daughter nearly every night.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This is not just a nuisance - it is disrupting our sleep, affecting our health and wellbeing, and I believe it also presents a safety concern (a loose cover might worsen further under constant load).&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Bury Place, Bloomsbury, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286628&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Manhole in the road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286628</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:48:40 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.51783 -0.123756</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Leafs on the pavement by railway arche, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286622</link>
<description>There are loads of leaves and litter on the pavement from the damage wall up to Marks loading bay which needs sweeping up please&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8286622.0.jpeg?edc5ccb8&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Sevenoaks Way, Poverest, Orpington, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286622&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Leafing</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286622</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:49:36 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.395338 0.11208</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Noisy manhole two months!!, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286614</link>
<description>The manhole is loose and super NOISY for the last two months. I have called and reported it before. I made videos from the street when you can hear how loud it is and also from my apartment Which is exactly outside on the 5th floor and it’s still VERY LOUD every time a car drives through it you listen it twice from the front and back wheel!! Please make your arrangements and come fix it… Just outside the triangular island and on the pink building, Grays Inn Buildings , is a small rectangular manhole , there are two one of them is super noisy!&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Rosebery Avenue, Holborn, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286614&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Manhole in the road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286614</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:39:33 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.521932 -0.112462</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Complete blocking the road disturbing the traffic, 12th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286611</link>
<description>A hire bike parking is wrongly allocated at the residasial are at Ingester place,Soho that misused by the conesumers woth no obsirvation from the WCC and the service providers.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;We stuggling to driving and parking our car and even to collect our delivery.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8286611.0.jpeg?fade47d2&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Ingestre Place, City of Westminster&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286611&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned HumanForest bike</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8286611</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:34:53 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.512841 -0.135013</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>