<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Can pot hole here be filled in please?, 29th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779455</link>
<description>Can this be inspected please?&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7779455.0.jpeg?0a4d4bed&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): St. Blaise Avenue, Plaistow, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779455&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Road Defect</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779455</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 02:52:43 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.405573 0.020742</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Can road surface around 17 Harwood manhole cover be checked?, 29th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779454</link>
<description>Can the road surface be inspected and relaid if necessary&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Harwood Avenue, Plaistow, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779454&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Road Defect</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779454</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 02:48:24 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.405555 0.019961</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Formal Complaint and Request for Resolution Regarding Mobile Signal Disruption and Estate Impact on Quality of Life, 29th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779443</link>
<description>Dear Sir/Madam,&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I am writing to formally raise concerns regarding serious disruptions to my mobile and internet connectivity, and to request an immediate review and practical resolution from the Council.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Directly opposite from Aylesford Street, approximately 3 to 4 metres away, stands a recently developed eight-storey council estate across from 3 storey buildings from ground level. Since its completion, I have experienced a severe and persistent degradation in mobile phone signal and data access inside my home. I currently subscribe to a 3G, 4G, 5G service through Vodafone provider and have previously had reliable service everywhere I go, even on the underground tube. However, I now receive virtually no signal within my property, constantly registering zero bars, making it impossible to make phone calls or use internet services on my phone, laptop, or computer without leaving the house entirely and walking down the street. I work from home due to accessible needs as a professional full time and cannot do anything in terms of work or personal.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This is not only deeply inconvenient but has serious implications for both my professional and personal life. As someone who works from home, access to reliable mobile and internet services is essential. The current situation prevents me from performing basic work functions, including attending virtual meetings, making business calls, or accessing cloud-based tools. In some instances, I am forced to walk to the far end of the street, where the housing block ends, near Grosvenor Road, just to establish any kind of connection!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Furthermore, the implications for health and safety are deeply concerning. In the event of an emergency, I would be unable to call emergency services without physically exiting my home and travelling a considerable distance to find a signal. This is an unacceptable risk and a breach of reasonable living standards.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The structure of the estate appears to be directly interfering with signal strength, and I am also concerned that this obstruction could have long-term effects on property values and the viability of the home as a modern, functional dwelling-particularly in light of increasing national policies around working from home and digital access being a basic utility.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Given the seriousness of the matter, I respectfully request the Council to investigate the following:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;• Immediate assessment of the impact of the estate structure on telecommunications access for surrounding residents. • Provision of a practical resolution, such as installation of signal boosters, repeaters, or Wi-Fi infrastructure paid for by the Council or in partnership with telecommunications providers. • Clear communication of findings and proposed steps, including a timeline for resolution.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This issue is having a measurable and detrimental impact on my quality of life and ability to work as a full time professional. I trust the Council will recognise the severity of the situation and respond promptly with appropriate support and a proposed solution.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I would be grateful for written confirmation of receipt of this complaint and an update on the Council&amp;#39;s next steps as soon as possible as this is affecting everyday life.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Aylesford Street, Pimlico, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779443&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street works and obstructions</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779443</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 01:19:32 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.486403 -0.132489</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dumped Item, 29th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779436</link>
<description>Arnsberg Way at the junction with Mayplace Road West, Bexleyheath: Please remove the dumped item from the pavement as seen in the attached picture.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7779436.0.jpeg?78bac461&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Arnsberg Way, Barnehurst, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779436&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779436</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 01:09:06 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.457014 0.148373</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dumped Rubbish by your Street Cleaning Contractor - Countrystyle, 29th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779435</link>
<description>Third report: Cinema Public Car Park, 22 Broadway, Bexleyheath, DA6 7RB: Please could you ask your street cleaning contractor - Countrystyle to stop dumping their blue waste sacks outside of this car park - as seen in the attached pictures. Quite frankly, it looks a mess, it attracts foxes and other vermin, encourages fly-tipping and is not a temporary dumping ground. Please remove these items and ask the contractor to stop leaving their rubbish here.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7779435.0.jpeg?d7e4d29f&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Broadway, Barnehurst, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779435&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779435</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 01:06:21 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.455655 0.151649</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>2 street lights have been broken for months., 29th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779422</link>
<description>There is two street lights together that have been off for a while. I’ve attached photos of the lamp numbers. Could we get this sorted promptly as this road has been hit with many stolen vehicles. with half the street being pitch black it makes it very easy for thieves to target. ‘ 06V0119’ and ‘07V0119’&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7779422.0.jpeg?95117cdc&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 28, Bercta Road, New Eltham, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779422&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street lighting</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779422</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 00:23:29 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.4367 0.072581</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dead wildlife, 29th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779420</link>
<description>Dead Waterbird caused by fishing line bagged and place on steps. What3words: ///grows.slam.grace&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7779420.0.jpeg?a638eb83&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Binsey Walk, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779420&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Wildlife issue</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779420</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 00:20:14 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.499268 0.122951</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Parts of a dismantled shed and pladtic bits dumped Wheathill Rd corner Penge Rd, 28th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779384</link>
<description>Boards from a shed and plastic pipe and bits dumped on footpath.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7779384.0.jpeg?e75ac582&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Wheathill Road, Anerley, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779384&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytip</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779384</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 23:35:07 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.403924 -0.066484</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street light not working, 28th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779382</link>
<description>Street light not working&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): The Avenue, Beckenham, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779382&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Light Not Working</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779382</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 23:31:04 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.41136 -0.019788</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Trees overhanging, 28th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779376</link>
<description>The trees are overhanging the roads, the buses are constantly smashing off of them. I have a daughter who is awake most of the summer nights, as the windows have to be open but the awful noise of these trees catapulting off of the buses is keeping her awake. They are so overhung in both the road and on the pavement it’s is becoming impossible to walk without having to duck. It’s also dangerous as the branches are being snapped off from the gravity of the buses and pinging everywhere, it won’t be long before someone gets hurt. The tree outside of 24 Dartmouth Park Hill is bending so much that it is pulling out of the ground and lifrjnf the pavement, this has resulted in people falling and tripping over the lifted pavement Slabs.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Dartmouth Park Hill, Archway, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779376&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779376</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 23:22:09 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.558399 -0.139498</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street light, 28th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779351</link>
<description>Limited lighting on footpath as trees and leaves block&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7779351.0.jpeg?3def6a7e&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 16, Southborough Road, Bickley, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779351&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Private Tree overhanging highway</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779351</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 22:56:26 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.401002 0.044784</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rubbish bags dumped, 28th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779349</link>
<description>Bags dumped on pavement&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7779349.0.jpeg?1e45b775&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Dot Hill, Plumstead, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779349&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779349</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 22:55:18 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.474847 0.082987</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rubbish all up the street, 28th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779347</link>
<description>Rubbish and debris blown all up the street&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7779347.0.jpeg?e7cf6ba7&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Brickfield Cottages, Plumstead, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779347&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street Spillage</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779347</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 22:54:07 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.478381 0.099987</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fox carcass by water, 28th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779342</link>
<description>Rotting fox body in the stream off the boardwalk in towards the allotments at East Wickham Open Space&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Radial Path, East Wickham, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779342&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Dead animal</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779342</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 22:51:12 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.472789 0.101121</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dumped rubbish, 28th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779332</link>
<description>Rubbish dumped&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7779332.0.jpeg?8d25cb58&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Graham Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779332&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Littering</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779332</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 22:46:53 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.546113 -0.062584</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>2 inch deep pothole about 18 inches wide, 28th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779316</link>
<description>An increasing large pothole needs repairing.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Eden Way, Eden Park, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779316&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Road Defect</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779316</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 22:35:45 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.390191 -0.031159</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rubbish outside 2a Highshore road building, 28th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779313</link>
<description>Beer bottles and other rubbish outside the building&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 32, Rye Lane, Peckham, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779313&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping - Other (Unidentified) (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779313</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 22:31:57 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.471625 -0.070248</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fly tipping outside the police station, 28th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779312</link>
<description>Repeat of previous fly tipping on church street. Directly outside the police station. Includes mattress and rubbish. .&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7779312.0.jpeg?d482b822&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 22, Camberwell Church Street, Camberwell, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779312&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Posting - General (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779312</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 22:30:48 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.473968 -0.091049</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Been parked there past few days, no one coming near the vehicle., 28th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779303</link>
<description>The vehicle makes entry into our driveway difficult causing a jam sometimes when other vehicles try to drive past.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 76, Saxville Road, St Paul&#39;s Cray, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779303&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicle</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779303</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 22:28:27 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.399361 0.106942</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flytipped furniture, 28th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779290</link>
<description>Flytipped cot&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7779290.0.jpeg?5b759a54&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Glengall Road, Old Kent Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779290&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping - General (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7779290</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 23:33:54 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.482564 -0.072165</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>