<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Railing to be replaced, 3rd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246234</link>
<description>REF 18/044 - Damaged railing to be replaced or repaired after a vehicle collision&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8246234.0.jpeg?4d628772&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Welling Way, Falconwood, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246234&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Traffic bollard</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246234</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 03:55:29 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.464418 0.094731</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>These bis signs keep appearing on lamposts, 3rd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246226</link>
<description>These ugly big signs keep appearing on lampposts . From well hall road when you turn into westmout road, they are above the bollards on both sides and further near the mini roundabout. I have called the number and complained and man was dismissive&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8246226.0.jpeg?909fb2f3&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Broad Walk, Well Hall, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246226&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246226</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 02:55:36 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.468472 0.046986</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Foliage affecting traffic pole, 3rd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246221</link>
<description>Pole 4 is affected by foliage&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Outer Circle, Marylebone, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246221&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees and plants</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246221</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 02:21:20 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.528791 -0.163784</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Multiple lights not working, 3rd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246201</link>
<description>About a dozen lights are not working in Riverside Gardens. 2 October.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The light in the far corner by the jetty hasn&amp;#39;t worked in years. It&amp;#39;s very dark in that corner.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8246201.0.jpeg?f8ab3f16&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Erith High Street, Northumberland Heath, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246201&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Light in park or open space</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246201</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:55:51 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.482149 0.179917</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Litter and urine, 3rd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246190</link>
<description>Man pulled up outside our flat, emptied all the rubbish from all doors of his car onto the floor and then urinated on the floor and drove off. Plate GY67 KOX&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8246190.0.jpeg?60cd6b74&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Brownswood Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246190&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Littering</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246190</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:42:13 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.562833 -0.095841</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree obstructing traffic signal, 3rd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246187</link>
<description>Tree obstruct traffic signal - aspect Pole 7 - required trimming&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Seymour Place, Marylebone, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246187&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees and plants</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246187</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:30:59 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.519098 -0.163021</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Erroneous &#39;Phoenix Centre&#39; arrow sign on lamp column fronting 396, Croydon Rd, Beckenham pointing up Faversham Rd., 2nd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246155</link>
<description>Erroneous &amp;#39;Phoenix Centre&amp;#39; arrow sign on lamp column fronting 396, Croydon Rd, Beckenham pointing up Faversham Rd.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;An online search reveals only a children&amp;#39;s Phoenix Centre at 40, Masons Hill, Bromley (Google Streetview image as the third image).&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Brckenham Hospital was redeveloped as the Beckenham Beacon Medical Centre around the year 2000. Perhaps this sign relates to that?&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Please remove the sign if it is indeed, as it appears, utterly pointless, and relocate it to Masons Hill.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8246155.0.jpeg?3400a6cf&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 379-397, Croydon Road, Beckenham, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246155&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Sign Missing/Damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246155</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:51:15 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.406096 -0.033412</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dear local aerial manager and local authorities. Simon Priscilla, Denise Corbin, antisocial behaviour department, local councillors, local mayor of Hackney, the commissioner of the metropolitan police, could you please all put your brains together and come up with a solution to stop this anti-social behavior and criminal activity taking place on the Trowbridge estate which is on the rise. Drug users junkies shiting outside leaseholders garage door 13,12 white male around 21:00pm.local authority could you please address this issue of anti-social behaviour. Drug users junkies,crackheads loitering and waiting in between Osborne Road garages and brickworth way to pick up drugs on 15/03/25 at 21:00pm. Junkies trying to break into leaseholders rented garages. local junkie was nosing around near leaseholders garage doors trying to open door. Possibly looking for somewhere to sleep for the night. Local residents feel unsafe and insecure with junkies, drug users on the increase in the area on the Trowbridge estate. Residence of getting scared to come out of a night because there is a constant flow of all different drug users loitering. Also urinating and shiting. There are families that live on this estate this is terrible behavior for residents to witness even small children. Local authorities have a duty to protect members of the public and residents.These issues need addressing ASAP.Also there is a property at 25 Trowbridge Rd, London E9 5LD which is attracting this anti-social behavior and criminal activity local criminals using the property as a drug den.The mayor of Hackney, police commissioner, management Simon Priscilla,Denise Corbin, local councillors would not like it if this was happening outside their home address would they., 2nd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246138</link>
<description>What does Hackney Council actually do about antisocial behavior. Absolute nothing.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8246138.0.jpeg?1b3260e2&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Reading Lane, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246138&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246138</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:39:41 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.544677 -0.057812</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>A4 blue laminated market advertisement on Croydon Rd Rec park railings (unrelated to the park) fronting Croydon Rd, Beckenham between the Beckenham Beacon and the bus shelter., 2nd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246126</link>
<description>A4 blue laminated market advertisement on Croydon Rd Rec park railings (unrelated to the park) fronting Croydon Rd, Beckenham between the Beckenham Beacon and the bus shelter.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8246126.0.jpeg?83414daf&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 379-397, Croydon Road, Beckenham, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246126&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flyposting</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246126</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:31:03 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.404763 -0.03399</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bikes in road and resident&#39;s parking bay causing obstruction, 2nd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246124</link>
<description>Bikes in road and resident&amp;#39;s parking bay causing obstruction&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8246124.0.jpeg?a651e877&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Meadowbank, Chalk Farm, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246124&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned Lime bike or scooter</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246124</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:30:46 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.5405 -0.159688</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>To whom it concerns. Could you please address these issues previously happened but not addressed antisocial behaviour criminal activity.A Residence of the Trowbridge estate Graham Hawkins has been breaking into Osborne road void garages since 2016 &amp; 2023 rent free. Graham Hawkins breaking into void garages with a battery pack handle grinder.Residence, Leaseholders were disturbed by what Graham Hawkins was doing Which this behaviour should not be tolerated by hackney council &amp; Randall Kerry garage team hand posted a warning letter to the address of Graham Hawkins 10 Dainty way E9 5JJ.Resident from 21 Mallard close E9 5JL Eugene Egan has been involved with the trespassing,assisting,helping Graham Hawkins move his stuff out of garage.when mr Graham Hawkins was breaking into the garage Eugene Egan was also aware of what Graham Hawkins was doing.Breaking and entering trespassing. Also on the night when Graham Hawkins was breaking into the garage 16,19,with a battery pack handle grinder. Eugene Egan approach mr Graham Hawkins and reply to Graham Hawkins the subcontractor purdys cut the lock and done that to you Graham and took your stuff out of garage 19 and put it into garage 16 and changed lock.Graham Hawkins was cutting the padlock off garage 16 with a battery handle grinder as Eugene Egan was there with Graham Hawkins On 01/08/23 at 20:00pm.Eugene Egan knows this information because he has a CCTV overlooking all of the leaseholders garages monitoring their daily routines and feeding information to Graham Hawkins. criminal behaviour was taken place. Eugene Egan has been tipping resident Graham Hawkins off about the void garages because it&#39;s a coincident how chair member knows which garages are empty,void and which ones are leased out seen as Eugene Egan works with the council official people he would know that sort of information.Hackney council put notice up on garage door to vacate garage 19,16 trespassing Graham Hawkins remove his stuff out of garage 16 and placed it into two garages which Eugene Egan has access and keys owns, leases from Hackney council which was 23 &amp; 24 Osborne road garages subletting criminal activity, possibly garage tenancy fraud in different names.Eugene Egan help,assisting,perpetrator,trespasser resident Graham Hawkins remove his stuff into Eugene egan garages at 23 &amp; 24 because the resident got caught and found out by the local hackney council garage team.Eugene Egan and Graham Hawkins should not be in that garage without the hackney councils authorization,criminal activity, trespassing.Shows the connections with one another how Trowbridge resident association chair member looks out for Graham Hawkins.criminal behaviour.Tra corruption. This was reported to the metropolitan police. Residence and other Leaseholders pay their rent so why should this one or two residents get away with breaking into garages rent free for a number of years this is discrimination and antisocial behavior. If somebody could please address this behavior and investigate., 2nd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246123</link>
<description>Income services manager Ian Clark please could you look into this a legal activity you target people for rent areas with garage but you do not target residence break in to void garages five years rent free. Hackney Council discriminate law dividing citizen&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8246123.0.jpeg?c54033f5&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Reading Lane, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246123&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246123</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:30:30 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.545082 -0.057999</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Graffiti, 2nd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246122</link>
<description>Graffiti on lamppost 146F3 on &amp;#39;cow path&amp;#39;&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8246122.0.jpeg?a57a8bd8&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Cow Path, Elmstead, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246122&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246122</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:30:24 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.422676 0.051466</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Outside Pizza Express and the trees to the north, 2nd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246120</link>
<description>I am concerned at the fungal growth of the magnificent beech trees on this side of Haverstock Hill. Is it meripilus and if so are these trees compromised, unsafe and likely to need felling?&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Haverstock Hill, Belsize Park, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246120&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Dead/Diseased tree</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246120</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:29:13 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.550545 -0.164811</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fly tipping, 2nd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246117</link>
<description>More rubbish has now been dumped on this footpath&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8246117.0.jpeg?c5921432&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Elmers End Road, Anerley, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246117&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytip</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246117</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:25:01 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.403833 -0.055174</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Gang tag graffiti on the glass and pavement by the bus shelter, 2nd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246115</link>
<description>There are a number of different gang tags sprayed as graffiti on the glass of the bus shelter and on the pavement nearby - please can all be removed as a matter of priority before more appear as it’s intimidating using this bus shelter and unpleasant. Thank you.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8246115.0.jpeg?2b7cfc20&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Green Lanes, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246115&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti / Flyposting on stop or shelter (non-offensive)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246115</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:24:47 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.572004 -0.096686</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Overflowing bin and litter, 2nd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246113</link>
<description>Litter needs cleaning&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8246113.0.jpeg?42e8d0ed&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Mount Pleasant Lane, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246113&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Overflowing Public Litter Bin</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246113</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:24:11 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.563735 -0.058208</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Multiple trees/bushes blocking pavement, 2nd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246112</link>
<description>As per report ref: 8101487 which I raised early September which was then marked as fixed even though the problem had not been resolved.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Multiple trees/bushes are blocking the pavement between 7a Victoria Road and the junction with Park Crescent. The overgrowth has been a regular occurence for years, they do not get pruned regularly enough. The blockage forces pedestrians to walk on the grass verge, which has caused the verge to turn to mud due to the footfall.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Victoria Road, Northumberland Heath, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246112&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246112</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:19:57 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.478393 0.176023</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Loose /detached pole on frame, 2nd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246109</link>
<description>The climbing frame in Whitehall has a displaced pole - it needs fixing as soon as possible. The frame came from Fawns and should be still under guarantees.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8246109.0.jpeg?2be2840e&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Blenheim Road, Southborough, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246109&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Playground Repairs</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246109</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:15:10 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.394921 0.04093</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Free males climbing on top of garage roof jumping up and down causing damage to roof tops., 2nd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246104</link>
<description>Hackney Council need to open some communities halls for young people to do things instead a climbing on garage roofs.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8246104.0.jpeg?d0bb4458&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Beanacre Close, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246104&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246104</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:13:13 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.545472 -0.028889</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>On the public footway near 436 Upper Elmers End Rd are once more displayed two 2.5m high weighted flag advertisements for Aro Barber&#39;s at that address., 2nd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246051</link>
<description>On the public footway near 436 Upper Elmers End Rd are once more displayed two 2.5m high weighted flag advertisements for Aro Barber&amp;#39;s at that address. This is an abuse ongoing for months that has resumed.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8246051.0.jpeg?2b4018aa&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 448-450, Upper Elmers End Road, Eden Park, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246051&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Obstruction to Highway</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8246051</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:04:36 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.389616 -0.026622</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>