<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Sewage from blocked drain, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235520</link>
<description>Smell of the gulley on the street is digusting. Causing issues with our toilets that is a precursor to a back up. Warned by plumber and have young child in the house - concerned for health.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 48, Blanmerle Road, New Eltham, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235520&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Blocked Roadside Gully</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235520</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 20:14:53 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.438885 0.068009</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Broken glass all over pavement, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235514</link>
<description>Lots of broken glass all over payment needs clearing&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Albemarle Road, Shortlands, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235514&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavement Defect</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235514</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 20:11:27 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.409091 -0.014294</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fly tipping. Rubbish and mattress, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235511</link>
<description>Fly tipped rubbish blocking narrow pavement&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235511.0.jpeg?9cc6e8a6&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 21, Sandy Hill Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235511&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235511</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 20:10:43 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.486397 0.067698</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Loud loose manhole cover, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235509</link>
<description>The manhole cover in front of 2 Thwaites cottage, Cray Road has been loose since the road resurfacing making loud noise each time vehicle drives over. This has caused significant disturbance to residence and road users. Can this be repaired before it becomes serious safety hazard please? Thanks&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235509.0.jpeg?4788a80e&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 97, Cray Road, North Cray, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235509&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Manhole covers</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235509</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 20:10:56 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.414632 0.113858</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Road view obstruction, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235508</link>
<description>Hiya slightly concerned about the flags on Erith horse roundabout obstructing oncoming traffic view it&amp;#39;s a busy roundabout and worried this may cause an accident one is the middle is fine however they have been placed around the perimeter at eyeline level&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Crabtree Manorway North, Lower Belvedere, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235508&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Obstructions on pavements and roads</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235508</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 20:10:44 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.502796 0.164148</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>This streetlight is off - again, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235501</link>
<description>This light (No. 7) has been out for some time. It leaves quite a large dark area on a street that has a phone theft problem. This doesn&amp;#39;t help and needs looking at urgently, please.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 28, Charlwood Street, Pimlico, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235501&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street lights</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235501</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 20:03:46 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.4908 -0.137795</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Streets lights come on too late, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235481</link>
<description>It’s dark outside and there are no lights. Kids constantly drive up on down on bikes with no lights&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235481.0.jpeg?69836be5&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 18, Ravensbury Road, St Paul&#39;s Cray, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235481&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Light Not Working</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235481</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:56:57 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.396678 0.096788</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dog poo and pee on stairs of Inwood house, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235479</link>
<description>Someone has been allowing their dog do deficate on the stairs of Inwood house. This is an ongoing problem&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235479.0.jpeg?0f7e9778&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Pytchley Road, East Dulwich, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235479&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Dog Waste Clearance (Estates)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235479</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:55:38 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.463025 -0.081003</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Road collapsing into drain, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235466</link>
<description>Hindering access to my property. Been reported before and has now been weeks. Unacceptable wait time. Fix it or you will start to need to write me letters for council tax&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235466.0.jpeg?dee838a0&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Kent House Road, Penge, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235466&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Road Defect</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235466</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:51:32 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.416426 -0.04454</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Three street lights not working, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235465</link>
<description>Three street lights are not working on this section of Hazelmere Road. This is causing the section of road outside of the tunnel to the woods to be very dark and increasing the risk to pedestrians and road users.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hazelmere Road, Petts Wood, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235465&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Light Not Working</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235465</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:50:43 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.394921 0.078069</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fly tipping, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235457</link>
<description>More fly tipping on the ‘T green’ leading up to Bostall woods&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235457.0.jpeg?1839fd3e&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Wickham Lane, Plumstead, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235457&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235457</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:48:38 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.482062 0.102074</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tarmac around edge has worn away, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235453</link>
<description>Tarmac worn away causing trip hazard. I tripped up this on 22nd September whilst out running and have bruised my ribs, cut my hand &amp;amp; arm and grazed both knees.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235453.0.jpeg?06afd033&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Nursery Avenue, Barnehurst, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235453&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other street defect</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235453</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:47:24 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.461851 0.144153</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Approximately 10mm deep pothole on pavement has been a tripping hazard, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235447</link>
<description>Approximately 10mm deep pothole on pavement in front of driveway has been a tripping hazard to my wife who is disabled. It has been more than 2 months and has only been getting bigger because of cats and foxes digging it deeper&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235447.0.jpeg?b0290573&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Newick Close, Bexley, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235447&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Damaged pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235447</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:44:08 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.449172 0.152381</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>New sacks, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235436</link>
<description>Always in the same position&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235436.0.jpeg?1877c398&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Kingsland Passage, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235436&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235436</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:38:40 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.546384 -0.076212</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Issue of Resident from 10 Daintry way E9 5JJ Graham Hawkins possibly tampering, storing items and going in cupboards in Daintry way block for a number of years since 2019 to 2022.The resident Graham Hawkins from number 10 Daintry way who has been going in and out Daintry way block Trowbridge estate cupboards,fiddling with things dressed inappropriately for someone who States they work for Hackney council to a resident who lives in the block. Possibly Hackney council new uniform.Graham Hawkins was wearing grey tracksuit bottoms, half naked bare chest man,flip-flops, tattoo on right upper arm shoulder and his wife&#39;s purple washing up gloves to hide his fingerprints with Hackney council keys. Graham Hawkins was An imposter is a person who pretends to be someone else such pretending to work for Hackney council to another resident in the block.reported to the metropolitan police safer neighborhood team Who seem to laugh when they see the pictures of imposter stating he works for the hackney council. police stated Graham Hawkins does not work for Hackney council dress like that and was laughing. Previously housing officer Simon Priscilla has stated the resident Graham Hawkins does not work for Hackney Council but in another breath another co-worker in the similar department ASB who goes by the name of Kathryn McHugh States Graham Hawkins does work for the council and cannot disclose that information. Hackney Council seem to be lying and covering anti-social behavior up protecting perpetrators. The local housing manager Denise corbin has been offloading her workload onto a resident Graham Hawkins unofficially working for hackney council doing Denise corbin job role and inspection job for her.possibly Denise corbin local manager can have the day off unofficially or stay in the office at Hillman Street hackney council for the day and not have to come down to the Trowbridge estate to do her inspections because Denise Corbin just has to pick up the phone and call her unofficial employee that Denise Corbyn uses for hackney council Graham Hawkins who lives nearby to ask him to do the inspection for housing manager Denise Corbin.in return housing manager turns a blind eye to resident Graham Hawkins behavior and anti-social behavior.Possibly Hackney council, corruption here. Which has not been investigated by Hackney council.This resident Graham Hawkins has been arrested by the metropolitan police because he was causing alarm and distressed to a resident,anti-social behavior. Graham Hawkins has a history of violence known to the police But the housing manager Denise Corbin unofficially is employing Graham Hawkins to do her job roll does Hackney council get the picture.if this is the case Denise Corbin is giving this resident Graham Hawkins permission,authorization as Graham Hawkins stated yes I work for the council to do Denise Corbin job role unofficially off the books only between two people knowing and enter the Daintry way block Trowbridge estate to cause alarm and distressed to another resident. The relationship between Graham Hawkins and the local aerial manager Denise corbin friends., 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235426</link>
<description>Hackney council pick on vulnerable disabled and learning disability people and do not address antisocial behavior.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235426.0.jpeg?6c6de483&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Reading Lane, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235426&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235426</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:35:09 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.54491 -0.057859</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Multiple pot holes, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235419</link>
<description>Seven sisters Rd JW St Ann&amp;#39;s Rd&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Seven Sisters Road, West Green, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235419&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pothole (minor)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235419</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:35:15 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.579486 -0.080647</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street light out, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235410</link>
<description>Street light at 31-33 Tanner Street is and has been out for months.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 33, Tanner Street, Old Kent Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235410&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street lighting</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235410</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:32:46 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.500322 -0.079777</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Overgrown trees blocking one side of road, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235398</link>
<description>Trees have now grown so far they are blocking one side of the road. Now it is dark it is even more dangerous driving as constantly forced onto opposite side of road at bend.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Trees need to ve severely pruned&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Blundell Close, Poverest, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235398&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Private Tree overhanging highway</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235398</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:30:11 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.386281 0.11281</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>More random household items, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235396</link>
<description>One day, I&amp;#39;m sure I could put these photos together and make an exhibit in the Tate Modern.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235396.0.jpeg?bb16be2d&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Glading Terrace, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235396&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235396</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:27:52 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.558124 -0.073874</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>4 blocked drains along Nightingale Place 29Sep25, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235387</link>
<description>Most of the drains along Nightingale Place are blocked. Photos taken 29Sep25.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Think I counted 4 of them blocked along this road down to the mini roundabout&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235387.0.jpeg?5ed381b5&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Nightingale Place, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235387&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Blocked Roadside Gully</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235387</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:24:31 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.482264 0.065284</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>