<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>White paint covering pavement, 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535397</link>
<description>Someone spills a can of white paint on the foot path several months ago. Please could we have it removed?&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8535397.0.jpeg?fa620f48&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Jerningham Road, New Cross Gate, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535397&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavement Jetting</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535397</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.471964 -0.040394</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Obstruction: Unauthorised Cones/Signs on Narrow Residential Road, 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535387</link>
<description>A resident living next to the school has put up their own unofficial “no parking” signs / cones / restrictions outside their property to stop parents from dropping off their children. These items are not council-issued and have been placed on the public highway.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This road is already quite narrow, with cars parked on both sides and large school buses needing to navigate it alongside parents and other road users. The unauthorised restrictions are adding to the congestion and confusing drivers.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Could the council please investigate and remove any unauthorised signage or objects, and provide guidance to the resident if required?&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Horn Park Lane, Eltham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535387&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535387</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.450505 0.022722</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>In front of Woodrow House Canterbury Road, NW6, 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535385</link>
<description>All along Canterbury Road , NW6 The Lights in front of Woodrow House and Across the Road ARE NOT SWITCHED ON.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Have Reported and they are STILL NOT ON. Roads are Open Now and Cars SPEEDING Down the Road. IT’s FRIGHTENING. What if it’s a Child, Elderly Person, ANY Resident and because the Street Lights are NOT ON, There is an ACCIDENT?&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Brent Council WILL BE AT FAULT. This is RIDICULOUS. You have built Woodrow House Put Street Lights In front of the Block and they are NOT ON.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;They do NOT have Numbers on either. WHY have they been put up? For Decoration? The Road is PITCH BLACK at Nights so Visibility is LIMITED.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The Street May look bright in the Photo, come down Canterbury Road at Nights and see how DARK IT IS. CRIME is also a Factor.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;If it’s DARK Criminals WILL ROAM. There has already been a HOMICIDE on Granville Road almost Two Years ago. CCTV and CCTV Signs were Requested as The Residents of Granville Road were FRIGHTENED after Witnessing The Homicide.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Brent Council DID NOT BOTHER. Showing LACK of CARE and SAFETY for The Residents.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Street Lights are IMMENSELY IMPORTANT. These lights in front of Woodrow Court, Canterbury Road NW6 MUST BE TURNED ON. Sooner rather than Later&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8535385.0.jpeg?303a9476&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Neville Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535385&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Lighting - Lamp Column not lit</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535385</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.533191 -0.199969</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flytipping, 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535379</link>
<description>Flytipping here is a weekly occurrence. We have complained to hackney for years. People on adjacent streets continue to do this despite being told not to by residents.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8535379.0.jpeg?9fe2baea&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Sandbrook Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535379&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping on Street</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535379</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:35:47 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.558419 -0.080995</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Public bin os 12- 13 Wadeville Close, 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535375</link>
<description>The public yellow bin is overflowing with rubbish and needs emptying asap please.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Wadeville Close, Lessness Heath, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535375&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street cleaning and litter</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535375</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.481455 0.149449</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>More leaves still on road and pavement its winter now so please collect and clean our street of leaves &amp; debri, 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535374</link>
<description>More leaves and debris are stood all along our road and although we reported on this couple of months ago they have not been back to take care of the entire pavement and road. The autumn leaves are still there and now they&amp;#39;re all stuck onto the pavement and the road making it very very dangerous with all the wet weather we&amp;#39;re heading now as well of people falling where the council would be liable can you please come and clean our street regularly? it is often neglected and this year has been worse than ever whatever is on the road from trees that do not belong to us and that in our garden and we have to take care of them this is not fair as the Council is responsible for the pavement and roads. We pay a hefty council tax so please use it to our favour once in awhile thank you.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8535374.0.jpeg?b73e2a2e&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Durham Avenue, Shortlands, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535374&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Leafing</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535374</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.397837 0.007916</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>95 Brondesbury villas by tree, 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535372</link>
<description>Fly tipping&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8535372.0.jpeg?c416f4a2&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Brondesbury Villas, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535372&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly-tip Medium - Up to medium size van load</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535372</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.535754 -0.19865</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Plumstead (common) Adventure Playground Graffiti, 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535288</link>
<description>Please see photo for more details there is graffiti all around the Plumstead (common) Adventure Playground.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I&amp;#39;ve also put in another report for graffiti on a bench nearby:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Between the Prince of Wales pub and the Adventure playground FixMyStreet ref: 8535264.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Thanks&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8535288.0.jpeg?d8f856b6&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Blendon Terrace, Plumstead&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535288&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535288</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.48182 0.076556</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Canterbury Road NW6, 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535283</link>
<description>The Street Lights Pictured along with ALL The Street Lights in front of the New Flats are NOT ON. At Nights it’s EXTREMELY DANGEROUS as 4 Roads are Open and Cars, Motorbikes, Bikes, Scooters they come at a Speed.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;For Residents, Young and Elderly and Children it’s HIGHLY DANGEROUS. There are Nurseries, Children Coming to and from School, Residents going in and out of their homes and with NO STREET LIGHTS ON. I have seen other Residents Complaining for MONTHS and STILL NOTHING.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Sadly if there is an ACCIDENT Brent Council will move to action and put The Lights back on. The Street Lights in front of the New Flats have NO NUMBERS on them so how can you say which Numbers to Switch on. They Look like Victorian Street Lights, NONE of THEM are ON.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;WHY are the Residents COMPLAINTS being IGNORED? This is The Second Time I have COMPLAINED. I am CONCERNED as I can see an ACCIDENT waiting to happen .&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Coming from Shopping on a Night Now is SCARY and DANGEROUS as these Lights are STILL NOT ON.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;It’s TIME to Sort this out for the SAFETY of the Residents.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8535283.0.jpeg?165582b5&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Mile Walk, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535283&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Lighting - Lamp Column not lit</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535283</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.533101 -0.199739</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Traffic lights not working properly, 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535268</link>
<description>Yesterday evening (10/12/25) I was waiting for lights to change on Royal College Street/Kentish Town Road (northbound next to number 349/old public toilets). There is a sensor indicating movement/cyclists waiting however it seems faulty as no red light bulb came on (I believe it normally indicates it&amp;#39;s working) and it skipped 5 lights turning green 5 times (these usually turn green once pedestrian crossed), meaning a massive queue of cyclists and cars has built up and no one knew what to do. Please repair, thank you&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Castle Road, Kentish Town, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535268&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Stuck on red</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535268</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.545208 -0.141662</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bench in need of TLC (graffiti on it and in need of straightening, tilted back wards permanently), 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535264</link>
<description>There is a bench (see photo, it has all the details you need incl a map) at the plumstead common, between the Prince of Wales pub and the Adventure playground, it is covered in graffiti and appears to have been pushed backwards by something heavy (can&amp;#39;t imagine this is an intended feature, the other benches do not have it).&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8535264.0.jpeg?350e5510&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Plumstead Common Road, Plumstead&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535264&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Parks/landscapes</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535264</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.481813 0.074778</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Litter on the green and paths at Escott Gardens including a large piece of polystyrene packaging., 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535257</link>
<description>Some of this litter has been around for weeks. Also some dirty cat litter which was left behind after dustbins were emptied 2 weeks ago.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Escott Gardens, Elmstead, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535257&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Litter and Detritus</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535257</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.425896 0.045155</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Very slippery surface due to heavy mos &amp; surface breaking up, 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535254</link>
<description>The majority of the asphelt sidewalk on the southern side of Lane has been degrading over a period years and it has become very difficult to travese using a wheelchair (my mother is wheelchair bound and I often push her to the village). This is exacerbated by increasingly heavy moss during autumn and winter, making it very slippery.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8535254.0.jpeg?5bf05ef4&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Back Lane, Bexley, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535254&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Damaged road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535254</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:09:57 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.444625 0.1429</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Concrete Stairway from Edge Hill to Nightingale Place Overgrown and messy, 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535246</link>
<description>The Concrete stairway that takes you from Edge Hill (Plumstead, London SE18) to Nightingale Place is very overgrown, with lots of rubbish and leaves on the stairs, it could be a tripping hazard&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Edge Hill, Woolwich&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535246&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/Footpaths Repairs</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535246</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.482006 0.069008</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Outside Block 153 Granville Road, NW6 5AR, 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535226</link>
<description>Furniture , Wood Planks etc as Pictured. Blue Recycle Bin Storage Boxes and General Recycling Items Need Clearing ASAP.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This is The ONLY Blue Communal Recycling Bin So it gets FULL FAST. Need More of these Bins on Granville Road NW6&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8535226.0.jpeg?9428842d&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Granville Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535226&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly-tip Large - More than a van load</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535226</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.532974 -0.195864</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rubbish dumped, 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535209</link>
<description>Car set left and is blocking road.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8535209.0.jpeg?e76d8d32&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Ashby Road, New Cross, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535209&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly-Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535209</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.467555 -0.028188</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street sweep required, 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535203</link>
<description>This section STILL NOT SWEPT!!!! Very dangerous to pedestrians.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8535203.0.jpeg?52a40c9a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Ashby Road, New Cross, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535203&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street Cleaning</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535203</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.467729 -0.028598</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street sweep required, 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535202</link>
<description>This section STILL NOT SWEPT!!!! Very dangerous to pedestrians.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8535202.0.jpeg?52a40c9a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Ashby Road, New Cross, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535202&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street Cleaning</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535202</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.467729 -0.028598</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fly tipping and overflowing bins, 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535200</link>
<description>Our bins haven&amp;#39;t been collected and people are fly tipping their rubbish&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Eastway, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535200&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Overflowing bin</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535200</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 15:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.545049 -0.03002</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Waste all over pavement, 11th December</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535178</link>
<description>The content of these bins is often all over the pavement, including a lot of dog waste. Not only is it unsightly and unsanitary, but people need to walk in the street to avoid it.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I think the bins either need to be moved or emptied every day.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The bins are at the corner of Whateley Road and Landcroft Road.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 199, Lordship Lane, East Dulwich, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535178&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Litter Bin - Move or Remove</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8535178</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 15:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.454919 -0.076731</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>