<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Issue of Resident from 10 Daintry way E9 5JJ Graham Hawkins possibly tampering, storing items and going in cupboards in Daintry way block for a number of years since 2019 to 2022.The resident Graham Hawkins from number 10 Daintry way who has been going in and out Daintry way block Trowbridge estate cupboards,fiddling with things dressed inappropriately for someone who States they work for Hackney council to a resident who lives in the block. Possibly Hackney council new uniform.Graham Hawkins was wearing grey tracksuit bottoms, half naked bare chest man,flip-flops, tattoo on right upper arm shoulder and his wife&#39;s purple washing up gloves to hide his fingerprints with Hackney council keys. Graham Hawkins was An imposter is a person who pretends to be someone else such pretending to work for Hackney council to another resident in the block.reported to the metropolitan police safer neighborhood team Who seem to laugh when they see the pictures of imposter stating he works for the hackney council. police stated Graham Hawkins does not work for Hackney council dress like that and was laughing. Previously housing officer Simon Priscilla has stated the resident Graham Hawkins does not work for Hackney Council but in another breath another co-worker in the similar department ASB who goes by the name of Kathryn McHugh States Graham Hawkins does work for the council and cannot disclose that information. Hackney Council seem to be lying and covering anti-social behavior up protecting perpetrators. The local housing manager Denise corbin has been offloading her workload onto a resident Graham Hawkins unofficially working for hackney council doing Denise corbin job role and inspection job for her.possibly Denise corbin local manager can have the day off unofficially or stay in the office at Hillman Street hackney council for the day and not have to come down to the Trowbridge estate to do her inspections because Denise Corbin just has to pick up the phone and call her unofficial employee that Denise Corbyn uses for hackney council Graham Hawkins who lives nearby to ask him to do the inspection for housing manager Denise Corbin.in return housing manager turns a blind eye to resident Graham Hawkins behavior and anti-social behavior.Possibly Hackney council, corruption here. Which has not been investigated by Hackney council.This resident Graham Hawkins has been arrested by the metropolitan police because he was causing alarm and distressed to a resident,anti-social behavior. Graham Hawkins has a history of violence known to the police But the housing manager Denise Corbin unofficially is employing Graham Hawkins to do her job roll does Hackney council get the picture.if this is the case Denise Corbin is giving this resident Graham Hawkins permission,authorization as Graham Hawkins stated yes I work for the council to do Denise Corbin job role unofficially off the books only between two people knowing and enter the Daintry way block Trowbridge estate to cause alarm and distressed to another resident. The relationship between Graham Hawkins and the local aerial manager Denise corbin friends., 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235426</link>
<description>Hackney council pick on vulnerable disabled and learning disability people and do not address antisocial behavior.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235426.0.jpeg?6c6de483&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Reading Lane, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235426&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235426</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:35:09 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.54491 -0.057859</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Multiple pot holes, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235419</link>
<description>Seven sisters Rd JW St Ann&amp;#39;s Rd&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Seven Sisters Road, West Green, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235419&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pothole (minor)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235419</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:35:15 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.579486 -0.080647</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street light out, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235410</link>
<description>Street light at 31-33 Tanner Street is and has been out for months.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 33, Tanner Street, Old Kent Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235410&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street lighting</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235410</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:32:46 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.500322 -0.079777</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Overgrown trees blocking one side of road, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235398</link>
<description>Trees have now grown so far they are blocking one side of the road. Now it is dark it is even more dangerous driving as constantly forced onto opposite side of road at bend.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Trees need to ve severely pruned&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Blundell Close, Poverest, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235398&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Private Tree overhanging highway</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235398</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:30:11 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.386281 0.11281</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>More random household items, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235396</link>
<description>One day, I&amp;#39;m sure I could put these photos together and make an exhibit in the Tate Modern.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235396.0.jpeg?bb16be2d&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Glading Terrace, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235396&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235396</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:27:52 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.558124 -0.073874</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>4 blocked drains along Nightingale Place 29Sep25, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235387</link>
<description>Most of the drains along Nightingale Place are blocked. Photos taken 29Sep25.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Think I counted 4 of them blocked along this road down to the mini roundabout&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235387.0.jpeg?5ed381b5&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Nightingale Place, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235387&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Blocked Roadside Gully</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235387</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:24:31 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.482264 0.065284</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>To whom it concerns. Could you please address these issues previously happened but not addressed antisocial behaviour criminal activity.A Residence of the Trowbridge estate Graham Hawkins has been breaking into Osborne road void garages since 2016 &amp; 2023 rent free. Graham Hawkins breaking into void garages with a battery pack handle grinder.Residence, Leaseholders were disturbed by what Graham Hawkins was doing Which this behaviour should not be tolerated by hackney council &amp; Randall Kerry garage team hand posted a warning letter to the address of Graham Hawkins 10 Dainty way E9 5JJ.Resident from 21 Mallard close E9 5JL Eugene Egan has been involved with the trespassing,assisting,helping Graham Hawkins move his stuff out of garage.when mr Graham Hawkins was breaking into the garage Eugene Egan was also aware of what Graham Hawkins was doing.Breaking and entering trespassing. Also on the night when Graham Hawkins was breaking into the garage 16,19,with a battery pack handle grinder. Eugene Egan approach mr Graham Hawkins and reply to Graham Hawkins the subcontractor purdys cut the lock and done that to you Graham and took your stuff out of garage 19 and put it into garage 16 and changed lock.Graham Hawkins was cutting the padlock off garage 16 with a battery handle grinder as Eugene Egan was there with Graham Hawkins On 01/08/23 at 20:00pm.Eugene Egan knows this information because he has a CCTV overlooking all of the leaseholders garages monitoring their daily routines and feeding information to Graham Hawkins. criminal behaviour was taken place. Eugene Egan has been tipping resident Graham Hawkins off about the void garages because it&#39;s a coincident how chair member knows which garages are empty,void and which ones are leased out seen as Eugene Egan works with the council official people he would know that sort of information.Hackney council put notice up on garage door to vacate garage 19,16 trespassing Graham Hawkins remove his stuff out of garage 16 and placed it into two garages which Eugene Egan has access and keys owns, leases from Hackney council which was 23 &amp; 24 Osborne road garages subletting criminal activity, possibly garage tenancy fraud in different names.Eugene Egan help,assisting,perpetrator,trespasser resident Graham Hawkins remove his stuff into Eugene egan garages at 23 &amp; 24 because the resident got caught and found out by the local hackney council garage team.Eugene Egan and Graham Hawkins should not be in that garage without the hackney councils authorization,criminal activity, trespassing.Shows the connections with one another how Trowbridge resident association chair member looks out for Graham Hawkins.criminal behaviour.Tra corruption. This was reported to the metropolitan police. Residence and other Leaseholders pay their rent so why should this one or two residents get away with breaking into garages rent free for a number of years this is discrimination and antisocial behavior. If somebody could please address this behavior and investigate., 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235382</link>
<description>To whom it concerns. Could you please address these issues previously happened but not addressed antisocial behaviour criminal activity.A Residence of the Trowbridge estate Graham Hawkins has been breaking into Osborne road void garages since 2016 &amp;amp; 2023 r&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235382.0.jpeg?f63b4ecb&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Reading Lane, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235382&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235382</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:22:42 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.545003 -0.057982</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Blocked drain 29Sep25, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235380</link>
<description>Photo taken 29th September 2025 on corner of Elmdene Road&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235380.0.jpeg?7ea47e68&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Plumstead Common Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235380&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Blocked Roadside Gully</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235380</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:22:34 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.482271 0.068732</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Strong sewage smell from Roadside Drain/Gulley, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235375</link>
<description>Causing pressure issues in the home. Plumber suggests it’s the main sewer that has a partial blockage that could back up into the home.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 70, Blanmerle Road, New Eltham, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235375&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Blocked Roadside Gully</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235375</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:22:02 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.43907 0.066982</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dumped rubbish near bin. There has been a fire here recently &amp; it’s where kids play, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235364</link>
<description>Constant dumping of rubbish &amp;amp; fly tipping &amp;amp; dangerous building waste on Blackstone estate for the last two years. There had been a fire in the overflowing bins recently. There is also a rat and fox problem that is attracted by the waste.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235364.0.jpeg?3e51dca4&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Elmbridge Walk, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235364&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Overflowing bin</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235364</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:18:51 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.541041 -0.063276</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>A victim of car robberies belongings and items discarded out her stolen vehicle in Merriam Ave, garages out the site of commissioners camera. Why are the council and the mayor and the commissioner of the metropolitan police allowing this to happen antisocial behavior., 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235357</link>
<description>Your local authority do not care about robbery or fifth or criminal activity they let it happen to innocent residents and Leaseholders on a daily basis they don&amp;#39;t care long as they get their rent and money in this world they don&amp;#39;t care.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235357.0.jpeg?0e271e68&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Beanacre Close, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235357&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235357</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:17:47 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.545407 -0.028851</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Green household bin dumped full of waste, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235342</link>
<description>I have reported this before. Fix my street informed me that the case is closed and has been dealt with. It is still there and has been for over 8 weeks. It is on the grass verge at Albion road on the corner of Townley road. It is tucked up against the fence and can be missed if looking to quickly&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235342.0.jpeg?e2ffb6b6&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Albion Road, Barnehurst, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235342&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Grass Verges</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235342</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:12:24 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.455132 0.144372</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Kerb uplight by tree roots, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235339</link>
<description>Lifting and disruption: The growing roots have exerted pressure, which has lifted and cracked, and displace the kerbstones by the tree, leading to unsafe conditions.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 47, Lime Grove, Blackfen, Sidcup, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235339&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235339</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:11:47 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.45018 0.097887</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The streets are disgusting, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235336</link>
<description>I am not sure if street and road cleaning have been reduced but the streets and roads between London Fields and Kingsland Road have declined in cleanliness recently. Everywhere seems to be covered with little and dog fouling and never seems to be cleaned.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Albion Drive, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235336&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Littering</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235336</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:11:44 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.539357 -0.070792</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dog mess, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235322</link>
<description>Dog mess on the pavement&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Albion Drive, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235322&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235322</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:11:20 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.539276 -0.06935</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pavement maintenance, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235314</link>
<description>Pavement is old and now badly cracked following roadworks a few months ago&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235314.0.jpeg?ef667137&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 82, Pickhurst Park, Hayes, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235314&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavement Defect</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235314</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:04:55 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.389253 0.003685</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Freezer dumped, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235311</link>
<description>Freezer was dumped when the tree branch was blocking pavement, tree was cleared but freezer left.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Crockenhill Road, St Mary Cray, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235311&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flyposting</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235311</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:03:23 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.385239 0.141314</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>There are 5 wooden pallets and rubbish bags dumped outside 1 Duke Street, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235305</link>
<description>There are 5 wooden pallets and rubbish bags dumped outside 1 Duke Street&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235305.0.jpeg?b66eb545&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1a, Duke Street, Mayfair, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235305&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235305</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:01:35 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.516351 -0.152384</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Whole street needs sweeping, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235304</link>
<description>Please spend some time property sweeping the street&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8235304.0.jpeg?5a44c800&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Kilburn Lane, Kilburn, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235304&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street cleaning - Street needs sweeping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235304</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:01:19 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.533004 -0.20544</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Piece of wood and matt dumped here, 30th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235301</link>
<description>Please collect, wood been there for few weeks&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Kilburn Lane, North Kensington, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235301&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly-tip Small - Less than one bag</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8235301</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 18:59:26 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.532464 -0.20958</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>