<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Pathway in park cracked and dropped causing trip hazard, 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622071</link>
<description>The pathway along the park near to the cafe has dropped and cracked over a large area causing a dangerous trip hazard. My daughter tripped on it today causing her to hurt her ankle. In addition to this area there are several other sections of the pathways in the park, mainly on the middle section path, that have deteriorated and are on different levels that need repairing or replacing as they have the potential for a serious trip hazards on the hill.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8622071.0.jpeg?6c23e71b&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Parkside Gardens, Brunswick Park, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622071&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622071</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 21:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.634863 -0.15291</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fly tipping at Wickham Road end of Kemerton Road on pavement, 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622053</link>
<description>Fly tipping as above&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Kemerton Road, Beckenham, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622053&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytip</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622053</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 21:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.40398 -0.019108</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lights out, 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622047</link>
<description>Bottom of Eltham high street lights are out on all 4 corners near McDonald&amp;#39;s&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Eltham High Street, Well Hall, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622047&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>All out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622047</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 21:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.450769 0.052137</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>124 Brondesbury villas, 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622046</link>
<description>Xmas tree&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8622046.0.jpeg?caac0253&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Brondesbury Villas, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622046&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly-tip Small - Less than one bag</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622046</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 21:02:10 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.535185 -0.200511</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Car For Sale Over Since Oct 2025, 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622032</link>
<description>There is a white Ford Fiesta that has been for sale near the entrance of the Pavillion Club for over a month. It has been in a collision with it&amp;#39;s drivers side mirror smashed off. The person who is selling this car constantly dumps cars &amp;quot;for sale&amp;quot; along this stretch making parking difficult for residents. This car has been parked up for sale since Oct 2025.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8622032.0.jpeg?f0178e6d&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Footscray Road, Eltham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622032&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622032</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.446472 0.062549</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pothole dangerous, 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622022</link>
<description>Poorly patched pothole damaged my car, yet again no one will pay for this. Pothole is the right line of 3 lanes that turn right from A4 towards Earl’s Court tube&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): West Cromwell Road, Earl&#39;s Court, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622022&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pothole (major)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622022</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.494406 -0.195721</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>MDF board dumped, 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622018</link>
<description>Please collect&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8622018.0.jpeg?e7c7608c&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Queen&#39;s Mead Road, Shortlands, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622018&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytip</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8622018</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.403588 0.005386</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flytip, 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621997</link>
<description>Hillbrck Clise by flats bin Chamber opposite Entrance to Icekand. Please clear flytip&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8621997.0.jpeg?9a62803b&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hillbeck Close, Peckham, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621997&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping - General (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621997</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.480367 -0.056951</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Collapsed drain cover, 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621994</link>
<description>Collapsed drain cover needs rectifying immediately as is dangerous.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8621994.0.jpeg?11bed82f&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Albemarle Road, Shortlands, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621994&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Road Defect</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621994</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.409128 -0.012844</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>58 A - bike blocking pavement every day, 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621992</link>
<description>They have a huge house and choose to park their bike on the pavement causing a blockage. Today I saw a wheelchair user having to cross the street to get past which is quite frankly disgusting. I see from Google Street maps that they&amp;#39;ve had this parked their since 2022 - how has this not been stopped before? Absolute self-centered arrogance.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8621992.0.jpeg?bf375b13&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Royal Place, Greenwich&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621992&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/Footpaths Repairs</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621992</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.476272 -0.00858</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abandoned zconeays Barriers, 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621981</link>
<description>Outside 911-915 Okd Kent Road. Please clear abandoned Conways barriers&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8621981.0.jpeg?2110a533&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Old Kent Road, Peckham, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621981&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Debris in the carriageway</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621981</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.478489 -0.054051</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Streetlight not working, 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621971</link>
<description>Streetlight opposite number 173 isn&amp;#39;t working, it&amp;#39;s very dark and doesn&amp;#39;t feel safe to walk along there.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 165, Longlands Road, Longlands, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621971&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Lamp post</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621971</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.432942 0.097478</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Traffic light knocked over, 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621961</link>
<description>New Cross Road junction of Hatcham Park Traffic light has been knocked ocver&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8621961.0.jpeg?afb0fd6d&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): New Cross Gate, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621961&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Damage - pole leaning / equipment detached from pole/facing the wrong direction</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621961</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.475276 -0.046927</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Icy Road causing motorcycle accidents, 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621960</link>
<description>Road needs salt/grit as motorcycles keep crashing on the turn&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 42, Southampton Way, Camberwell, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621960&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621960</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.480437 -0.090182</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bed and mattress dumped, 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621956</link>
<description>This bed and mattress was dumped by where the garages use to be on Lambarde Avenue. This has been here for about a week. There is also a wheelie bin that has been left in the location that has incorrect contents. This has been left for a few months.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8621956.0.jpeg?cc551fab&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Lambarde Avenue, Eltham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621956&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621956</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:11:47 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.427299 0.060233</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Graffiti sprayed on side of storage unit outside 29 Bedwell house residential flats., 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621925</link>
<description>I like to report graffiti sprayed on the side of a Lambeth street storage unit outside 29 Bedwell house residential estate. The graffiti is against a grey metal panel. Please could it be removed it has been there approximately over two months now since I first reported it.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8621925.0.jpeg?52ca46a2&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 328, Brixton Road, Brixton, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621925&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621925</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 19:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.468742 -0.112774</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Burst water/ leaking pipe, 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621923</link>
<description>This was reported to Thames water over 2 weeks ago, however the freezing temperatures is causing the water to freeze making the crossing and pathway treacherous. Someone will either slip into the road trying to cross at the pedestrian crossing or break a bone falling on the frozen pavement. The water is gushing also causing pedestrians to be soaked when walking along the pavement&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 5, Brampton Road, Blendon, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621923&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flooding in the road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621923</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 19:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.461119 0.126738</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ouside Lemoge Clinic, 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621917</link>
<description>I reported the rocking manhole very recently and I received the response that &amp;#39;&amp;#39;Our Inspector has visited this location and found a new cover has been fitted&amp;#39;. The issue remains the same, the manhole might be new as you mentioned in your Fix My Street report but it keeps rocking. I have also raised a formal complaint on Camden&amp;#39;s website (ref COMLR25476). Please send the inspector to check the manhole again and tell them that it must be checked with a car or a vehicle to run over it so you can actually hear it rocking. It keeps rocking while I am writing this message.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Kilburn High Road, Kilburn, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621917&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Manhole in the road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621917</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 19:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.541469 -0.197569</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Signboard missing, lack of countdown, Grasshaven Overall complaint, danger to the environment, 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621892</link>
<description>Dear Royal Borough of Greenwich,&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I am writing to raise a formal complaint about the continuing neglect of the Thamesmead Moorings map signage at Grasshaven Way, and the wider state of the immediate public realm around it. In or around January 2020, severe winds tore away the large map sign that displayed the local moorings and the Grasshaven Way area. This was not a small decorative item. It was a public wayfinding feature, a marker of local identity, and part of the area’s sense of place. It was also clearly a council installed asset. Years later, it has still not been replaced. That prolonged inaction is unacceptable.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This is not only about a missing sign. It is about what the absence communicates to residents: that our area is not worth maintaining, that basic public assets can be lost and simply forgotten, and that local culture and pride are optional rather than valued.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;It is particularly frustrating because the location is not hidden away. It sits in a place people pass and wait, including by the nearby bus stop. Yet there remains a visible lack of care in the immediate environment, including persistent littering and general grime. When everyday public spaces look abandoned, it normalises neglect and invites more of it.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;To make matters worse, the bus stop immediately next to this area still lacks a working real time countdown display. Whatever the reason for this, the result is the same: residents are left waiting without reliable passenger information, especially during poor weather. This is exactly the kind of basic service gap that becomes even more aggravating when the surrounding public realm is also visibly uncared for. It also makes the SL11 issue feel even more unreasonable, because residents are expected to tolerate service shortcomings without even the minimum passenger information infrastructure.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I am asking the Council to treat this as a matter of public realm standards, resident confidence, and local identity, not as a minor cosmetic request.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Please provide a written response addressing the following: 1. Asset record and responsibility Confirm whether the Grasshaven Way Thamesmead Moorings map signage is recorded on your asset register, and which team is responsible for its maintenance and replacement.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;2. Replacement commitment and timeline Confirm whether the map signage will be replaced. If yes, provide a clear timetable with target dates for design, procurement, installation, and completion. If no, provide the reasons and the decision maker.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;3. Interim action If replacement will take time, confirm what interim measure will be installed to avoid leaving an obvious “missing” public asset in place for yet another year.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;4. Public realm standards at the site Confirm what actions will be taken to address litter and environmental condition in the immediate area, including what the cleaning schedule is and what enforcement activity is planned where needed.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Bus stop real time information 5. Confirm who is responsible for the countdown display at the nearby bus stop and what steps will be taken to install or restore real time passenger information, including expected dates.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;6. Accountability Provide a named officer or team contact and a reference number for this complaint. If this issue has been previously logged, please link it to the existing record.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Residents are tired of seeing visible neglect normalised. The Council should not need SIX WHOLE YEARS to replace a torn down map and restore basic standards around a key everyday location. If this matter cannot be resolved promptly, I will escalate it through the Council’s complaint stages and to ward councillors.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I look forward to your response within the published timescales for formal complaints.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Yours faithfully, Joel Okanta&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8621892.0.jpeg?ecbf99c3&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Central Way, Thamesmead, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621892&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street furniture</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621892</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 19:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.501467 0.102937</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Graffiti, 3rd January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621871</link>
<description>Loampit Bale (Haleswortgh Road) Remove graffiti from bus shelter&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8621871.0.jpeg?6c286767&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Loampit Hill, Deptford, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621871&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti / Flyposting on stop or shelter (non-offensive)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8621871</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 19:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.466435 -0.020996</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>