<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Mattress dumped, 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647473</link>
<description>Mattress has been dumped against tree at junction with Trafalgar Close for about a week&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8647473.0.jpeg?daaa9e64&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 39, Greenland Quay, Rotherhithe, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647473&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping - General (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647473</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.493532 -0.041787</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fly tipped rubbish has been left in two lots on Grangehill Road, 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647461</link>
<description>Between Greenvale and Earlshall Roads there are two lots of Flytipping been left in Grangehill Road&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8647461.0.jpeg?ddfc10fb&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Grangehill Road, Eltham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647461&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647461</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.457809 0.055153</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fly tipping, 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647460</link>
<description>Fly tipping&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8647460.0.jpeg?4c87333a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Wynford Way, Eltham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647460&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647460</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:46:23 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.432173 0.057007</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abandoned vehicle untaxed, 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647439</link>
<description>Vehicle abandoned for over 1 year and now untaxed. Av59 vkk&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Lessness Heath, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647439&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647439</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.495502 0.127749</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flytipping at junction of Abbey Gardens and Monnow Road, 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647430</link>
<description>See above&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Monnow Road, Bermondsey, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647430&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping - General (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647430</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:42:54 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.491643 -0.067357</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large amount of dog fouling, 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647422</link>
<description>Dog mess&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Sunray Avenue, Dulwich Village, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647422&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Dog Waste Clearance (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647422</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.45827 -0.090035</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Drug users loitering early morning Christmas Eve outside my front door making telephone calls to order drugs to collect.., 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647404</link>
<description>Drug users loitering,urinating, feces outside my door on redpath.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8647404.0.jpeg?717b1fe8&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Edmeston Close, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647404&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Sport Area</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647404</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.546866 -0.033054</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Crashed wall lying in access road., 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647397</link>
<description>Recent&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8647397.0.jpeg?bbf27eb5&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 103, Abbey Street, Old Kent Road, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647397&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647397</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:38:54 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.497899 -0.076449</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Very large hole has opened up in the road, 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647339</link>
<description>Someone has placed a wheelie bin over the hole in the road on Holmsdale as you are approaching the mini roundabout before Page heath lane/Villas&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Homesdale Road, Widmore, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647339&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Road Defect</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647339</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.400714 0.035612</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Debris and Waste on Pavement, 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647334</link>
<description>I own the restaurant Greystone and continually get people adding bags and rubbish next to and on top of my bins causing failed collection. My main green bin has not been collected in 2 weeks as someone has put a broken old cupboard and generals waste bags next to my bins. Please note that the bags appear to have letters sticking out the top so the culprit should be easily identifiable.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8647334.0.jpeg?20962bcc&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Weir Road, Bexley, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647334&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647334</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.441997 0.150769</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Damaged footway os 117, 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647298</link>
<description>Footway has been damaged and is sinking after building works and skips being placed on the pavement&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 104, Wellington Avenue, Blackfen, Sidcup, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647298&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Damaged pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647298</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.446467 0.104014</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pothole near No.64, 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647288</link>
<description>Pothole centre of road near no.64 down to base concrete.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 175, Old Farm Avenue, Longlands, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647288&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Damaged road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647288</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.436592 0.091277</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pothole near No. 177, 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647272</link>
<description>Pothole centre of road near no.177 down to base concrete.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 175, Old Farm Avenue, Longlands, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647272&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Damaged road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647272</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.436592 0.091277</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Residents living in the Frampton Park Estate in Hackney, east London, have told the BBC they have been living without water for almost five days. Some residents have reported a limited supply, with many saying toilets are unable to be flushed. Hackney Council said the problem had been caused by a burst water main in the E9 area and that it was talking to Thames Water &quot;to ensure they address these issues as quickly as possible&quot; and &quot;provide the support that the residents affected need in the meantime&quot;. Thames Water said the burst water main had affected water pressure &quot;to a number of blocks&quot;, and said teams had been working &quot;around the clock to resolve this complex issue&quot;. &#39;Nightmare&#39; Serap Cifci, who lives in the Wellstreet Block on the Frampton Park Estate with her mother, said a pack of six water bottles were left on her doorstep on Saturday evening, before they had experienced any water supply problems. Other neighbours had received the same pack of water, but said they were not informed as to where this had come from. Cifci said: &quot;I thought they might be being kind because it was so cold and pipes might freeze, but then I thought probably not, as no-one gives out anything for free.&quot; Then, in the early hours of Sunday morning, Cifci said she tried to use the toilet and it would not flush. Since then she has had no cold or hot water supply to her property. Cifci said she then contacted Hackney Council, which told her to contact Thames Water. Thames Water, Cifci said, &quot;only offered a virtual assistant via WhatsApp&quot;. She said it was unable to explain &quot;much more than: &#39;We are working to fix the problem&#39;. &quot;We have no idea how long this is going to go on for,&quot; Cifci said. She described how she had been travelling to her partner&#39;s house and local friends&#39; houses for showers, which she said was costing her unnecessary travel expenses. She described the situation as &quot;a nightmare&quot;. &#39;Stress triggers seizures&#39; Nearby, Lesley McCutcheon, who lives on Woolridge Way, said she had been without water for nearly six days. &quot;Along with having no cold water in the bathrooms and no water in the toilet system since New Year&#39;s Day, we couldn&#39;t get through to the emergency out-of-hours number,&quot; she said. She added: &quot;I suffer from arthritis so trying to lift buckets of water to flush a toilet is impossible. I have to wait for my husband or daughter to return home from work.&quot; McCutcheon said she had epilepsy, which meant she could not carry boiled kettle water to fill up sinks to wash dishes. &quot;I&#39;m not allowed to put myself into danger,&quot; she said. &quot;Stress triggers seizures. Also its been absolutely freezing and there is no water to go through the boiler to put the heating on, which really affects my arthritis.&quot; She said the situation was &quot;stressful&quot; and was made worse &quot;when nobody tells you what is happening&quot;. Local councillor Clare Joseph updated local residents via a community Facebook page and said she had been told by Hackney Council&#39;s repairs team that the problem should be fixed by Thames Water by Thursday evening. She also said: &quot;I have asked for confirmation that Thames will distribute bottled water.&quot; Hackney Council said they were aware of the issues and &quot;appreciate how frustrating this has been for residents&quot;. A Thames Water spokesperson said: &quot;We&#39;re very sorry to residents of the Frampton Park Estate who have been experiencing water supply issues. We understand how disruptive and distressing this has been, and we apologise for the inconvenience caused.&quot; The company said repair work was expected to finish on Thursday. The spokesperson added: &quot;Once the repair is complete, we will carry out standard testing to make sure everything is back to normal, before we recharge the water main to bring the area back into service. We&#39;re aiming to complete this process as quickly as possible. &quot;In the meantime, we&#39;re prioritising support for customers who need extra support and who are on our Priority Services Register, and bottled water deliveries are being made to those households.&quot;, 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647270</link>
<description>Hackney Council, Thames water get your act together vulnerable disabled elderly people suffering with no water supply for one week on frampton park estate. This is sickening,distressing for residents. Hackney Council not informing residents or updating.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8647270.0.jpeg?242d654a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Hillman Street, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647270&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Maintenance / Repairs Issue</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647270</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.545351 -0.05743</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>A Fly Tipping on Street problem has been found, 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647240</link>
<description>Fridge and bags of builders rubbish dumped by tree outside 49 Lingwood Road&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Lingwood Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647240&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping on Street</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647240</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.573311 -0.062673</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large sinkhole which is getting worse daily, 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647219</link>
<description>Sinkhole which rapidly growing in size, in the middle of the pedestrian crossing, has been there since the summer of 2025, holes and cracks now appearing in the road surface.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8647219.0.jpeg?de635378&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Barnfield Gardens, Plumstead&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647219&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647219</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.48205 0.072012</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Excessive rubbish in bushes, 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647210</link>
<description>This rubbish has been in these bushes for at least 2 months and is getting worse. The bin is being emptied but the rest of the rubbish is still there. It&amp;#39;s absolutely disgusting.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8647210.0.jpeg?f9996700&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Shooters Hill, Plumstead&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647210&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Litter Bin</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647210</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.470722 0.058023</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rubbish blocking the pavement, 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647175</link>
<description>This creates a real hazard as wheelchair and buggy users can’t go through and need to cross the road at a dangerous intersection of Tewson Road to Lakedale road&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8647175.0.jpeg?e9a9a213&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Tewson Road, Plumstead&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647175&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647175</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:12:26 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.486723 0.091461</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pot hole centre of road near no . 18, 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647161</link>
<description>Pothole centre of road near no.18 down to base concrete.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 23, Old Farm Avenue, Longlands, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647161&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Damaged road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647161</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.434777 0.100619</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Smashed bollard and smashed road name sign, 8th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647140</link>
<description>Smashed bollard and smashed road name sign from a road traffic collision. Footways paving slabs also raised and broken. Sainsbury Rd junction with Gipsy Hill.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8647140.0.jpeg?3cc14f7a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 79A, Sainsbury Road, West Norwood, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647140&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8647140</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.424149 -0.083871</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>