<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Massive amount of litter and rubish on and next to the stairs needs clearing, 11th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401901</link>
<description>Disgusting amount of litter on the stairs and around them, they are public stairs and I have seen many rats there in the daytime going through the rubbish its a public health hazard. So much for a Royal borough.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8401901.0.jpeg?e6921fb5&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Pettman Crescent, Plumstead, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401901&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/Footpaths Repairs</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401901</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 03:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.491116 0.082862</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>No street lighting on the slope down to the Subway alongside Plumstead Road, 11th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401899</link>
<description>No street lighting on the slope down from Plumstead Road bus stop down towards the Subway, very dark, completely unlit, several council owned lamps attached to the wall of the slope above this path but none of them work. Very unsafe for women like me walking down that slope as its very dark and littered with rubbish and is a public health and safety issue that needs fixing.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8401899.0.jpeg?2f540f44&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Plumstead Road, Plumstead, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401899&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street lighting</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401899</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 03:44:46 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.491092 0.081793</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Driveway needs to be repaired, 11th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401898</link>
<description>The driveway for NO7 has loose / missing bricks in the pavement which causes people to trip, and injure themselves, and in some cases cause some people to rage in pain and sometimes cause damage in retaliation. Along with this, the missing bricks damage my cars tyres as they have to go over misplaced and missing bricks when going into my driveway and cost me a large amount in needing to replace some tyres due to the wear and tear from this issue. I need it fixed as soon as possible and smoothed out like the other 6 driveways have.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Asolando Drive, Walworth, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401898&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Car parking</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401898</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 03:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.490111 -0.093659</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree Leaves falling on parked resident cars making car wash useless., 11th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401896</link>
<description>The Trees in the car park of the ASOLANDO DRIVE compound and the one in the Browning Settlement Garden over extending into the carpark and over No7&amp;#39;s allocated car parking space has almost everyday ended up with dropped leaves falling on my car and making a car wash pointless. I want someone to trim the trees a generous amount to enable myself to get my car washed and not see it covered with leaves the following day and see it without any leaves like the other 6 residents enjoy this luxury.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Asolando Drive, Walworth, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401896&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401896</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 03:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.490131 -0.093588</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Over Parking In the Car Park, entrance difficult to enter sometimes., 11th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401895</link>
<description>When you enter the ASOLANDO DRIVE compound you often have to slow down an agonising amount as one house (near the middle and opposite ben ezra house) tends to have 2/3 cars parked outside their place and not in any allocated parking spots literally two/ three steps down the compound to the carpark. This makes the entrance to the carpark very difficult and often becomes a very risky squeeze when it should in fact be very easy as the car park has a lot of spaces random people often end up leaving their vehicles and not have to worry about getting a ticket. This sort of both side of the pavement parking sometimes encourages random people coming to pick up their kids from the local Robert Browning School to come and leave their cars on the pavements blocking the entrance sometimes for residents. Must be addressed and sorted/ monitored more actively&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Asolando Drive, Walworth, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401895&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Car parking</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401895</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 03:18:59 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.490026 -0.093889</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flytipping, 11th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401893</link>
<description>Massive amounts of flytipping has occurred at this entrance of the ASOLANDO DRIVE compound. This has been the case for the last month and nothing has been done about it including from the local bin man who comes and parks his car in the compound car park and often sleeps in it for long periods of time with his number plate taken off to avoid any tickets even though parking tickets are very rare in this car park hence why there is a lot of random cars being parked here all day and some possibly even empty out their rubbish here and leave.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Asolando Drive, Walworth, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401893&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping - General (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401893</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 03:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.490148 -0.093639</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carpark Lights turn off at 10:15pm - 1:45am, 11th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401891</link>
<description>These are the lights in the ASOLANDO DRIVE compound, and have been doing this for the last two months. The three street lamps directly outside my property were recently repaired by the council, but they are still not functioning properly. They switch off completely at around 10:15pm, then briefly turn back on around 1:45am for about thirty minutes before shutting off again for the rest of the night. Before the clocks changed, they shut off at around 11pm, so the period of darkness has actually increased. Meanwhile, the street lights outside the car park work normally throughout the night. This inconsistent and reduced lighting leaves the area unusually dark for long stretches, creates unnecessary safety risks, and suggests the repair was not completed or configured correctly.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Asolando Drive, Walworth, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401891&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street lighting</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401891</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 02:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.490081 -0.093747</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>No lights on bridge over station, 11th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401825</link>
<description>Since the new bridge at the train station had been built there are no lights on around it at all. It is very dark going up the steps and especially in top. It is impossible to see if anyone else is on the bridge and I several times bumped into other people coming towards me. I also have a deaf friend who has been scared several times whilst crossing&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Whitehall Lane, North End, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401825&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Lamp post</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401825</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 01:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.467299 0.190538</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Litter and rubbish, 11th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401815</link>
<description>It was updated as resolved but it’s not. It’s a consistent issue and there’s certain rubbish on that road that hasn’t moved in months. It not pleasant and nice .&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Thanet Road, North End, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401815&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street cleaning and litter</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401815</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.475154 0.179615</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Smelly road gully, 11th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401804</link>
<description>The gully on the road outside 35 Bristol Gardens has had an extreme sewage smell on and off 3 times in the last 7 days. The smell is so extreme that it affects the nearby properties when the odour comes out. Come and clean it!&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 35, Bristol Gardens, Maida Vale, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401804&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Smelly drain</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401804</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.523186 -0.186737</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Please see below the response from the Grounds Maintenance Team -Hi I have asked for the housing officer for this to be removed to the perimeter of the land which is not the reasonability of Hackney Council Ground Maintenance to maintain., 10th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401774</link>
<description>Please see below the response from the Grounds Maintenance Team -Hi I have asked for the housing officer for this to be removed to the perimeter of the land which is not the reasonability of Hackney Council Ground Maintenance to maintain.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8401774.0.jpeg?aa56e93c&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Reading Lane, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401774&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Maintenance / Repairs Issue</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401774</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 23:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.54474 -0.057235</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dear sir/madam Could you please ask aerial manager &amp; Trowbridge resident association chair member for an update on Osborne Road barrier gate being fixed. Trowbridge resident association chair member advertising no updates, information for a number of years on Trowbridge resident association group websites which this information is outdated and incorrect.Could chair member please give current ETA, update to Osborne Road E9 5JR barrier gate is going to be fixed.Antisocial behaviour at Osborne Road garages,legal parking, no parking enforcement, unauthorized vehicle or hours.Residents with any problems please make contact with your chair member Trowbridge resident association group. To discuss any issues on the estate &amp; antisocial behaviour,crime. You can make contact with your Trowbridge resident association group chair member via website link. Please feel free to contact us with any issues around the estate. Trowbridge Residents Association | Homeowners Association Business https://share.google/V0EetNBq8U8GhGdxR Email: eugene.egan70@gmail.com Phone: 07944759507, 10th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401765</link>
<description>Dear sir/madam&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Could you please ask aerial manager &amp;amp; Trowbridge resident association chair member for an update on Osborne Road barrier gate being fixed. Trowbridge resident association chair member advertising no updates, information for a number of yea&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8401765.0.jpeg?12fa1253&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Hillman Street, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401765&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Maintenance / Repairs Issue</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401765</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 23:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.545357 -0.057651</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>There was a white male Jehovah&#39;s witness standing next to a leaflet stand outside marks and Spencer&#39;s who displays an aggressive behavior and is quite intimidating this is somebody who works with the lord god., 10th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401762</link>
<description>There was a white male Jehovah&amp;#39;s witness standing next to a leaflet stand outside marks and Spencer&amp;#39;s who displays an aggressive behavior and is quite intimidating this is somebody who works with the lord god.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8401762.0.jpeg?214a5e66&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Mare Street, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401762&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Maintenance / Repairs Issue</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401762</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 23:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.547661 -0.055017</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Furniture dumped near bin store, 10th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401718</link>
<description>Furniture items dumped near Archer&amp;#39;s Lodge bin store. Not a coincidence that this keeps happening because the local authority waste disposal teams continue to leave bins outside of the bin stores that encourage illegal waste dumping.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1-8, Culloden Close, Old Kent Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401718&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping - General (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401718</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.485721 -0.065456</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Countdown unit not working., 10th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401681</link>
<description>Countdown unit completely blank.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8401681.0.jpeg?23367ce5&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Sloane Street, Chelsea, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401681&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Countdown - not working</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401681</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.497687 -0.15904</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fly tipped dumped items in alleyway., 10th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401669</link>
<description>Fly tips dump items in alleyway.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8401669.0.jpeg?0620c35b&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Brinkworth Way, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401669&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Illegal Parking</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401669</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.545506 -0.026703</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flooding on road, 10th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401658</link>
<description>Drain must be blocked as there is a large puddle which hasn&amp;#39;t drained away after rain. Thanks for unblocking.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8401658.0.jpeg?ce19e802&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 79, Grange Road, Old Kent Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401658&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401658</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.494596 -0.076185</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Single mattress near park gates, 10th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401641</link>
<description>Single mattress left on pavement&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 50, Wrotham Road, Welling, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401641&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401641</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.46908 0.121011</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Huge amount of Fytipping by Hazel Way, 10th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401639</link>
<description>Huge amount of flytipping next to bins on the top of Hazel Way. Recurring flytipping hot spot, tones of recycling also flytipped as there are no recycling bins in the area. Please clear&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8401639.0.jpeg?bcbc681f&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Alscot Way, Old Kent Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401639&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Posting - General (Estates)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401639</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.492354 -0.076432</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dumped by tenants moving out of #11, 10th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401636</link>
<description>Some metal things… clothing rail &amp;amp; not sure what other bits are… maybe a picture frame??&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8401636.0.jpeg?5cd354e0&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Gould Terrace, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401636&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8401636</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.548116 -0.055283</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>