<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Can this recycling drop off area be emptied please?, 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758784</link>
<description>Please empty this area &amp;amp; the recycling bins&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7758784.0.jpeg?6a40b544&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Magpie Hall Lane, Bromley Common, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758784&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Public Litter Bin</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758784</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 22:15:05 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.382584 0.041416</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dog fouling on Anerley Road, 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758765</link>
<description>I have increasingly noticed dog muck on Anerley Road for the last couple of weeks. I have had to clean dog dirt after opening my gate and stepping into it, and I have repeatedly had to dodge dog dirt on my way on this road. I&amp;#39;ve lived here for 7 years - I appreciate there is going to be dog dirt from time to time, but I would say this is getting increasingly worse.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Anerley Road, Anerley, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758765&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Dog Fouling</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758765</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 22:08:42 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.410739 -0.064766</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Could this sign be fixed and made good?, 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758762</link>
<description>Could this Laburnum Way sign be fixed please?&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7758762.0.jpeg?1bb9f91d&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Laburnum Way, Southborough, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758762&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Sign Missing/Damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758762</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 22:07:19 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.383046 0.059734</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Missed collection, 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758752</link>
<description>Recycling rubbish not collected&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7758752.0.jpeg?403ebc33&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Stoke Newington Church Street, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758752&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758752</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 22:01:05 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.560536 -0.084768</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Churchill Gardens Dry Pond, 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758746</link>
<description>I am writing to express concern that the pond has been allowed to dry out completely. While I understand that recent weather has been unusually hot and dry, it is disappointing that no preventative action appears to have been taken.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The Council should explore practical solutions, such as requesting support from the London Fire Brigade to replenish the water levels. The absence of local ducks and geese underscores the environmental impact of this neglect.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I urge Bromley Council to take immediate steps to preserve our local green spaces and protect the natural wildlife that depends on them.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Tetty Way, Plaistow, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758746&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Park Repairs</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758746</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:58:33 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.403324 0.012948</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Enfield council nd police not addressing dangerous driving, 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758742</link>
<description>Enfield council turned all roads to LTNs then put cycle lanes on green lanes. Consequently the council have increased traffic and traffic speed on hoppers road a thousand fold. Our lives are blighted with speeding of 40 plus mph on a residential road, despite an entirely unmonitored 20 mph. . It is strange which roads have become LTNs. But why are reg council and police ignoring traffic volume and traffic speed on hoppers road.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hoppers Road, Palmers Green, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758742&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758742</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:54:24 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.628591 -0.104034</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>There is becoming a big issue of criminal activity and antisocial behavior on the Trowbridge estate. if someone from the local council could answer these questions and address these issues raised. why is it the local Olympic village silk mill Square and meadow square have had an update of CCTV surveillance cameras connected in partnership with the metropolitan police and Hackney Council while they leave the old Trowbridge estate without any CCTV making it a free-for-all for criminal behavior and displacing the anti-social behavior what took place where the CCTV has been installed but now has been moved to other parts of the estate as a dumping ground. Maybe this is due to Hackney Council not having enough money or just making other residence on the other side of Trowbridge estate suffer in squalo and slums. The metropolitan police commissioner sir Mark Rowley only can afford to stick one camera on the old Trowbridge estate Merriam Ave but metropolitan and Hackney Council stick loads in the Olympic village no common sense displacing antisocial behavior. Hackney Council has taken over the planning authority for the Olympic village in Hackney Wick, including Silk Mill Square, from the London Legacy Development Corporation (LLDC). This transfer began on September 1, 2024, with Hackney Council taking responsibility for decisions on new planning applications. From December 1, 2024, the council will also manage local planning policies and determine planning gain levies. As of December 1, 2024, the planning powers will be transferred from LLDC to Hackney Council, including determining local planning policies and levies on new developments., 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758732</link>
<description>There is becoming a big issue of criminal activity and antisocial behavior on the Trowbridge estate. if someone from the council could answer these questions and address these issues raised. displacing anti-social behavior&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7758732.0.jpeg?811c727c&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Meadow Close, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758732&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758732</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:48:52 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.547361 -0.026643</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>One of the steps by the concrete shard pillar has come loose and poses a serious hazard. This has happened before so clearly not fixed properly., 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758731</link>
<description>Been like this for a few weeks.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): London Bridge, The Borough, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758731&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavement Defect (uneven surface / cracked paving slab)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758731</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:49:10 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.506224 -0.088234</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Prime estate agents advertising sign on the pavement, 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758727</link>
<description>This is a conservation area, but the estate agent Prime Collection has a sign obstructing the pavement outside 18a Hanson St. This is a fairly new sign. The attached photo was taken at 2114hrs, so to aggravate the situation the illegal sign will probably be left there overnight to the detriment of the disabled, the partially sighted and wheelchair users. The rubbish is also a problem, but the sign is more important.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7758727.0.jpeg?0f4cc5a8&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 17, Hanson Street, Fitzrovia, Camden Town, City of Westminster&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758727&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Signs and bollards</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758727</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:46:20 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.51992 -0.140432</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pavement around tree pits risen and serious trip hazard, 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758721</link>
<description>On Lynton Road, especially from the Red sweet shop up to the junction where City of London School is, there are several trees where the pavement has risen, causing serious trip hazards. There is also not enough room between the trees and the gates for wheelchairs and buggy’s to get past, forcing people to walk in the dangerous road with their buggies. I have reported this several times over the last 2 years but nothing has been done and the situation has just got worse so this is the final straw before I make a formal complaint to the head of the council. I live on Bermondsey Street and I walk through to Southwark Park Road every morning along the same route and I have done for over 2 years and I think the streets have just got worse. I actually find myself wondering if the streets of Bermondsey are ever inspected for faults as there seem to be a lot of them. I don’t know what the process is but it’s clearly not working.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Lynton Road, Old Kent Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758721&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/footpaths</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758721</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:42:45 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.489756 -0.068718</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>3 inch hole on the sidewalk, getting bigger, 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758714</link>
<description>3 inch hole on the sidewalk, getting bigger&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7758714.0.jpeg?df685340&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 5, Foyle Road, East Greenwich, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758714&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/Footpaths Repairs</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758714</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:40:25 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.48238 0.010769</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Overgrown bushes outside 173 Lynton Road making people walk into the road, 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758696</link>
<description>This has been like this for a few months now and the situation is only getting worse. The bushes are so overgrown they are spilling out onto the pavement and I had to push my buggy into the road today in order to get past. Additionally, the state of the pavements in the area are very bad.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Lynton Road, Old Kent Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758696&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/footpaths</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758696</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:33:07 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.489593 -0.06728</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rubbish left on street for weeks, 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758688</link>
<description>This has been like this for over on month&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7758688.0.jpeg?6810f3d6&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 95, Green Lanes, Bowes, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758688&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Rubbish (refuse and recycling)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758688</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:31:04 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.610809 -0.109705</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>So much rubbish all down the street, 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758682</link>
<description>Rubbish all down street overflowing bins everywhere&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7758682.0.jpeg?1a6f973d&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 95, Green Lanes, Bowes, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758682&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Rubbish (refuse and recycling)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758682</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:30:02 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.610809 -0.109705</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Open manhole H&amp;S ISSUE, 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758681</link>
<description>Health and safety hazard of manhole open and left, anyone can fall down it or trip on it it’s on the grass between the block of flats at 129-135 Mottisfont Road and the House on the corner of church manor way rats have been seen climbing in and out&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7758681.0.jpeg?6c42007b&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Mottisfont Road, Abbey Wood, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758681&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Blocked Roadside Gully</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758681</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:28:51 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.49112 0.102829</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pole has been knocked over leaving stub, 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758649</link>
<description>Trip hazard - I caught my foot as walking along. Base of pole Needs to be removed&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7758649.0.jpeg?6c7856a5&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 161, High Street, Beckenham, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758649&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Public Right of Way footpath</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758649</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:16:32 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.406536 -0.029064</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Household items outside of block, 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758643</link>
<description>These items have been here since last week and it looks like people have begun smashing the items across the floor making it dangerous for other residents.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7758643.0.jpeg?25360444&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Leatherhead Close, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758643&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758643</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:14:40 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.568594 -0.076069</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Water coming from back of shop, 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758634</link>
<description>Water is coming from the back of this shops aircon or ventilation system, the water sheds across the footpath which seems to encourage algae, and then flows into the gutter. Other than being very unpleasant this presents a hazard for pedestrians.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7758634.0.jpeg?ec09408e&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Dalton Street, West Norwood, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758634&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/footpaths</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758634</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:11:56 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.435682 -0.103756</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fly tipping Pellerin Rd, 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758631</link>
<description>Hello Hackney We need your help in collecting this fly tipping waste. It arrived last week and was dumped on the road. For safety, I moved it from off the road and onto the pavement and into my neighbour’s front garden.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7758631.0.jpeg?0c904852&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Pellerin Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758631&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758631</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:10:44 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.551852 -0.076094</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flytip outside 44 and in bins of 42, 24th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758621</link>
<description>Junk on pavement and bins including recycling bin stuffed with black bags etc by the usual tossers&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7758621.0.jpeg?55a71a28&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Banyard Road, Bermondsey, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758621&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping - General (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7758621</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:05:36 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.494436 -0.058782</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>