<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>212 Edington Road: white goods; suitcase and duvet., 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473736</link>
<description>White goods on grass verge, suitcase and duvet near to recycling bin next to flats.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Edington Road, Abbey Wood&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473736&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473736</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.49366 0.115651</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>No wedding and see this crazy to add here!, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473734</link>
<description>Missing drained ones next to Tesco! Has been as follow as sen at HoC; Be polite Use exact locations Say how long the issue’s been present ( if local you can find it easy and if care with degree into this with social policy subject as many more to do this Jos at at top not AsD! As we had debates at uni then at work so never used false information or gossips as per request here and all details from life experiences and books too plus advises as well; Don’t identify or accuse other people Don’t include private contact details in the description&amp;#10;&amp;#10;STAGNATION and now flower baskets too also do not post repairs regarding some street miles away from that street on the floor but post to local and not on later too!&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Marine Street, Bermondsey, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473734&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/footpaths</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473734</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.49818 -0.069188</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>100 Eynsham Drive: heap of rubbish., 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473731</link>
<description>Rubbish over payment.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Eynsham Drive, Abbey Wood&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473731&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473731</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.494995 0.113952</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree branch ready to fall off, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473726</link>
<description>The pathway between Alford road and sandcliff road has a tree with broken branches which could fall onto someone , I&amp;#39;ve managed to move one but there&amp;#39;s another big branch very lose that needs to be cut back&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473726.0.jpeg?252f67ba&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Friday Road, Northumberland Heath, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473726&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473726</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:19:47 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.483639 0.167385</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rubbish still not cleared, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473722</link>
<description>Previous report of rubbish piled up in the street was closed and marked as fixed, it has NOT been fixed! The pile of rubbish is now blowing all over the street, being torn apart by rats and foxes.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473722.0.jpeg?cbe0c9cc&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Cerise Road, Peckham, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473722&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping - General (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473722</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.471838 -0.068174</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fallon over sign, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473706</link>
<description>On Harrow Road near Great Western Road Road works sign fallon over trip hazard&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473706.0.jpeg?da333f33&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 504-506, Harrow Road, Kensal Town, City of Westminster&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473706&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Signs and bollards</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473706</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.524913 -0.202635</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fallon over sign, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473705</link>
<description>On Harrow Road near Great Western Road Road works sign fallon over trip hazard&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473705.0.jpeg?da333f33&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 504-506, Harrow Road, Kensal Town, City of Westminster&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473705&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Signs and bollards</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473705</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.524913 -0.202635</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potencial ( correct spelling why in red? ) car park area!, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473702</link>
<description>Block off land for builder by new houses not filled up as area with nothing special and OMG businesses in it with fire hazards and awful windows! Some resting ones should be after lease removed as just date of space with crap and closed ones! Rent for free and here you go! Where we meant to work or rent places for new business which will pay taxes for local communities and small businesses! Chineses done so many of it and then boom we cannot afford this as benefits if we want or not with zero input into it and all for free! Think! Look at size of it and walk during night! Some move so let us as that nice building to managed as I won&amp;#39;t go there! Tacky with awful attitude and I don&amp;#39;t have one as not your business and you have to many to look after! Results here we go!&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Leather Place, Old Kent Road, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473702&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Parks/landscapes</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473702</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.494486 -0.079262</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Mirror - now broken - dumped outside property, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473694</link>
<description>Broken glass and frame moved to forecourt of 19 Shortlands Grove to avoid accidents.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Shortlands Grove, Shortlands, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473694&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytip</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473694</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.402903 -0.006561</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Outside 153 Granville Road NW6 5AR, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473678</link>
<description>Large White Wardrobe along with other Things. Wardrobe NEEDS MOVING ASAP. Has a Mirror on.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473678.0.jpeg?ecb63e20&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Granville Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473678&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly-tip Large - More than a van load</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473678</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.533008 -0.195522</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Office rubbish dumped on the street (cardboard boxes), piling for days., 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473668</link>
<description>Office rubbish dumped on the street (cardboard boxes), piling for days. Not in any rubbish bags, so will never be collected. This is already the second instance I have had to report it recently; it seems the office is not aware of how to properly dispose of the rubbish.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473668.0.jpeg?fefad1b7&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 38, Grosvenor Gardens, Victoria, City of Westminster&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473668&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473668</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.496601 -0.146148</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Broken old sofas flytipped, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473667</link>
<description>Sofas dumped on pennethorne road not too far from junction with goldsmith road&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473667.0.jpeg?c84916c3&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Pennethorne Road, Peckham, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473667&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping - General (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473667</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.476187 -0.063927</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>White metal poles/hanging rail, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473665</link>
<description>Left outside number 86 - rubbish consistently left outside this property&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 82, Talfourd Road, Peckham, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473665&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping - General (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473665</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.471052 -0.077482</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Wow, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473662</link>
<description>As in old days fine to all and scan all if pays or not as now this one so well. If not paid more than and n/a inquiry then why and fair decision so on! Old houses either to replace by new and like for like if wanted for local ones only as priority as happens to me and was declined! Budget solution or help with tickets if over 1.30 min as legal only 1hr! Or map with better links! Bins next to balconies is this legal please and who gave permission? Fake courts and Croydon by some and why? cannot add or scan or read pass to boss as not on envelope for you too! More friendly attitude and listen and sent to all what you want to do before not after! Check council estates as so many empty with 0 to pay for taxes and waste as seen 2/3 at some near by area empty and build up as crazy for example by as per map as awful and seen rats and windows almost rotten and to many empty car spots and battle in other places for it! Crimscott Street ( forgot place to clean) and as you see street nit added and in red again then mistakes as correct! Tell me why local one? Some business left as all mess around too! has been for years! Bill up in sick projects opposite council on yards and places to park! We had the in Glasgow so no thanks! Hazel/Curtis Way a nightmare! New roads against people will and grammar mistakes! Pay for ir and get private for this mess and become middle class as you wish!&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 61, Willow Walk, Old Kent Road, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473662&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473662</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.494326 -0.079198</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street light not working at all, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473643</link>
<description>No light from this lamppost&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473643.0.jpeg?4a463171&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 29, Kinnerton Street, Belgravia, City of Westminster&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473643&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street lights</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473643</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.500026 -0.156821</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Human forest bikes, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473639</link>
<description>There are human forest bikes blocking pavement and cycle stand outside slip slow coffee shop. The bikes need to be removed&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473639.0.jpeg?68a89ebd&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 26-46, Lisson Grove, Marylebone, City of Westminster&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473639&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned HumanForest bike</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473639</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.522337 -0.165182</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Missing manhole cover o/s 1 Callendar Rd nr Talbot Place, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473628</link>
<description>Missing manhole cover o/s 1 Callendar Rd nr Talbot Place on footway - caller has moved cover back this is very loose still and could be a trip hazard&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Callender Road, North End, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473628&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other street defect</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473628</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.472204 0.17998</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Overflowing bin by canal, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473608</link>
<description>Park bin overflowing with dog poo bags&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Lea Bridge Road, Leyton&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473608&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Overflowing Public Litter Bin</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473608</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.563112 -0.047638</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Issue, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473590</link>
<description>You can walk in out with no problem , I mean toilet and interviews by main windows as so many rooms empty! Bins food wastage a good idea but we use brown ones not grey this why most dumped stickers out! Only in our side of house 1-47 PS. se16? Pilot program again? As mentioned boring and not safe so renting ones from City or Canary W. as dirty and tenants left further away. No new residents as many empty buildings and not most prefer not to stay here and some here not welcoming too to many! IT system to be checked as had to use this way as many either do not work or blocked off or later as my applications and no proper staff according to governments acts with %! Many empty communal sites no to new ones as most empty! Waste of public money and 4/5 next to each others? NO! Grown up as it is modern society! get use to it!&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 160, Tooley Street, The Borough, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473590&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Public toilets</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473590</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.503096 -0.080775</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>In front of 145 Granville Road NW6 5AR, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473578</link>
<description>The Lady is Like my Beloved Mum Elderly. These Dog Walkers RELENTLESSLY Make there Dogs FOUL in front of Residents homes on Granville Road.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Please CLEAR THIS Dog Mess in front of 145 Granville Road. The Resident is a Wheelchair Lady.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;They are NOT CLEANING UP after there Dogs. Dogs MESS is DISGUSTING, DIRTY, UNHEALTHY and can CAUSE ILLNESS. Elderly Residents and Children have to walk along Granville Road and ENDURE THIS PROBLEM DAY IN and DAY OUT.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;There is also a Nursery School and Children and there Parents have to walk along Granville Road. I have REQUESTED STOP FOULING and CLEAN UP AFTER YOUR DOG SiGNS in front of 145, 147 and 149 as this is A DOG WALKERS PARADISE.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;No one is Listening to me. I have CLEANED MANY A DOG MESS and it’s HORRENDOUS. I CARE about The Road I live and it’s NOT FAIR Elderly Residents have to ENDURE this .&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473578.0.jpeg?c3b5eed4&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Granville Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473578&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street cleaning - Dog mess</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473578</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.533008 -0.195522</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>