<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Well we need to look into it when rains!, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473541</link>
<description>As sent before to council a lots of photos and this was ignored decided to write again as was not passed higher up so this why! When rains this part of pavement looks like little pond with water up to 1st brick and new drained ones done above level of pavements bricks in zone where not needed too by bust stop just 50 yards down. Also same problem on Thurland Road where all to hight to work well and when wet big area under water too. We need experts to do audits and sign this off as seen many road done and then in a week or two again new road has been open up why we can do it better! Waste of money! 14 days to reply it is 14 days! Also window by to main building has old display too. Meeting A nobody in even with those who created post and to D many not even hello by young girl! Security could check better and better knowledge by reception too over the phone and taking responsibilities for your mistakes as we all do! Some emails took 2 years to reply and where that benefits or fair job for disable if to difficult for some pass to those with degrees or fair panel not 1 against 2! I have 6 years to go to proper court not kids one as a lots of nepotism across and braking law in gov. institutions too as not mine don&amp;#39;t care and worst of catholic too and single and not for many! Disable must means interview must be provided! Key words used form job description and heard of this many times tow at last few institutions as unfair way of employing! Some offer to some job for entry level not for someone with uni into it and lots of experiences doing this for years so think of it and pay for mistakes and don&amp;#39;t higher your fiends pretending to be other companies online! Some even tried to be me to apply what it is for me and found this by lack in September to fake websites to as provided. I Know what I wanted to do and with whom and please don&amp;#39;t copy and paste someone else knowledge too or hack so won&amp;#39;t get job. Many more but now pay from soon for next one to1056 and0&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Jamaica Road, Bermondsey, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473541&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/footpaths</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473541</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.497787 -0.065616</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Please add end lines to double red lines, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473530</link>
<description>I think the end lines are missing in this area for the double red lines (circled) at pedestrian crossing points, as in the example in Westminster (circled in green)?&amp;#10;&amp;#10;There may be other crossings in the vicinity missing the end lines too.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Thanks&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473530.0.jpeg?5e9f2322&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Clapham High Street, Clapham, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473530&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473530</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.461741 -0.137861</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Gradually items appearing in an abandoned supermarket trolley, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473528</link>
<description>Hilldrop road /Brecknock road side Lots of junk appearing outside the portacabins this last 2 weeks, and an abandoned supermarket trolley and today 2 full bin bags Not an official collection site for rubbish.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473528.0.jpeg?566cc45f&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hilldrop Road, Holloway, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473528&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473528</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.551809 -0.131408</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bin full, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473508</link>
<description>This bin needs regular emptying and now people are putting household waste here. You should go through it and get their address and fine them.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;There is enough room in this bin for genuine waste, without selfish people making it worse.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Thanks&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473508.0.jpeg?8948e001&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Daly Drive, Bickley, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473508&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Public Litter Bin</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473508</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.399709 0.0611</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Incorrect paving slab used here, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473503</link>
<description>Opposite 22 The Pavement, London SW4 0HY. The inlaid paving slab marking the start of the segregated cycle path here (circled in red) is the incorrect one, as it is showing &amp;quot;mixed use&amp;quot;. It should be the cycle only slab, as shown in the example attached. Thanks&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473503.0.jpeg?d7fa5f98&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 21, The Pavement, Clapham, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473503&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473503</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.46204 -0.140247</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Better use of public buildings!, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473473</link>
<description>As a member of public we need ti think ahead in case as seen as was on sick leave for a while a lots of government business used partly as for example this Job Centre which I think have potential as a lot of facilities to use as main hub for trainings, as small place for general meetings where ideas can be passed further to levels up and also be a bit more friendly to disable customers as 3 floors and a bit of hassle as not ramp or lift as other ones having one floor so easy to use. Lots of not used back rooms for some who prefer 1-2- 1 service so on as we can imagine! Also better usage of internet boxes on street as good idea when works! Free internet zone in this place with supervision no for TV place or private emails with qualified staff across each floor and Director with manager so on with adequate experiences and training, will too! Listen and be professional to what matters to Jon seekers but be realistic too! Fraud and solutions including benefits solve faster and talk to residents and be fair to them as seen a lots including no empathy at all with attitude me me me me and they lie! This is politics but we must play fair after all and be in 21 century aware of current law and do not be discriminated against any of acts against anyone after all! View of some oldest companies changes too and this is massage form top to all of us. Some therapies can be provided too as training as well.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Newington Causeway, Elephant and Castle, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473473&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Car parking</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473473</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.497466 -0.098446</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Graffiti, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473453</link>
<description>On grey box at east end of petrol station.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473453.0.jpeg?25017f7a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Theobald Street, Walworth, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473453&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti - General (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473453</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.494321 -0.090393</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hedge growing into pavement, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473428</link>
<description>Hedge needs cutting and is beginning to block the pavement. For wheelchairs the slope the other side of the post box is difficult and narrow.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473428.0.jpeg?7a88248c&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Lugard Road, Peckham, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473428&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/footpaths</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473428</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.472155 -0.057919</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Try to walk there over night!, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473404</link>
<description>This forgotten part overgrown with bushes and poor old lighting too! Love it anyway! Its like Narnia walking different zone like near church to Turguand Street se17 where Chaplin was baptised, two different worlds when pass so a lot missing historical signs which as per previous one can brig a lots of attention to new build up area with new shops and other fun places for kids and adults as we forgot about youngest ones a lots where new build up huge compacts are build top and under bridges or in a left spots hey can be created with time. Also St. James school could be reduced to half size and church yard used as should be during day not night for storage activities as heard off or where bones are placed too as we can create near pun little square for adults near subway then kids, teen area near school then new school two with entrance from Main Street and bins moved from view of Prospect House se16 too. Lots of money can be used for renovations of churches or antics which can bring new tenets as artist and usage for under bridges spaces too. Also dislike idea of church used as houses or place for fun as at Clements Road as this is horrible idea and part used behind just waste! Hopefully new pedestrian as last bit missing would be open by the King as in that part in 70s for Jubilee by late Queen EII and few places opened too so we must clear a lots before all this happens. All this might bring new business into area as we cannot build up and do not think of smallest details but so important to us residents and new ones as to get more of those with pennies we must do extra mile after all and competition is huge as for example ex Battersea Power Station or Vauxhall too. A lot of empty building like ex Barclays at corner of Grange Road/Tower Bridge Rd next to late toilets. Also ex NatWest building on same street closer to Tower Bridge too. Easy to start from nine zone then it is bit more difficult to manage and DPR please as some tried to use my ideas too! GDPR.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Old Kent Road, Old Kent Road, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473404&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/footpaths</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473404</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.491374 -0.080507</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Grafiti under Bellenden railway bridge needs to be removed, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473403</link>
<description>2 Grafitis under Bellenden railway bridge needs to be removed.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473403.0.jpeg?9a7405ac&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 89, Bellenden Road, Peckham, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473403&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti - General (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473403</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.469041 -0.072656</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tarmac not repaired from drop drive, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473392</link>
<description>Jet have just finished doing gas piping o/s my drive and a part from run in has been left unrepaired.their lorry caused the damage.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Stratton Road, Blendon, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473392&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Damaged road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473392</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.460971 0.134316</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pavement remains unrepaired, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473380</link>
<description>The pavement was dug up by one of the &amp;#39;services&amp;#39; and remains unrepaired possibly a year later. There&amp;#39;s another one just 50 meters down the road.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473380.0.jpeg?2e869606&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 67, Gordon Road, Peckham, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473380&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/footpaths</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473380</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.46942 -0.061025</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Corner of hermit place and kilburn vale, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473359</link>
<description>Newly laid cobblestone path has a decline and is gathering water is a slip hazard, near priory tavern pub&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hermit Place, Kilburn, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473359&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavement Defect</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473359</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.538464 -0.191539</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Waste in subway, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473329</link>
<description>Since This morning&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473329.0.jpeg?2f10be52&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Rampayne Street, Millbank, City of Westminster&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473329&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Litter</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473329</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.490065 -0.13285</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Broken post, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473325</link>
<description>Post coming out of pavement.dangerous&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473325.0.jpeg?6472d3e9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Wellfit Street, Loughborough Junction, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473325&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/footpaths</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473325</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.464699 -0.101611</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dog fouling on Albion Rd N15, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473323</link>
<description>Dog pooon pavement outside 57 Albion road&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473323.0.jpeg?f461af64&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Albion Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473323&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473323</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.554032 -0.08474</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lights not working, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473321</link>
<description>Lights on path leading from ethelbert close to glassmill lane or not working and after 4pm it very scary to use the path especially as I am a woman. Please repair urgently. Thank you&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Mill Vale, Shortlands, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473321&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Light Not Working</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473321</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.403144 0.010973</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bike advertising, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473319</link>
<description>They always advertise on the is bike&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473319.0.jpeg?f44ce66d&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Sloane Avenue, Chelsea, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473319&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flyposting</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473319</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.491074 -0.162949</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flytipping, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473318</link>
<description>Since This morning&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8473318.0.jpeg?7bf4a4c9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Rampayne Street, Millbank, City of Westminster&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473318&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473318</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.490065 -0.13285</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Build up of leaves on pavement and gully causing risk to pedestriansBuild up of leaves on pavement and gully causing risk to pedestrians, 27th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473317</link>
<description>Build up of leaves on pavement and gully causing risk to pedestrians&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Forty Hill, Enfield, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473317&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/footpaths</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8473317</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.66684 -0.071999</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>