<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Road works! Temporary lights! Road blocks! water stop!, 7th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8638132</link>
<description>The ongoing roadworks across the borough, which have now been continuing for over a year and are causing unacceptable disruption to daily life. While the situation was already bad, the works that began yesterday have made travel completely unreasonable. A journey that normally takes 10–15 minutes — travelling by bus from Edmonton Green to Enfield College — took 1 hour and 30 minutes yesterday and an extraordinary 3 hours and 45 minutes today. Under normal circumstances, I would have walked most of this journey rather than remain on a bus for hours. However, due to the icy pavement conditions, walking was not a viable option, leaving me with no choice but to stay on the bus throughout the delays. Despite this, the bus was eventually terminated at Tesco, at which point I had no option but to walk the remainder of the journey anyway. The condition and management of these roadworks demonstrate a serious lack of consideration for residents. Traffic congestion is extreme, bus routes are unreliable, and there appears to be little to no effective traffic management in place. People still need to get to work, college, appointments, and home, yet these roadworks are making everyday journeys unnecessarily stressful and time-consuming. Residents are paying the price for what feels like poor planning, poor coordination, and a failure to properly manage the impact of these works. This level of disruption is simply unacceptable. Additionally, as a result of these roadworks, my water supply was cut on the 30th at approximately 12:30am without any prior warning, causing further disruption and highlighting the lack of communication and consideration shown to residents.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): High Street, Ponders End, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8638132&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Road works</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8638132</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 02:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.64353 -0.046666</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Blocked drainage pipes, 7th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8638123</link>
<description>All the drainage pipes are blocked in this area causing flooding several inches deep covering the entire area outside the housing whenever it rains. Since the area is where the walkway ends so both cars and people use it too access houses,bus stops etc it can be rather difficult to get around the flooded area&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Crayford Road, Barnes Cray, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8638123&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Blocked rainwater gulleys</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8638123</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.449208 0.188566</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Request a traffic volume assessment., 7th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8638120</link>
<description>Hi,&amp;#10;&amp;#10;There has been a large up tick in learner drivers over the past few months, often you see cars back to back from multiple companies. It appears this residential road is now some kind of DVLA route? Is there any controls that can be put in place, it&amp;#39;s drastically increased traffic, which is pretty unfair for local residents.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Thanks,&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Ronalds Road, Plaistow, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8638120&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Obstruction to Highway</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8638120</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:19:16 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.410339 0.015524</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street lighting out, 6th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637995</link>
<description>The light from the lamp post is out. leaving the section of the road very dark and potential hazard due to poor visibility.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Woodside Road, Barnehurst, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637995&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Lamp post</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637995</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.45542 0.168205</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Huge 12 inch+ pot hole, 6th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637993</link>
<description>There is a huge pot hole which is impossible to see in the dark. The car physically shook when I hit it - I will need to check for damage in daylight. There was a previous report early December - I am not sure if it is the same one. If it is, it needs fixed urgently!&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Elmstead Lane, Elmstead, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637993&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Road Defect</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637993</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.414923 0.045919</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Our bins and communal area is a hotspot for dumping rubbish, 6th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637992</link>
<description>Our flat bins and communal area is a hotspot for dumping rubbish most local neigbours and fly tippers are the issue and yet the council refuse to resolve this on going issue leaving foxes amd rats to infest our area&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Sigdon Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637992&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Overflowing bin</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637992</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.549251 -0.062296</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Car with no MOT registered as SORN parked on public road outside Penfold House, 6th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637991</link>
<description>Parked outside 13-18 penfold house entrance on the barnfield estate, someone is parking a SORN car on the public road. They have covered it with a large sheet to conveniently hide the plates. Photo taken 4th January 2026&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8637991.0.jpeg?134cc38b&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Wrottesley Road, Plumstead&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637991&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637991</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.479404 0.072003</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Blocking entry, 6th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637990</link>
<description>After emptying bins, workers left cardboards blocking the path and bike storage. Please remove and make sure it won’t happen again.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8637990.0.jpeg?4c4677f3&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Victoria Park Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637990&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping on Street</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637990</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.537073 -0.048126</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street lamp flickers, intermittently on, 6th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637924</link>
<description>The lamp keeps going off, then coming back on, on, off, on ,off all night. Hard to sleep through&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8637924.0.jpeg?1b39a87a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Station Road, Penge, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637924&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Light Not Working</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637924</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.419853 -0.055231</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Next to parking suspension near no 49 ish., 6th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637915</link>
<description>Works on Arlington Road don’t have safe pedestrian diversion routes. Pavement closed. No ramps. No pedestrian alternatives.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 31, Arlington Road, Chalk Farm, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637915&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roadworks</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637915</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.53561 -0.141462</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Brown settee littered on Harrier Mews Thamesmead pavement., 6th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637911</link>
<description>As you come into Harrier Mews SE28 0DQ from Goldfinch Road, as you drive into the road, look to your right on the pavement, you will see a pile of dark brown sofa set placed on the pavement. This blights the road and saddens and depresses me a lot to see all these household waste being dumped under the cover of night by local residents. The fact that they do it at night to conceal their identity is clear evidence that these people know it is a crime to fly tip. Please can you investigate the two cases reported tonight and have the nuisance items dumped on our pavements removed. Thank you.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Merganser Gardens, Thamesmead&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637911&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637911</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.495142 0.086255</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fly tipping on corner of conduit road, 6th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637907</link>
<description>Photo taken 6th January 2026&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8637907.0.jpeg?e2860091&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Buttmarsh Close, Plumstead&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637907&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637907</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.486209 0.071664</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Glass panel dumped on public pavement, 6th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637903</link>
<description>A glass panel has been left at a common spot for fly tipping at the function of Frederick Place and Burrage Road. Photo taken 6th January 2026.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8637903.0.jpeg?33bc7aac&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Frederick Place, Plumstead&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637903&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637903</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:27:20 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.485117 0.072956</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Massive amounts of domestic waste dumped outside 19 Wrottesley Road, 6th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637891</link>
<description>Looks like someone from the HMO on 19 Wrottesley Road has left a huge amount of domestic tat on the public pavement. Photo taken 6th January 2026 when this first appeared.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8637891.0.jpeg?1081e04b&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Wrottesley Road, Plumstead&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637891&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637891</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.480507 0.072776</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Household items left on the pedestrian pavement in front of number 35 Harrier Mews Thamesmead London SE28 0DQ, 6th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637888</link>
<description>The lady living at number 35 Harrier Mews Thamesmead London SE28 0DQ brought the items pictured in the photo attached out of her house on 30/12/2025 and placed them on the public pavement. This not only blights the street, it also prevents wheelchair and pushchairs from free access to the pavement. This lady frequently fly tips items onto the pavement knowing that these household waste will not be collected by the refuse team. This behaviour can’t continue, we are constantly trying to keep up with all these people causing a nuisance by tipping their rubbish everywhere without consideration for the rest of us. It’s just not fair. This lady has an estate car but instead of going to the recycling centre like the rest of us, she chooses to litter the street with her waste. Please kindly address this problem as soon as possible. Thank you.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8637888.0.jpeg?d225e783&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Harrier Mews, Thamesmead&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637888&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637888</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.496115 0.086303</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>LC 1/3 not working, 6th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637868</link>
<description>LC 1/3 not working&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8637868.0.jpeg?2a004d42&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Dukes Orchard, Coldblow, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637868&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Lamp post</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637868</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:13:36 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.438382 0.159742</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street light not working, 6th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637852</link>
<description>Street light not working&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 30, Broom Avenue, St Paul&#39;s Cray, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637852&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Light Not Working</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637852</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.405091 0.109315</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dumped tumble dryer and other household items, 6th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637831</link>
<description>It’s blocking the pathway and the bins to the flats. They have been put against the bins of 26 Hazel walk of people it doesn’t belong to. Making it difficult for us to access and use our own bin sheds.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8637831.0.jpeg?86466ea4&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hazel Walk, Southborough, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637831&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytip</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637831</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.384606 0.058352</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rosendale Road SE21 Lairdale Estate – southern vehicle, 6th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637792</link>
<description>Rosendale Road SE21 Lairdale Estate – southern vehicle entrance ie Lairdale Close – green box tagged – box would seem to be control box for the new Lambeth car chargers which are out of view on the left hand side. . Please forward fixmystreet.com link to your contractor for reporting pin, picture and Google Streetview link (which does not show box as so new): https://www.google.com/maps/@51.4452464,-0.0983916,3a,48.9y,310.12h,85.45t/data=!3m7!1e1!3m5!1sUqJN2JyYFGJwnbUzOUb4Ew!2e0!6shttps:%2F%2Fstreetviewpixels-pa.googleapis.com%2Fv1%2Fthumbnail%3Fcb_client%3Dmaps_sv.tactile%26w%3D900%26h%3D600%26pitch%3D4.550033147754704%26panoid%3DUqJN2JyYFGJwnbUzOUb4Ew%26yaw%3D310.1199527727562!7i16384!8i8192?authuser=0&amp;amp;entry=ttu&amp;amp;g_ep=EgoyMDI1MTIwOS4wIKXMDSoKLDEwMDc5MjA2N0gBUAM%3D&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8637792.0.jpeg?f623f444&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Rosendale Road, Tulse Hill, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637792&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637792</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.445295 -0.09858</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bag of abandoned clothes, 6th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637789</link>
<description>Been there a week&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8637789.0.jpeg?6597a820&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Royal Oak Road, Barnehurst, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637789&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Carriageway</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8637789</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.455596 0.142523</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>