<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Pavement and foot pave broken and drains are blocked so rain water and waste water from shop will be collected and accumulated and create rain/dirty waterpods, 2nd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105967</link>
<description>The pavement and foot pave has been broken for a few years, basically starting from the street corner all the way up to around number 8. The drains on the street are also blocked so whenever it rains the street would collect and accumulate rain water plus KFC chicken leaks lots of dirty water outside on the street to contribute the situation. The street becomes dirty waterpods and it takes days of hot weather to dry out. If not the dirty waterpods will be there for months, and even icy in winter. It’s dirty and smelly and that makes half of the street on this side to be often wet and smell bad with lots of insects flying around. This has been going on for years and have been reported a couple of times before.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8105967.0.jpeg?ab308463&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 2, Chatsworth Way, West Norwood, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105967&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/footpaths</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105967</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 05:16:33 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.435482 -0.103643</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dead fox on lordship lane se22 a2216, 2nd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105966</link>
<description>DEAD FOX ON LORDSHIP LANE SE22 A2216. near east dulwich grove&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Lordship Lane, East Dulwich, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105966&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Clinical Waste - Dead Animal (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105966</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 05:05:25 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.460432 -0.075308</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Broken fence in the communal yard, 2nd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105965</link>
<description>The fence in the communal yard has been broken for several years, ever since a tree fell on it. The damage has left the area untidy and prevents residents from being able to use the yard properly, including for drying laundry.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8105965.0.jpeg?848db351&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Densole Close, Penge, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105965&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree Requires Pruning</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105965</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 04:53:27 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.412092 -0.043239</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Neighbour&#39;s tree branches encroaching into my garden and damaging my grass, 2nd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105959</link>
<description>I am writing to formally report persistent antisocial behaviour by my neighbour at 244 Crayford Way, DA1 4LR, which has been causing significant disruption and distress to myself and other residents in the area. I live at 242 Crayford Way, and over the past several months, there has been a noticeable decline in the quality of life for those of us living nearby due to the actions and neglect of the resident at number 244. Despite repeated attempts to resolve matters amicably through direct conversation, the issues have continued and worsened. Key concerns include: 1. Neglect of Trees and Garden Encroachment Several years ago, the neighbour&amp;#39;s tree began to overgrow into my garden. The accumulation of dead leaves has severely damaged my lawn and turned my garden into what now resembles a dumping ground. Despite speaking to him on more than one occasion and requesting he cut back the branches, no action has been taken.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I respectfully request that the council investigate these ongoing issues as a matter of urgency. In particular, I would ask that you: • Enforce the responsibility to maintain private trees that encroach onto neighbouring properties&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Crayford Way, Barnes Cray, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105959&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Private property</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105959</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 04:16:53 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.45489 0.193314</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Litter Bin placed in front of private residential building and gardens-it has to be Removed from the site, 2nd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105957</link>
<description>A few days ago a new Litter Bin was placed on the pavement of 28 Quebec Way and right in front of the garden space of Claremont House, a private property. This litter bin attracts daily loads of garbage that often end up thrown either in the nearby private flower beds or spread all over the pavement, creating many mobility and hygiene problems to residents, kids and staff from the nearby nursery operating on the ground floor of Claremont House, as well as to passers-by. For aesthetic and more importantly for material Health &amp;amp; Safety reasons this litter bin should not be placed in any space in front or next to the Claremont House building site and associated garden space. It has to be removed from this particular site. There are at least 2 litter bins in Quebec Way, one at the beginning of the street and another one at the other far end, therefore the specific litter bin in front of Claremont House is not necessary and certainly its current position is inappropriate. If the Council still want to install a 3rd bin, they can place it either on the opposite pavement opposite to Claremont House, or on any other pavement space in Quebec Way street before or after Claremont House, but certainly not in front of Claremont House building. I&amp;#39;d appreciate if the Council service remove this litter bin completely from this area.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8105957.0.jpeg?a5b5e9a7&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 28, Quebec Way, Rotherhithe, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105957&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Litter Bin - Move or Remove</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105957</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 03:51:53 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.498749 -0.042469</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dumped headboard, 2nd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105938</link>
<description>Dumped headboard side of WESTBERE house in alleyway&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8105938.0.jpeg?24ff4c0b&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 193, High Street, Poverest, Orpington, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105938&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytip</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105938</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:29:35 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.388302 0.114611</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Numerous damaged areas on both sides of the road, 2nd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105918</link>
<description>I complained on 27/09/2024 and 3 days later was advised areas had been inspected and nothing identified as needing to be dealt with. Both sides are in an appalling condition, worse than a year ago, and it’s safer to walk in the road than negotiate the so called pavement, especially if you are elderly or disabled. A small area has recently been marked out as due to be repaired as an elderly neighbour fell and injured himself. (A separate report by another resident has been filed). Why only that small area? These arrows should be extended to either end both sides as, quite honestly, this fall could have occurred anywhere along the road. I extend an invitation to a highways inspector to make arrangements with me to walk along the length of the road both sides and to tell me where he/she doesn’t think the surfaces need to be urgently dealt with. Thank you. NB There are too many photos to add as examples&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Blenheim Drive, Falconwood, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105918&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Damaged pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105918</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:24:37 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.46955 0.095633</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Speed bump causing structural damage to my house, 2nd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105916</link>
<description>There is a speed hump outside my house at 37 Melford Road, and when large vehicles go over this, the house vibrates. We have been living here 5 years now and have noticed multiple cracks on walls and brickwork, which will need repairing. These houses have extremely shallow foundations, and the vibrations from large vehicles such as buses and lorries going over the speed hump are seriously damaging the house. It does not help that the street has a constant flow of buses day and night. We would like the speed bump to be removed to fix this problem - it is creating damage to our house and even the road is showing damage from the pounding weight of the buses. There is no need for two speed bumps to be present in such a short section of the road that already has roundabouts at either end and parked cars which by already naturally slows down the traffic.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Melford Road, Dulwich, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105916&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Roads/highways</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105916</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:22:05 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.444287 -0.065082</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dumped bag of old clothes, 2nd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105914</link>
<description>Dumped bag of old clothes&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8105914.0.jpeg?bca330af&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Darenth Road, East Wickham, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105914&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Alleyway</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105914</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:20:45 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.470975 0.107264</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dumped shopping trolley, 2nd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105908</link>
<description>Dumped shopping trolley&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8105908.0.jpeg?85bdfc2a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Wickham Street, East Wickham, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105908&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105908</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:20:17 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.470915 0.105215</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dumped shopping trolley and rubbish, 2nd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105905</link>
<description>Dumped shopping trolley and rubbish bags&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8105905.0.jpeg?1521551e&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Beal Close, East Wickham, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105905&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Alleyway</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105905</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:20:05 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.471349 0.106795</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dumped shopping trolley and rubbish, 2nd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105903</link>
<description>Dumped shopping trolley and rubbish bags&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8105903.0.jpeg?b465a4a9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Beal Close, East Wickham, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105903&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Alleyway</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105903</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:19:50 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.4714 0.106041</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Litter on the street and casuing pest issue, 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105883</link>
<description>There is too much litter on the street and it is causing problem for childrens to pass through the way. We cant even take out kids straller due to litter and my child was about to fall due to it. This is everytime issue if you can put a notice there and near to the stairs of flat dont throw litter. I stay in flat and observed things kept outside charity shop but people bring them in night and throw it. Moreovet, cofee pot gus whose bin are there he always throw extra bin at stairs entrance and it is hard fof us to walk down.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8105883.0.jpeg?6fc531ad&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Springfield Road, Welling, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105883&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street cleaning and litter</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105883</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:50:18 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.462652 0.108486</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Light out, 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105879</link>
<description>Lamp post outside 3 Wicksteed close. It keeps going out. It needs replacing. It is very dark in the close. My daughter is visually impaired going into the winter it needs sorting. She struggles in winter with the darkness already&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Wicksteed Close, Coldblow, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105879&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Lamp post</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105879</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:44:22 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.430669 0.165441</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Noisy any time a vehicle pass over it, 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105867</link>
<description>Noisy any time a vehicle pass over it.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8105867.0.jpeg?6354b75e&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): New Kent Road, Walworth, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105867&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Manhole Cover - Damaged (rocking or noisy)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105867</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:32:08 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.494103 -0.092405</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ongoing Fly-Tipping and Street Obstruction, 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105866</link>
<description>Rubbish has been left on the street for weeks without removal, and the situation has now worsened, with the waste being used by homeless individuals to build a makeshift camp.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This is creating not only an eyesore but also a clear health and safety hazard for residents and passers-by. The accumulation of waste and the obstruction of common areas are unacceptable, and urgent action is needed to address this matter.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8105866.0.jpeg?fe55b24d&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 151,153, Bermondsey Street, Old Kent Road, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105866&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street - Furniture Cleaning</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105866</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:31:23 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.499453 -0.080446</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Loose manhole cover, 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105863</link>
<description>Everytime a car drives over it makes a loud noise.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8105863.0.jpeg?a34885a4&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Bayswater Road, Paddington, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105863&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Broken drain cover</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105863</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:29:41 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.511436 -0.176601</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree on Timbercroft Lane, 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105856</link>
<description>Don&amp;#39;t close this report until it&amp;#39;s truly fixed. There is a tree lying on Timbercroft Lane between the tattoo shop and Who&amp;#39;d A Thought it pub on 7 Timbercroft Lane. Please remove the tree as criminals left it there.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8105856.0.jpeg?0a8322a3&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, The Slade, Plumstead, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105856&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fly Tipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105856</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:29:00 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.479052 0.087423</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Brand New Street Light not working., 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105800</link>
<description>This new street light has never worked since it was installed a couple of weeks ago. The light is outside number 16 Princes Plain BR2 8LE.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Lower Gravel Road, Bromley Common, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105800&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Light Not Working</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105800</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:04:06 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.378638 0.049796</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dumped Items, 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105770</link>
<description>On North Cray Road at the junction with Bunkers Hill, Sidcup: Please could you remove two dumped builders sacks of waste from the pavement.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Bunkers Hill, North Cray, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105770&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105770</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:01:44 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.429205 0.138613</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>