<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.55761;lon=0.073477;d=20</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.55761,0.073477/20" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Opposite the Dry Cleaners next to the Alliance pub, 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705847</link>
<description>There is a pot hole the size of a small crater that&amp;#39;s been here at least a year and is getting bigger. This is a road of heavy traffic. Fire engines and buses go past. Every 3 seconds a car hits this pot hole and the walls of my house shake. We are all at our wits end. There are so many reports about this particular pot hole but nothing has been done. Please please fill this pot hole as a matter of urgency&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 32, Mill Lane, West Hampstead, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705847&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Potholes</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705847</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.551124 -0.201452</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Barriers, 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705842</link>
<description>Yellow barriers have been placed in the parking bays. This is against planning regulations as the bays have not been requested by the site to be taken out of action. This has occurred outside 55 little birches.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 55, Little Birches, Longlands, Sidcup, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705842&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Obstructions on pavements and roads</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705842</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.43412 0.088925</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pavement has collapsed and there is a permanent puddle across the whole pavement, 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705835</link>
<description>The pavement has collapsed at this location and rain water does not drain away. It has been getting steadily worse and it is now very difficult to walk on the pavement and avoid the deep puddle.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8705835.0.jpeg?98295ace&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Valley Road, Streatham, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705835&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/footpaths</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705835</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.427333 -0.120461</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Debris and Grass Verge Damage, 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705829</link>
<description>There is a huge amount of debris left from the building site on 55 Little Birches all the way up from Little Birches to the middle of Harland Avenue making it unsafe to walk with my child on the pavements now because of building site debris (this is not just dirt and rocks but also glass/nails etc). The grass verges are also damaged where they have been swinging their lorries up on the verges along with paving slabs which is dangerous to myself and my child. They should have to hire a road sweeper as part of the planning. Please send a council official/health and safety investigator.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 55, Little Birches, Longlands, Sidcup, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705829&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street cleaning and litter</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705829</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.434082 0.088939</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Marlborough park avenue and burnt oak lane leaf clearance on side of road and pavement, 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705792</link>
<description>Slushy leaves everywhere, becoming icy and slippery in the cold. Council have been before but observed sitting in their vans most of the day instead of doing anything! Leaves are all over pavement and side of the road at the burnt oak end of Marlborough park avenue plus burnt oak lane outside of entrance to bruford college/the glades and all along pavement towards Holy trinity school. My child slipped on these today as slushy. When it&amp;#39;s icy its really dangerous! Needs clearing asap&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8705792.0.jpeg?b2a3c3ad&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 41, Marlborough Park Avenue, Blackfen, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705792&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street cleaning and litter</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705792</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.440403 0.102455</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fly tipping, 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705778</link>
<description>3 years. Repeated fly tippers. Always at night in a van. Covering their number plates. Waste is restricting access to our bins particularly for residents with mobility issues.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8705778.0.jpeg?461c7197&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Foxgrove Road, Beckenham, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705778&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytip</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705778</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.411853 -0.016726</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>30 inch pothole, 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705776</link>
<description>Water is collecting and splashing. It’s unsafe for pedestrians and wheelchair users.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8705776.0.jpeg?1facc258&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Surrey Quays Road, Rotherhithe, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705776&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Potholes</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705776</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.496434 -0.051443</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abandoned car, 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705756</link>
<description>The car has been parked / abandoned for longer than 40 days&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8705756.0.jpeg?fe086734&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest address to the pin placed on the map (from OS Places API): Bushberry Road, Hackney, London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705756&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned Vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705756</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.545999 -0.034613</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Uneven paving slab, 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705737</link>
<description>Council recently attended and removed an uneven paving slab which was causing trip hazard and filled with tarmac. The paving slab next to it is now lifting and has to be continually pushed down to prevent anyone tripping.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8705737.0.jpeg?2409635a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Ashcroft Avenue, Blackfen, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705737&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Damaged pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705737</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:02:34 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.449676 0.101563</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Thorough litter pick required on Alwyn estate, grange walk, 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705709</link>
<description>Please thoroughly carry out a litter pick on the Alwyn estate Grange walk, especially in the small garden area immediately behind the communal bin area.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8705709.0.jpeg?8b775ad9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Radcliffe Road, Old Kent Road, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705709&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Litter Pick</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705709</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.496881 -0.079583</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lighting in the shelters by the boiler house and the main road around and before the roundabaouts do no work. The lighting around Thanesmead it is extremely poor and we feel unsafe coming back home both in the road and around the streets, 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705706</link>
<description>Many light post around Thanesmead roads and streets do not work. We are tax payers that do not feel safe around the area due to the lack of lighting&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Carlyle Road, Thamesmead, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705706&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Damage - lighting not working (bus shelter)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705706</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.503726 0.119201</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>No light on birch walk section frequently used by residents, 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705692</link>
<description>There&amp;#39;s no light in this section of birch walk which connects residents from Loampit road to Bexley road, it is scary and pitch dark but the only pedestrian route for a lot of us, some being school kids due to a bus stop as well. Also, seen shady activity going on like two people disassembling what seemed like stolen bikes so CCTV would be good addition.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8705692.0.jpeg?c84ce2c1&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Birch Walk, Northumberland Heath, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705692&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Lamp post</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705692</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.479576 0.164771</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abandoned for over 6 months..no tax or MOT, 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705691</link>
<description>Abandoned vehicle&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Crescent Road, Beckenham, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705691&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicle</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705691</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.405279 -0.017333</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Alien estate area between pavement on grange walk and flats is getting lots of junk thrown in and need to be cleared, 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705684</link>
<description>Please remove the incrementally increasing amounts of rubbish and denris which are being thrown in the gap between Grange walk pavement and the council flats. Without being removed others just then add more to it and the problem gets worse so please act on this.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8705684.0.jpeg?54571941&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Grange Walk, Old Kent Road, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705684&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Communal Areas (Int)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705684</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:53:24 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.496628 -0.079269</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Parking on yellow lines on a bend too close to corner of garrolds close, 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705681</link>
<description>Using blue badges and parking outside white oak swimming pool on bend causing an obstruction on double yellow lines when there is suitable free parking at side of the facility . Buses and cars having difficulty passing . This is happening daily&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8705681.0.jpeg?4fb39374&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hilda May Avenue, White Oak, Swanley&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705681&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Car parking</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705681</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.400695 0.16997</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abandoned wheelie bin on Fendall street, near entrance to melford court, SE1 3DX, 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705672</link>
<description>Abandoned wheelie bin which has been on the pavement for at least two months. It is getting full up with general debris, rubbish and water. Please remove.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8705672.0.jpeg?8f4ce3fb&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Fendall Street, Old Kent Road, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705672&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pavements/footpaths</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705672</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.496612 -0.078409</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Leigham Court Road SW16 / Valley Road / Knolly’, 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705667</link>
<description>Leigham Court Road SW16 / Valley Road / Knolly’s Road junction a number of polycarbonate A3 size flyposter boards attached to traffic light poles plus on Valley Road about 15 yards from this junction pole with multi cycle route direction sign on it – see Google Streetview link below. Attached with plastic zip ties so you will need a knife or a box cutter to remove. https://www.google.com/maps/@51.4327129,-0.1178906,3a,23.3y,352.02h,88.33t/data=!3m7!1e1!3m5!1sRxQk38GNWBptrVri8MSHVw!2e0!6shttps:%2F%2Fstreetviewpixels-pa.googleapis.com%2Fv1%2Fthumbnail%3Fcb_client%3Dmaps_sv.tactile%26w%3D900%26h%3D600%26pitch%3D1.6710121694706288%26panoid%3DRxQk38GNWBptrVri8MSHVw%26yaw%3D352.0190741127922!7i16384!8i8192?entry=ttu&amp;amp;g_ep=EgoyMDI2MDExMy4wIKXMDSoKLDEwMDc5MjA2N0gBUAM%3D&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Valley Road, Streatham Hill, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705667&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flyposting</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705667</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:49:16 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.432943 -0.117832</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>It&#39;s not resolved yet, 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705656</link>
<description>The rubbish is still there, the issue is not resolved. It&amp;#39;s absolutely unacceptable. Why it&amp;#39;s marked as fixed???&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 27, Watts Street, Peckham, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705656&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping - General (Street)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705656</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:46:23 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.475914 -0.074992</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fambridge Close and Kangley Bridge Road, 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705618</link>
<description>Lots of potholes and lots of uneven surfaces, blocked drains.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Fambridge Close, Perry Vale, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705618&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Potholes</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705618</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.427213 -0.032975</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Huge 18 meter long puddle spears when there is heavy rain has caused grass verge to collapse and also pavement is collapsed and damaged in one place., 16th January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705606</link>
<description>Huge 18 meter long puddle appears in heavy rain as the drain doesn’t work properly. It’s a nightmare for pedestrians to pass because cars driving through spray up the deep water onto passers by, the pavement and the garden ans car of the property facing the puddle. There is damage to the grass verge it looks like it has sunk down below the level of the Kirb stone. The pavement also has a hole in by this collapsed verge. The kirb is a trip hazard and so is the pavement pot hole. This puddle has been reported several times. Each time the council say that the issue is fixed. Then the time it rains the enormous puddle reappears. Pedestrians have to wait watch traffic and run the length of ut to avoid being drenched. The rest of the pavement is also heaven and full of deep puddles in rain.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8705606.0.jpeg?a0269836&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Queen&#39;s Mead Road, Shortlands, Greater London&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705606&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Blocked Drain</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8705606</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.403397 0.007386</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>